{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Lakhjeet Singh\r\nlakhjeett@gmail.com\r\n+917015275262\r\n\r\nCAREER OBJECTIVE\r\n\r\nTo obtain an entry-level position within an organization that offers security and\r\nprofessional growth which requires strong analytical and technical skills.\r\n\r\nWORK EXPERIENCE\r\n\r\nSupervisior\r\nOld Grain Market Tohana / Sep 2016 - Jan 2018\r\n\r\nEDUCATION DETAILS\r\n\r\nSecondary with 62 % in 2010\r\nH.b.s.e\r\nHaryana Borad Of School Education\r\n\r\nSenior Secondary with 60 % in 2012\r\nH.b.s.e\r\nHaryana Borad Of School Education\r\n\r\nAdvance Diploma In Computer with 64 %\r\nin 2013\r\nRed Cross\r\nRed Cross\r\n\r\nIELTS with 5.0 CGPA in 2014\r\nGreay Matters\r\nBritish Council\r\n\r\nPERSONAL DETAILS\r\n\r\nAddress\r\n\r\nkamalwala\r\n\r\nDate of birth\r\n\r\n28/10/1994\r\n\r\nGender\r\n\r\nCity\r\n\r\nState\r\n\r\nPin Code\r\n\r\nNationality\r\n\r\nMale\r\n\r\nTohana\r\n\r\nHaryana\r\n\r\n125120\r\n\r\nIndia\r\n\r\nMarital Status\r\n\r\nUnmarried\r\n\r\nReligion\r\n\r\nSikh\r\n\r\nLanguages known\r\n\r\nEnglish, Hindi, Punjabi\r\n\r\nhereby declare that all the above facts are true to best of my knowledge.\r\n\r\nDECLARATION\r\n\r\n\fDate: 28/10/1994\r\nPlace: Tohana\r\n\r\nLakhjeet Singh\r\n\r\nPowered by TCPDF (www.tcpdf.org)\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[16,35,"EMAIL"],[37,50,"CONTACT"],[254,265,"ROLE"],[267,283,"ORGANISATION"],[284,290,"LOCATION"],[293,312,"DURATION"],[337,364,"EDUCATION"],[375,408,"INSTITUTION"],[412,446,"EDUCATION"],[457,490,"INSTITUTION"],[494,540,"EDUCATION"],[542,551,"INSTITUTION"],[566,593,"EDUCATION"],[595,625,"INSTITUTION"],[660,669,"LOCATION"],[766,793,"LOCATION"]]}]]}