{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["SAYYED SHAIFAL ABBAS \r\n\r\nPCHS, B-Wing, 3rd floor\r\nWorli Naka, Dr E Moses Rd,\r\nMumbai – 400018\r\nMobile: +919699304843\r\nEmail: Shaifalsayyed@icloud.com | Shaifalsayyed@gmail.com\r\n\r\n I am a very creative person with positive attitude towards life. \r\n\r\n I am looking for an opportunity where I can use my experience, creativity, \r\n\r\nideas, for the client and company benefits.\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nI have more than 10 years of work experience where I worked with DHL Logistic, \r\nHerbal Concept, WNS, & currently working as a Freelancer Creative head, Direct\r\nand Indirect Social Media Marketing. \r\n\r\n I have more than 7 years of experience in Customer Service and more than 2 \r\nyears of experience in Shipping Logistic.\r\n\r\nOVERVIEW  \r\n\r\nCAREER PROFILE \r\n\r\nWORK EXPERIENCE  \r\n\r\nJuly 2016 Till Date\r\n\r\nCreative Sales| Media marketing for various Small & MNC co.\r\n\r\nFront Desk Customer Interaction head for Bran-stuff Products\r\n\r\n Did Online Marketing Strategies for Narayana e-Techno School (Andheri)\r\n\r\n Did Copywriting for Radio Channel\r\n Handling Social Media Marketing for Online Clothing Brand (Brandstuffworldwide) \r\n\r\nFreelancing: As a freelancer I did online and offline marketing, online promotion, writing creative taglines \r\n& Assisting Customer Relation strategies. \r\n\r\n30 September 2013 till 29 July 2016.\r\n\r\nWorked with DHL Logistic as a Senior Executive for AU NFE IMPORT & previously worked with OFR\r\nUS EXPORT.\r\n\r\n Working on SAP for Forwarding Order Booking / Freight Booking\r\n\r\n\f Send Electronic Shipping Instruction\r\n Take care of Pre Alerts and handle station queries.\r\n Good hand on Ocean Export in creating House bill and Master bill.\r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n24 \r\n\r\n th   May 2012 to 29 September 2013\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\nWorked as a PN Senior Customer Service Executive with WNS for British Gas Process\r\n\r\n Dealing with customer enquiries via email and also making departmental calls to UK\r\n\r\nPage 2 of 3\r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n1  st    January 2007 to 10\r\nWorked as a Customer Service Executive with HERBAL CONCEPT (Discovery Herbs) \r\n\r\n th   May 2012\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n   Interact with Customers\r\n Solve their queries regarding our herbal products\r\n Place an Order & take care of the Shipping Department\r\n To look into Google Ad words and to update the advertisement on internet\r\n\r\nEducational Qualification:\r\n\r\nSecondary School Certificate Examination (Maharashtra State Board)\r\nSchool: VBM MODEL ENGLISH PRIMARY HIGH SCHOOL\r\nYear of Passing: March -2005\r\n\r\nHigher Secondary Certificate Examination (Maharashtra State Board)\r\nCOLLEGE: SIDDHARTH COLLEGE OF ARTS, SCIENCE & COMMERCE\r\nYear of Passing: March -2007.\r\n\r\nSYB.COM - 2009\r\nCOLLEGE: SIDDHARTH COLLEGE OF ARTS, SCIENCE & COMMERCE\r\n\r\nCertified Fitness Course – 2017\r\n Institute: IFSA (Intellectual Fitness & Sports Academy)\r\n\r\nCOMPUTER SKILLS\r\n\r\n Basic in Computers\r\n Google Ad words\r\n\r\nOTHER ACTIVITIES\r\n   Writing\r\n   Vlogging\r\n   Cycling\r\n\r\n\fFreelancing: As a freelancer I have helped few companies in there online marketing, online promotion \r\n\r\nand promoting their social page.\r\n\r\nPage 3 of 3\r\n\r\nPERSONAL DATA\r\n\r\n  DATE OF BIRTH\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n18th May 1990\r\n\r\n   PLACE OF BIRTH\r\n Mumbai\r\n\r\n   LANGUAGES\r\n\r\n English, Hindi, Marathi\r\n\r\n    MARITAL STATUS \r\n\r\n Single\r\n\r\nDATE:      10-June-2018\r\nPLACE:     MUMBAI                                                    (SAYYED SHAIFAL ABBAS)\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,20,"PERSON"],[25,93,"LOCATION"],[103,116,"CONTACT"],[125,149,"EMAIL"],[152,175,"EMAIL"],[453,465,"ORGANISATION"],[469,483,"ORGANISATION"],[485,488,"ORGANISATION"],[515,539,"ROLE"],[541,585,"ROLE"],[633,649,"ROLE"],[691,709,"ROLE"],[767,786,"DURATION"],[790,821,"ROLE"],[834,849,"ORGANISATION"],[853,889,"ROLE"],[894,913,"ORGANISATION"],[923,950,"ROLE"],[955,989,"ORGANISATION"],[1000,1011,"ROLE"],[1042,1064,"ROLE"],[1076,1111,"ORGANISATION"],[1326,1338,"ORGANISATION"],[1344,1378,"ROLE"],[1404,1419,"ROLE"],[1662,1704,"DURATION"],[1728,1764,"ROLE"],[1770,1797,"ORGANISATION"],[1950,1976,"ROLE"],[1982,1996,"ORGANISATION"],[2292,2332,"EDUCATION"],[2368,2405,"INSTITUTION"],[2439,2479,"EDUCATION"],[2516,2561,"INSTITUTION"],[2596,2603,"EDUCATION"],[2621,2666,"INSTITUTION"],[2670,2713,"CERTIFICATE"],[2715,2759,"INSTITUTION"],[2784,2802,"SKILLS"],[2806,2821,"SKILLS"]]}]]}