{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["CURRICULUM VITAE\r\n\r\nB.MOHAMED SABEEK\r\n\r\n39-A, Muslim West Street,\r\n\r\nNatham-624401\r\n\r\n           \r\n\r\n           Mobile: +91-9943856262\r\n\r\nDindigul District\r\n\r\nEmail: sabeek.93@rediffmail.com\r\n\r\nCARRIER OBJECTIVE:\r\n\r\nTo learn and function effectively in an organization and be able to deliver to the \r\n\r\nbottom-line and to upgrade my knowledge and skills and make a difference in whatever I do.\r\n\r\nACADEMIC CHRONICLES:\r\n\r\n B.E - ELECTRICAL AND ELECTRONICS ENGINEERING WITH 66% IN APRIL - 2015.\r\n\r\n S.B.M College of Engineering and Technology – Dindigul.\r\n\r\n DIPLOMA IN ELECTRICAL AND ELECTRONICS ENGINEERING WITH 78% IN APRIL - 2012.\r\n\r\n N.P.R College of Engineering and Technology – Natham.\r\n\r\n X – STANDARD STATE BOARD EXAMINATION IN APRIL - 2009.\r\n\r\n Sarva Seva higher secondary school – Natham.\r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n Worked was an Electrical Site Engineer and load estimator in DNR Electrical \r\n\r\nWorking as an Electrical Site Engineer (Erection, Commissioning & Procurement) on \r\n\r\nIndustrial and Commercial Projects in HARI Engineering ‘A’ Grade Electrical Contractor in \r\n\r\nPROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:\r\n\r\nFrom May 2015 to July 2016:-\r\n\r\nConsultancy Trichy.  \r\n\r\nFrom August 2016 to Till Date:-\r\n\r\nMadurai. \r\n\r\nNATURE OF JOB INVOLVED:\r\n\r\nLBS and RTCC panels.\r\n\r\n Erection and Commissioning of EB pole structures, RMU & FRTU unit, VCB panel,\r\n\r\n Erection, Testing and Commissioning of Transformers both Oil type and Dry type as well\r\n\r\nas Bus duct Erections both Sandwich and Air insulated type, Cable trays and Earth bits.\r\n\r\n Executing Electrification based on the design, Monitoring subordinates works, Maintain\r\n\r\nrecords and Man power Management.\r\n\r\n All Type of panel boards like MV Panel, MCC, MPCC, SSB, MLSB, APFC, VFD and\r\n\r\nHarmonic filter panels Testing, Erection and Commissioning.\r\n\r\n\fTECHNICAL SKILLS:\r\n\r\n Project Execution, planning and implementation at all stages.\r\n\r\n Preparation of Electrical Load Calculations and Single line diagram.\r\n\r\n Studying and execution as per electrical designs layout.\r\n\r\n Selections of cables, bus bars and switch gears ratings based on the load.\r\n\r\n Basic CADD, MS – Office, Selection of Light Fixtures based on LUX level.\r\n\r\nProject Title: Design of matrix converter based UPFC for grid integration of \r\n\r\n Preparation of BOQ’s & Tender Documents.\r\n\r\n Prepare daily progress reports and Checking RA bills.\r\n\r\n Co-Ordination with Client and Consultants.\r\n\r\nBasic Knowledge About:\r\n\r\n HVAC    – Chiller, VRF and AHU.\r\n\r\n CCTV     – DVR and NVR.\r\n\r\n Fire Protection – Conventional & Addressable.\r\n\r\n Building Management Systems.\r\n\r\nEngineering Project:\r\n\r\nrenewable energy source.\r\n\r\nPersonal Data:\r\n\r\nObjective:  Voltage Regulation.\r\n\r\nName\r\n\r\n : B. Mohamed Sabeek \r\n\r\nDate of Birth\r\n\r\n : 10/12/1993\r\n\r\nFather’s name\r\n\r\n : S.K. Basheer\r\n\r\nLanguages Known\r\n\r\n : English, Tamil\r\n\r\nPassport Number\r\n\r\n : P5468130\r\n\r\n : Indian\r\n\r\n : Playing chess and surfing internets.\r\n\r\nNationality\r\n\r\nHobbies\r\n\r\nDeclaration:\r\n\r\nknowledge.\r\n\r\nDATE   :\r\n\r\nPLACE :\r\n \r\n\r\n                           I hereby declare that the information furnished above is true to the best of my\r\n\r\nNAME\r\n\r\n(B.MOHAMED SABEEK)\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[20,36,"PERSON"],[46,64,"LOCATION"],[69,82,"LOCATION"],[120,134,"CONTACT"],[138,155,"LOCATION"],[166,190,"EMAIL"],[422,475,"EDUCATION"],[498,553,"INSTITUTION"],[558,616,"EDUCATION"],[639,692,"INSTITUTION"],[697,750,"EDUCATION"],[756,800,"INSTITUTION"],[824,848,"ROLE"],[853,867,"ROLE"],[871,885,"ORGANISATION"],[904,928,"ROLE"],[1014,1030,"ORGANISATION"],[1103,1124,"DURATION"],[1142,1149,"LOCATION"],[1160,1184,"DURATION"],[1190,1198,"LOCATION"],[1817,1834,"SKILLS"],[1836,1878,"SKILLS"],[1884,1952,"SKILLS"],[1958,2014,"SKILLS"],[2020,2094,"SKILLS"],[2100,2172,"SKILLS"],[2176,2299,"PROJECTS"],[2587,2635,"PROJECTS"],[2703,2720,"PERSON"]]}]]}