{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Vipul Rana\r\nDelhi, Delhi\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Vipul-Rana/e84eb15efed003ad\r\n\r\nTo secure a challenging position in an organization where I can effectively contribute my managerial\r\nand technical skills to build a successful career that will be helpful to the organization and my\r\ndevelopment while being innovative and flexible. \r\n \r\nSOFT SKILL \r\n \r\nOperating System XP, Win-7.8 \r\nEditor Application Ms -Word, Ms-Excel, Ms-PowerPoint. \r\nWeb Internet Surfing, E-mailing, online Marketing\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate to: Himachal Pradesh - Chandigarh, Chandigarh - Delhi, Delhi\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nMARKETING MANAGER\r\nRawal Chemicals - India\r\nAugust 2021 to Present\r\n\r\nexecutive\r\nkavya forex Pvt.Ltd\r\n2014 to September 2015\r\n\r\nMARKETING AND SALES MANAGER (MARKETING IN FILD AND ACHIEVE MONTHLY TARGET.\r\n\r\nhandling operation like money exchange and currency card. Since in 2014 to till sep 2015.\r\n3. 8 month experience in matrix cellular Services as a BED.\r\n4. 16 month experience T R Sawhney motors pvt ltd as a Ciaz consultant. Since 2016 to 2018\r\n5. One and half years experience in Tony Inn Hotel as sales operation Manager.\r\n6. Currently working at Tony Properties & Tony Buildcon Pvt Ltd last from 2 years.\r\n\r\n7. WORKING RESPONSIBILITY\r\n\r\n❖ As per working responsibilities' I have done lot of responsibility of various company.\r\nAs per my last company T R Sawhney motors pvt ltd. I was Ciaz consultant here. I have six cars sales target\r\nin a month's with complete all the paper work; arrange meeting with customer and also coordination\r\nwith cold calling.\r\n\r\nPERSONAL STRENGTH\r\n\r\n• Ability to Work under Time & Accuracy Pressure.\r\n• Self-Motivated.\r\n• Polite & Friendly Nature.\r\n\r\n\fEducation\r\n\r\nMBA\r\nH.P Board of education\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,10,"PERSON"],[12,24,"LOCATION"],[616,633,"ROLE"],[635,650,"ORGANISATION"],[660,682,"DURATION"],[686,695,"ROLE"],[697,716,"ORGANISATION"],[718,740,"DURATION"],[977,996,"DURATION"],[997,1023,"ORGANISATION"],[1029,1045,"ROLE"],[1069,1098,"DURATION"],[1102,1116,"ORGANISATION"],[1120,1144,"ROLE"],[1718,1721,"EDUCATION"],[1723,1745,"INSTITUTION"]]}]]}