{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Vikram Kumar Jha\r\nKatihar, Bihar\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Vikram-Kumar-Jha/6ae32578ca1eb3b3\r\n\r\n• To challenge with the career to achieve goal. \r\n• To have a good work for learning with earning.\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\r\n\r\nPersonal Details\r\n\r\nDate of Birth: 1992-01-02\r\nEligible to work in: India\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nsale and marketing\r\nSatin finance Pvt ltd - Delhi, Delhi\r\nFebruary 2017 to July 2018\r\n\r\nAccounts Assistant\r\nRaj Furnitures - Delhi, Delhi\r\nJanuary 2014 to May 2018\r\n\r\nDear sir/madam,\r\nSales  and  marketing  high  lable  confidence  power  for  customer  support  services  and  sales  our\r\nproducts......\r\n\r\nI  Have  good  knowledge  of  Computer  operator,  banking  and  finance,  Account  Assistant,and  filed\r\nExecutive,and supervisor and other works.\r\nPlease give me a chance, and my first priority Work therefore Work is Duty and Duty is Worship for me.\r\n\r\nSales and Marketing Representative\r\nSunshine global insurance company - Purnia, Bihar\r\nJanuary 2014 to January 2017\r\n\r\nSales and marketing executive\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nB.COM in Ac,B's,Eco,Eng, Enterpenure, Hindi\r\nPurnea College Purnea - Purnia, Bihar\r\n2009\r\n\r\n\fB.com\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Sales and marketing\r\n\r\n• Computer skills\r\n\r\n• English\r\n\r\n• Typing\r\n\r\n• Hindi\r\n\r\n• Data entry\r\n\r\n• Microsoft Word\r\n\r\nAdditional Information\r\n\r\nMy work is mine salary,life\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,16,"PERSON"],[18,32,"LOCATION"],[347,365,"ROLE"],[367,388,"ORGANISATION"],[405,431,"DURATION"],[435,453,"ROLE"],[455,469,"ORGANISATION"],[486,510,"DURATION"],[910,944,"ROLE"],[946,979,"ORGANISATION"],[997,1025,"DURATION"],[1075,1098,"EDUCATION"],[1120,1134,"INSTITUTION"],[1177,1241,"SKILLS"]]}]]}