{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["SUMMARY   \r\n\r\nITI + DME in Mechanical Engineering with over 4 yrs. of experience in production Department as well as quality \r\ncontrol and quality assurance activities, having experience in Inspection & Testing of product, 5S, KIZEN .I am looking \r\nfor a position as a Quality control / quality assurance engineer in a dynamic and a progressive organization that would \r\nallow me to leverage my core competencies to achieve desired results and add value to the organization and its business \r\nprocess\r\n\r\nKEY SKILL & Synopsis\r\n\r\n Ability to handle diff. measuring instruments like Vernier Caliper, Micrometer etc.\r\n Work with confidence.\r\n\r\nOrganization: Maico Gulf LLC. RAS Al Khemaih (UAE)                                                                                          \r\n\r\nMAICO   GULF   LLC.  Is   HVAC   based  company.   Which   is  manufacturing   and   providing   all   type  of\r\nventilation system all over the Middle East and other countries. \r\n\r\nPROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE\r\n\r\n Sagar Baburao Bhadange\r\nPhone: +971525784704 \r\nIndia: +919371198022\r\nE-mail:Sagar.bhadange4@gmail.com\r\n              \r\n\r\nInspection & Testing of product.\r\nProblem solving – supervisory skills\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n Decision making skills\r\n\r\n Ability to work in Team\r\n\r\n Quality Assurance & Quality control Engineer \r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nSafety and quality conscious.\r\n\r\n          Car park ventilation system\r\n\r\nFan coil unit\r\nEnergy recovery ventilator\r\nSmoke ventilator \r\nEcology unit \r\nIndustrial fan \r\nDomestics fan. \r\n\r\nDesignation:  QA-QController  \r\n\r\nPeriod of Employment:  – DEC 2014 to Jan 2017.\r\n\r\nResponsibilities handled:\r\n\r\n Handling third party inspection for executing of job \r\n\r\nPreparation of monthly rejection report & graph\r\n\r\nControl of measuring instruments,  gauges & Calibration activity\r\n\r\nSupervision and inspection of works to ensure compliance to the requirements of specifications.\r\n Assures smooth operating of the inspection unit, maintain daily records and reports.\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nResponsible to follow and maintaining quality standards for processing material into partially finished or finished products.\r\nResponsible to follow methods and procedures for inspecting, testing, and evaluating the precision and accuracy of product\r\nand / or production equipment.\r\nIncoming, in process & final inspection. \r\n\r\n\r\n Witness and report on inspection and testing of materials & Product\r\n\r\nInspection as per relevant QAP/standards/client requirement.\r\n\r\nPage 1 of 4\r\n\r\n\fSuggestion improvements opportunity in the department/function. \r\n\r\n\r\n Vendor / Supplier development \r\n\r\nOrganization:  BAJAJ AUTO LTD. PUNE INDIA              \r\n\r\nDesignation: Assembly engineer \r\n\r\nPeriod of Employment:  – april2014 to NOV 2014.\r\n\r\nResponsibilities handled:\r\n\r\n Worked in engine assembly department.\r\n\r\n Engine Assembly of KTM ,Pulsar.200,220 \r\n\r\n Worked all stages on line start with gear box to end with engine testing. \r\n\r\nOrganization: KEC INTERNATIONAL LTD. NAGPUR INDIA\r\n\r\n                         KEC is the leading Tower manufacturing company across the globe (RPG Group)\r\n\r\nDesignation: CNC Engineer \r\n\r\nResponsibilities handled: \r\n\r\n Daily work management & shift handling.\r\n\r\n CNC Operating, programming.\r\n CNC maintenance as per schedule  \r\n\r\n Achieving production targets on shift to shift basis.\r\n\r\n Continuous monitoring of process to improve the quality.\r\n\r\nTaking actions for achieving quality targets.\r\n\r\nProduction planning & problem solving.\r\n\r\nOrganization: NRB BEARING LTD. THANE INDIA\r\n\r\n                                                     NRB Bearing Ltd. is a Leading in Bearing Manufacturer industry engaged in Design,\r\nManufacture & Supply various types of Bearing as per Market requirements & specifications.\r\n\r\nDesignation: Trainee.  \r\n\r\nPeriod of Employment:  – Sept 2006 to Sept 2009.\r\n\r\nResponsibilities handled:\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nOperating & Programming of CNC LATHE Machine\r\nCarrying out Inspection of material\r\n\r\nPage 2 of 4\r\n\r\n\fACADEMIC QUALIFICATION \r\n\r\nDiploma in Mechanical Engineering\r\n\r\nMSBTE MUMBAI\r\n\r\n University / Board\r\n\r\nGOVT ITI AKOLA – Mumbai Board\r\n\r\nMaharashtra State -  Delhi Board\r\n\r\nMaharashtra State Board Amaravati -  Mumbai Board\r\n\r\n48.67%\r\n\r\nPercentage\r\n\r\n62.%\r\n\r\n77.57%\r\n\r\n73.71%\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nCourse\r\n\r\nITI \r\n\r\nNCVT\r\n\r\nS.S.C.\r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n OTHER INFORMATION\r\n\r\n: First:  SAGAR\r\n\r\nMiddle: BABURAO\r\n\r\nLast: BHADANGE\r\n\r\nName\r\n\r\nDate of Birth\r\n\r\nGender\r\n\r\nMarital Status\r\n\r\nNationality\r\n\r\nPassport No.\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\n16th November 1988\r\n\r\n: Male\r\n\r\n: Unmarried\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\nIndian\r\n\r\n: K7582782\r\n\r\nLanguage Known\r\n\r\n: English, Hindi, Marathi \r\n\r\nE-Mail\r\n\r\n: Sagar.bhadange4@gmail.com    \r\n\r\nExpiry Date  (DD/MM/YYYY)\r\n\r\n010/01/2023\r\n\r\nContact Address\r\n\r\n: Bhadange’s house, vitthal nagar, Mothi Umari, Akola. Maharashtra. India Pin. 444001\r\n\r\nExpected CTC: Best of Industry \r\n\r\n                                        I affirm that the information furnished above are true & correct to the best of my knowledge. \r\n\r\nThanks & Regards,                                                                                                                                            Date\r\n\r\nPage 3 of 4\r\n\r\n\fSagar Baburao Bhadange\r\n\r\nPage 4 of 4\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[14,17,"EDUCATION"],[27,49,"EDUCATION"],[60,66,"DURATION"],[227,232,"ORGANISATION"],[287,313,"ROLE"],[656,671,"ORGANISATION"],[688,691,"LOCATION"],[786,805,"ORGANISATION"],[996,1018,"PERSON"],[1027,1040,"CONTACT"],[1050,1063,"CONTACT"],[1072,1097,"EMAIL"],[1151,1187,"SKILLS"],[1256,1291,"SKILLS"],[1511,1525,"ROLE"],[1556,1577,"DURATION"],[2591,2606,"ORGANISATION"],[2607,2611,"LOCATION"],[2612,2617,"LOCATION"],[2648,2665,"ROLE"],[2695,2717,"DURATION"],[2932,2954,"ORGANISATION"],[2955,2961,"LOCATION"],[2962,2967,"LOCATION"],[3061,3070,"ORGANISATION"],[3088,3100,"ROLE"],[3161,3176,"SKILLS"],[3197,3209,"SKILLS"],[3324,3334,"SKILLS"],[3444,3460,"SKILLS"],[3478,3494,"ORGANISATION"],[3495,3500,"LOCATION"],[3501,3506,"LOCATION"],[3563,3579,"ORGANISATION"],[3792,3815,"DURATION"],[3984,4017,"EDUCATION"],[4021,4026,"INSTITUTION"],[4027,4048,"INSTITUTION"],[4320,4325,"PERSON"],[4337,4344,"PERSON"],[4354,4362,"PERSON"],[4591,4616,"EMAIL"],[4735,4741,"LOCATION"],[4742,4754,"LOCATION"],[5130,5152,"PERSON"]]}]]}