{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["  INDRAJEET MAURYA\r\n  MECHANICAL ENGINEER   \r\n   Mailing Address:                                                   \r\n  296/1, New Priyaka Camp, Madanpur Khadar,\r\n   Sarita Vihar, New Delhi, Delhi - 110076 (INDIA)\r\n   Email : imaurya2018@gmail.com\r\n\r\nContect No. : +917523085511,+919818043477\r\n\r\n \r\nCAREER \r\n\r\n \r\n OBJECTIVE\r\n \r\n\r\nTo work in a globally competitive environment on challenging assignments this will\r\nexplore   myself   fully   and   realize   my   potential.   Looking   for   excellent   growth\r\nprospective towards the betterment of organization.\r\n\r\nEDUCATIONAL CREDENTIALS\r\n\r\n2010 - 2013          :      Diploma in Mechanical Engineering from SKCE Institute  \r\n                                        (Meerut) with 67%\r\n2008 - 2010            :      Intermediate from SMT SRD HSS, U.P. Board with 56%\r\n\r\n2006 - 2008            :      High School from PT JLN Inter College,U.P. Board \r\n                                        with 50%\r\n\r\nTECHNICAL SKILLS\r\n\r\n Air handling Unit (AHU) Installing and AHU Chilled Water Piping Connections.\r\n Assisted   HVAC   technician   in   installing   and   managing   cooling   and   heating\r\n\r\nsystems.\r\n\r\n Strong   background   in   reading   and   interpreting   instructions   and   sefety\r\n\r\nprocedures  associated  with  HVAC  processes.\r\n Proven ability to read schematics and work plans.\r\n Testing, pumps, motors, filters, coils, piping, diagnose and repair problems in\r\n\r\nthe  system  and  propose  relevant  solutions.\r\n\r\n Great  ability  to determine  whether  a part of a system or the system in whole\r\n\r\ncan  be repaired  or  will  need  to be replaced.\r\n\r\n Knowledge and ability to perform preventative and general maintenance tasks\r\n\r\non HVAC systems.\r\n\r\n    \r\nWORKING EXPERIENCE\r\n \r\n\r\n Worked   with  UBAID   CONSTRUCTIONS   &   CONSULTANTS,  as   a  “HVAC\r\nTECHNICIAN” during the period from 10th September 2013 to 25th November\r\n2015.\r\n\r\n Working   in  3  STEPS   ENGINEERING   HVAC   SOLUTIONS,  as   a   “HVAC\r\nTECHNICIAN”  during the period from 28th  November 2015 to till continue in\r\nservice.\r\n\r\n\fPASSPORT DETAILS\r\n\r\nPassport  No.                    -                   M1696206\r\nDate of Issue                     -                  28/08/2014\r\nDate of Expiry                    -                  27/08/2024\r\nPlace of Issue                    -                  Lucknow\r\n\r\nSUMMER TRAINING AND PROJECT\r\n\r\n Four weaks summer training at “Imperial Auto Industries Limited” \r\n\r\nFaridabad\r\n\r\n A Project Report on “Motorised Cran” \r\n\r\nSOFTWARE EXPOSURE\r\n\r\nOperating Systems :       Windows XP, Windows 7, Windows 8 and Internet\r\n                                                Surfing and Basic knowledge of  MS office Excel\r\n\r\nHOBBIES\r\nReading Books, Internet browsing Surfing on Net and Listening Songs\r\n\r\nPERSONAL PROFILE\r\n\r\nFather’s Name :                            Mr.Lalman Maurya\r\nDate of Birth :                               16-07-1993\r\nMarital Status :                             Single\r\nGender :                                        Male\r\nStrength :                                      Hard Working, Ability to mould  self  in\r\n                                                       teem work, Positive thinking\r\nNationality :                                  Indian\r\nLanguages known :                     Hindi & English\r\nPermanent Address :                   Vill. :         Fulhar Khurd\r\n                                                     Post :       Bansgaon\r\n                                                     District :  Gorakhpur (U.P.) – 273403, INDIA\r\n\r\nI hereby declare that the above information is true to the best of my knowledge.\r\n\r\nDECLARATION \r\n\r\nDate  : ____________  \r\nPlace : ____________\r\n\r\n\f                                                   \r\n\r\n        \r\n\r\n                                      INDRAJEET MAURYA \r\n\r\n                                                                     \r\n\r\n                                                                                    \r\n \r\n           \r\n \r\n \r\n \r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[2,18,"PERSON"],[22,41,"EDUCATION"],[180,189,"LOCATION"],[191,196,"LOCATION"],[226,247,"EMAIL"],[265,278,"CONTACT"],[279,292,"CONTACT"],[593,604,"DURATION"],[621,654,"EDUCATION"],[660,674,"INSTITUTION"],[719,725,"LOCATION"],[737,748,"DURATION"],[785,796,"INSTITUTION"],[821,832,"DURATION"],[868,888,"INSTITUTION"],[976,1010,"SKILLS"],[1092,1157,"SKILLS"],[1777,1816,"ORGANISATION"],[1827,1845,"ROLE"],[1869,1912,"DURATION"],[1932,1973,"ORGANISATION"],[1985,2003,"ROLE"],[2028,2077,"DURATION"],[2348,2355,"LOCATION"],[2422,2456,"ORGANISATION"],[2461,2470,"LOCATION"],[2496,2512,"PROJECTS"],[2564,2574,"SKILLS"],[2576,2585,"SKILLS"],[2587,2596,"SKILLS"],[2601,2666,"SKILLS"],[2691,2700,"SKILLS"],[2701,2706,"SKILLS"],[2853,2869,"PERSON"],[3530,3539,"LOCATION"],[3820,3836,"PERSON"]]}]]}