{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Jitendra Purviya                                                                                                                           \r\n\r\nG-67  Laxmi Nagar Delhi\r\n\r\nContact: +91-9685243467 \r\n\r\nObjective\r\n :  \r\n \r\n\r\nEducational Qualification:\r\n\r\nName of\r\nExam\r\nB.E- CS\r\n\r\nName of\r\nUniversity\r\nRGPV-Bhopal\r\n\r\nEmail: jeetsirts19@gmail.com                                               \r\n                                                                                                        \r\n\r\nTo obtain a creative and challenging position that enables me to gain valuable experience and improve \r\nmy technical skills that I am gaining as part of my degree course and academic projects.\r\n\r\nSchool/College\r\n\r\nSagar Institute Research Technology\r\n& Science Bhopal(MP)\r\n\r\nYear of\r\nPassing\r\n2012\r\n\r\nResults\r\n(%)\r\n70%\r\n\r\n12th\r\n\r\nMP. Board\r\n\r\nGovt.R.N.A. H.S  School Pipariya (MP)\r\n\r\n2008\r\n\r\n78%\r\n\r\n10th\r\n\r\nMP. Board\r\n\r\nGovt.R.N.A. H.S  School Pipariya (MP)\r\n\r\n2006\r\n\r\n78.6%\r\n\r\nTechnical Proficiency:\r\n\r\n Operating System:  Window 07-10, Ubuntu 16.04. \r\n\r\n\r\nScripting Language:  HTML, CSS, JS, Jquery ,Angularjs & PHP. \r\n\r\n Database: MYSQL,MongoDB,IndexedDB & Websql. \r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nFramework: Codeigniter,Laravel.\r\n\r\n Content Management System: Wordpress,Opencart.\r\n\r\n Area of Interest: Web development , Application development.\r\n\r\nExperience:  5 Years in PHP , Codeigniter and Laravel  Mysql .\r\n\r\n Company: Gten Technologies Pvt Ltd. \r\n Designation: Senior Software Engineer\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nFrom:  10/08/2017  To Present.\r\n\r\n Company: Tecgenome Consulting Pvt Ltd.\r\n\r\n Designation: Senior Associate Developer.\r\n\r\n\f\r\n\r\nFrom:  03/10/2016  To 06/07/2017  (9 Months ). \r\n\r\n Company: Aksoft  Pvt Ltd.. \r\n\r\n Designation: PHP Developer\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nFrom:  01/04/2013  To  31/05/2016  (38 Months ).\r\n\r\nProjects List\r\n :  \r\n \r\n    \r\n I have Recently Developed these websites .\r\nwww.bagabuilder.co.uk\r\nwww.shopbloom.in\r\nwww.karmaguruworld.com\r\nwww.attune.events\r\nwww.imetalsx.com\r\nwww.fuscobrownehealthcare.co.uk\r\nwww.icabanking.com\r\n :  \r\nTechnologies Used\r\n \r\n\r\n Client  Side Language:  HTML, CSS, JS, Jquery ,Angularjs.\r\nServer Side Language  : PHP , Codeigniter and Laravel. \r\n\r\n\r\n Databases: MYSQL,MongoDB.\r\n\r\n VCS: bitbucket  & Github\r\n\r\nExtracurricular Achievements\r\n \r\n\r\n :   \r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nTopper in 10th class at school level high school-06.\r\n the PRESIDENT in the 12th class science society i.e. of  my school.\r\n1st position in dance compitition at school level -08.\r\nParticipated in collage level T.S.A. cricket tournament 2010.\r\n\r\nPersonal Vitae:\r\n\r\nFather’s Name                      -     Mr. Rajabhaiya Purviya.\r\nPermanent Address              -     New Galla Mandi Road Hathwansh Pipariya (MP) \r\n\r\n Date of Birth                         -    9th Aug. 1990\r\n\r\n\r\n Marital status                        -     Single\r\n Nationality                            -     Indian\r\n\r\n Hobbies                                 -     Surfing internet, singing & play cricket.\r\n\r\nLanguages Known                -     Hindi , English\r\n\r\n      “I hereby declare that the above information's are true to best of my knowledge.” \r\n\r\n\fDate:…...................                                                                                           \r\n\r\nPlace: Delhi                                                                                         (JITENDRA PURVIYA)\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,16,"PERSON"],[161,166,"LOCATION"],[179,193,"CONTACT"],[265,272,"EDUCATION"],[297,308,"INSTITUTION"],[319,340,"EMAIL"],[711,757,"INSTITUTION"],[758,764,"LOCATION"],[765,767,"LOCATION"],[790,794,"DURATION"],[819,823,"EDUCATION"],[827,836,"INSTITUTION"],[840,872,"INSTITUTION"],[874,876,"LOCATION"],[881,885,"DURATION"],[896,900,"EDUCATION"],[904,913,"INSTITUTION"],[917,949,"INSTITUTION"],[951,953,"LOCATION"],[958,962,"DURATION"],[1022,1034,"SKILLS"],[1036,1042,"SKILLS"],[1078,1082,"SKILLS"],[1084,1087,"SKILLS"],[1089,1091,"SKILLS"],[1093,1099,"SKILLS"],[1101,1110,"SKILLS"],[1113,1117,"SKILLS"],[1134,1139,"SKILLS"],[1140,1147,"SKILLS"],[1148,1157,"SKILLS"],[1160,1167,"SKILLS"],[1188,1199,"SKILLS"],[1200,1208,"SKILLS"],[1241,1250,"SKILLS"],[1251,1260,"SKILLS"],[1284,1299,"SKILLS"],[1302,1326,"SKILLS"],[1343,1350,"DURATION"],[1407,1433,"ORGANISATION"],[1451,1475,"ROLE"],[1491,1514,"DURATION"],[1529,1558,"ORGANISATION"],[1577,1604,"ROLE"],[1621,1646,"DURATION"],[1649,1657,"DURATION"],[1676,1693,"ORGANISATION"],[1713,1726,"ROLE"],[1742,1768,"DURATION"],[1771,1780,"DURATION"],[2594,2617,"PERSON"],[3252,3257,"LOCATION"],[3347,3363,"PERSON"]]}]]}