{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["                                                                                                \r\n\r\nMahadev Das\r\n\r\nB.Tech in Civil Engineering from Techno India Batanagar,  \r\nBengal.\r\n (Approved by AICTE, New Delhi &\r\n affiliated to MAKAUT, Kolkata)\r\n\r\nwest \r\n\r\nPermanent address\r\nMedinipur.  \r\n\r\n             : Vill-Patpur. P.O:-Dhara. PIN:-722138. D.T:-West \r\n\r\nEmail Id\r\nMob. No.\r\n\r\n              State:- West Bengal.\r\n\r\n:  mdmahadevdas@gmail.com\r\n:  07278377048\r\n\r\nObjective: To  enhance and utilize  my  technical  knowledge and  skills  with  \r\nadvance opportunities and \r\nto  pursue a challenging carrier.\r\n Experiance:\r\n \r\nTata Housing, Bhubaneswar & GSRP ,Darjeeling.\r\nCurrent Position: Currently worked at “LARSEN &TOUBRO” for the project of \r\n“GSRP”,in Structural Department at Darjeeling. \r\n\r\n      Total 1 year experience in construction industry for  the project of \r\n\r\nKey Skills in Civil Engineering:\r\n\r\n Expertise to handle equipments ( slump cone test apparatus,\r\n      compressive cube testing machine, flakiness and elongation testing \r\napparatus and so on)\r\n      for control the quality at site as per IS code.\r\n Skilled in structural section with modern construction methodology.\r\n Familiar with Indian Codes.\r\n Efficient to prepare BBS, BOQ &BOM.\r\n\r\n \r\nAcademic Qualification:\r\nExamination\r\n\r\nInstitute Name\r\n\r\n B.Tech \r\n\r\nTechno India Batanagar\r\n\r\n    \r\n\r\n Higher \r\n\r\nSecondary\r\n Madhyamik\r\n\r\nNangi High School(H.S).\r\n\r\nWBCHSE\r\n\r\nBatanagar Sri Ramkrishna \r\nAshram Vivekananda \r\nVidyamandir.\r\n\r\nWBBSE\r\n\r\nBoard \r\nName\r\nMAKAUT\r\n\r\nYear Grade/\r\n\r\nPercentage\r\n\r\n80.04% \r\n\r\n201\r\n6\r\n\r\n201\r\n2\r\n201\r\n0\r\n\r\n67%\r\n\r\n72.25%\r\n\r\nSkills:\r\n\r\n Excellent communication skills in English, Bengali & Hindi.\r\n Has a good analytical & problem solving skills.\r\n Competent, punctual, responsible &motivating team player.\r\n\r\n\fIndustrial  visit & Project Works:\r\n\r\n CESC Power plant, for Budge Budge,WB 1days\r\n Calcutta River-Side Project, Kolkata for 2 days\r\n Metro railway project from Noapara to Airport(Tantia Construction Limited) for 30 days\r\n Raychak on gonges project (Ambuja Reality Development Ltd) for 30 days\r\n\r\nAdditional information:                                                                                                                                                                    \r\nActive member of  Sri Ramkrishna Ashram(Batanagar)  and Student member of \r\nIEI (Institute of Engineers India),Kolkata\r\n\r\nInterests:\r\n\r\nConstruction of bridge, high rise building & road, Concrete technology, Physics, \r\nMathematics. \r\n\r\nHobbies:\r\nTeaching, Reading news paper, Gardening.\r\n\r\nComputer Efficiency:\r\n\r\n Certified in course of Information technology Application\r\n MS office Application\r\n Autocad 2016\r\n\r\n Extra-Curricular Activities:\r\n\r\n Essay Writer(Have many certificate for essay writing)\r\n Varies kinds of social activity\r\n\r\n :  Sanatan Das\r\n :  Purnima Das\r\n\r\nPersonal Details :\r\nFather’s Name \r\nMother’s Name\r\nDate of Birth\r\nState \r\nNationality\r\nBlood Group\r\n               \r\n              All the information given here is correct and true to the best of my \r\nknowledge.\r\n\r\n :  West Bengal\r\n :  Indian\r\n    \r\n\r\n :  01st December, 1994\r\n\r\n :  A+\r\n\r\nDate:  \r\n\r\n                                                                                                                                    \r\nSignature\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[100,111,"PERSON"],[115,142,"EDUCATION"],[148,160,"INSTITUTION"],[175,182,"LOCATION"],[408,420,"LOCATION"],[427,449,"EMAIL"],[454,465,"CONTACT"],[631,643,"PROJECTS"],[645,656,"LOCATION"],[659,663,"PROJECTS"],[665,676,"LOCATION"],[716,732,"ORGANISATION"],[754,760,"PROJECTS"],[789,800,"LOCATION"],[817,834,"DURATION"],[1341,1347,"EDUCATION"],[1352,1374,"ORGANISATION"],[1425,1442,"ORGANISATION"],[1452,1458,"INSTITUTION"],[1472,1522,"INSTITUTION"],[1526,1531,"INSTITUTION"],[1599,1605,"DURATION"],[1609,1615,"DURATION"],[1617,1623,"DURATION"],[2700,2709,"SKILLS"],[2725,2732,"SKILLS"],[2872,2883,"PERSON"],[2889,2900,"PERSON"],[3124,3135,"LOCATION"]]}]]}