{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["CURRICULAM – VITAE (C.V.)\r\n\r\nA Z A M   W A R S I       4 9 4 / 9 - C / 3 7 A , S A R A I   H A S A N G A N J ,\r\n                                      Daliganj, Lucknow – 226001 U.P.\r\n\r\nIndia\r\n\r\n+917703056225,7499975841,  \r\n\r\n                                                                                                                                                               Mob. :\r\n\r\nOBJECTIVE \r\n \r\n.\r\n\r\n \r\n          _____________                                                                    \r\n \r\n\r\nTo work with a dynamic and professionally esteemed\r\norganization   where   my   skills   and   abilities   can   be\r\nutilized.\r\n\r\nEXPERIENCE\r\n\r\nUnder training of Alavi Associates, Chartered \r\nAccountant, Lucknow as an Accountant Since Feb. \r\n2008 to April 2011.\r\n\r\nContract Base Work Under Chartered Accountant :-\r\n\r\n2009   Era Educational Trust               Hardoi Road, \r\nLucknow, U.P – India \r\n\r\n2009  Taj Hotel                            Gomti Nagar, \r\nLucknow,U.P – India \r\n\r\n2009 - Brans Info Tech Pvt.Ltd.\r\n                                                                 Raj Nagar, \r\nGhaziabad,U.P - India  \r\nEmployer\r\n2011-to   till   date   in  A.Automovers   Pvt.Ltd.(Mahindra   &\r\nMahindra Group)     \r\n                                                                 \r\nDesignation :- Accountant \r\nDay to Day Accounting   & Finalisation book of\r\nAccount   Preperation   Balance   Sheet   &   Profit   &\r\nLoss Account. \r\n\r\n \r\nJob Responsibilities\r\n\r\n :-  \r\n\r\n1.   MIS   like   Daily   Collection   Report,   Monthly\r\n\r\nPetty cash expenditure details .\r\n\r\n\f2. Insurance Claim Reconciliation.\r\n\r\n3. Preparation of Monthly Financial reports .(Vat\r\n\r\n& Service Tax Report).\r\n\r\n4. Debtor & Creditor Reconciliation Statement .\r\n\r\n5. Preparation   of   all   types   of   vouchers   Entry   In\r\n\r\nTally .\r\n\r\n6. Recording  transactions   in daily   basis in  Tally,\r\n\r\nmaintaining books of accounts.\r\n\r\n7. Petty   Cash   Voucher   &   Invoices   Posting   Daily\r\n\r\nBasis In Tally.\r\n\r\ntransactions.\r\n\r\n8. Responsible   for   expenditure   and   collection\r\n\r\n9. Making outstanding detail & follow- up.\r\n\r\n10. Entries of cash Book, Sales Bills & Purchase\r\n\r\nBills etc.\r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n11. Cash Handling & Preparation of Day Book.\r\n\r\n12. Daily Revenue Collection & reconciliation.\r\n\r\n13.\r\n\r\nPetty   Cash   Management   &   cash   Book\r\n\r\nMaintain. \r\n\r\n14.\r\n\r\nPayment process.\r\n\r\n15. Credit Card Payments and follow up.\r\n\r\n16.\r\n\r\nStock   Audits   &   Cash   verification   Audit\r\n\r\nWork.\r\n\r\nsales reports\r\n\r\n17. Handled work related to monthly billing and\r\n\r\n            Preparation of ledgers & regular accounting.\r\n\r\n18.\r\n\r\n Assistance in the Final Accounts & Balance\r\n\r\nsheet.\r\n\r\n19.\r\n\r\nPreparation   and   Maintenance   of   various\r\n\r\nregisters like   \r\nPurchase   Register,   Sales   Register,   Journal\r\nRegister,   Debit   Note   Register,   Credit   Note\r\nRegister,   Stock   Register,   Post   DateCheque\r\n(PDC)Register,   Receipt   Register(RR),Payment\r\nRegister(PR).\r\n\r\n20. Experience   of   handling   general   ledgers,\r\n\r\naccount payables,    \r\naccounts receivable, sales, billing etc.\r\n\r\n\f21. Manage   the   collections   and   bank   statements\r\n\r\nreconciliation.\r\n\r\nreports.\r\n\r\n22. Responsible for processing tour and expense\r\n\r\n       23. Preparation of staff attendance, maintaining\r\n\r\nleave records    \r\n\r\n            for the employees.\r\n\r\n23.\r\n\r\n Client Reconciliation Statement.\r\n\r\nHandling day to day Accounts in Tally ERP.\r\n\r\n \r\n   Personality Traits\r\n \r\n\r\n Excellent communication and interpersonal \r\n\r\nskills.\r\n\r\n Ability to work in team as well as individually.\r\n\r\n Positive thinking and hardworking.\r\n\r\n Possess leadership qualities.\r\n\r\nPROFILE\r\n\r\nName  : Azam Warsi\r\n\r\nFathers Name   :  Mr.Nisar Warsi\r\n\r\nMother Name  : Mrs.Shammi Warsi\r\n\r\nMarital Status    :  Unmarried\r\n\r\nD.O.B.              : 14-08-1990\r\n\r\nLANGUAGES KNOWN\r\n\r\nPermanent   Address     :     494/9C/37A   Sarai   Hasan   Ganj,Daliganj,   Lucknow,\r\nUttar Pradesh –226001  India\r\n\r\n English  - Read  - Speak - Write \r\n Hindi     - Read  - Speak  - Write\r\n Urdu                 - Speak \r\n\r\nEDUCATION QUALIFICATION\r\n\r\n Intermediate – 2008 from U.P. Board, Allahabad\r\n B.Com . – (III Year 2012) from Lucknow University  \r\n\r\nCOMPUTER KNOWLEDGE\r\n\r\n  Accounting Software :  Tally – (All Version),Tally from IPCC Tally \r\nAcademy,Lucknow\r\n\r\n  Applicatons             :   Microsoft Office – MS Excel, MS Word & MS\r\nPower Point\r\n\r\n\f                                    Pagemaker & Internet.\r\n\r\nSTRENGTH                                     \r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n                               Effective in working as a team work.\r\n                            Professional in taking up responsibilities.\r\n                            Good interpersonal skills and hard working.\r\n\r\nINTERESTS\r\n\r\nChess,Cricket, running, computers.\r\n\r\nDate  :                                                                                 \r\nPlace  : Lucknow\r\n\r\nSignature\r\n\r\n4 9 4 / 9 - C / 3 7 A ,   S A R A I   H A S A N G A N J , D A L I G A N J   , L U C K N O W\r\nU T T A R   P R A D E S H - 2 2 6 0 0 1 ( I N D I A )\r\nM O B - 7 7 0 3 0 5 6 2 2 5 , 7 4 9 9 9 7 5 8 4 1\r\ne - m a i l :   a z a m w a r s i 2 6 @ g m a i l . c o m\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[29,48,"PERSON"],[160,167,"LOCATION"],[185,190,"LOCATION"],[194,218,"CONTACT"],[677,693,"ORGANISATION"],[695,717,"ROLE"],[719,726,"LOCATION"],[733,743,"ROLE"],[750,776,"DURATION"],[832,836,"DURATION"],[839,860,"ORGANISATION"],[890,897,"LOCATION"],[899,902,"LOCATION"],[905,910,"LOCATION"],[915,919,"DURATION"],[921,930,"ORGANISATION"],[973,980,"LOCATION"],[981,984,"LOCATION"],[987,992,"LOCATION"],[997,1001,"DURATION"],[1004,1028,"ORGANISATION"],[1108,1117,"LOCATION"],[1118,1121,"LOCATION"],[1124,1129,"LOCATION"],[1143,1164,"DURATION"],[1171,1194,"ORGANISATION"],[1195,1223,"ORGANISATION"],[3696,3706,"PERSON"],[3728,3742,"PERSON"],[3761,3777,"PERSON"],[3946,3953,"LOCATION"],[3956,3969,"LOCATION"],[3979,3984,"LOCATION"],[4127,4139,"EDUCATION"],[4142,4146,"DURATION"],[4152,4162,"INSTITUTION"],[4164,4173,"LOCATION"],[4177,4182,"EDUCATION"],[4197,4201,"DURATION"],[4208,4226,"INSTITUTION"],[4279,4284,"SKILLS"],[4374,4390,"SKILLS"],[4393,4401,"SKILLS"],[4403,4410,"SKILLS"],[4413,4428,"SKILLS"],[4921,4928,"LOCATION"]]}]]}