{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Hariprakash Yadav\nSadat, Uttar Pradesh\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Hariprakash-Yadav/7715ce0775a08904\n\nI want work with a reputed organization where I can learn and \nupgrade my skills and also contribute to.my knowledge and \nexperience to achieve organizational goal and achieved a highest \nposition in that\n\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\n\nWork Experience\n\nBI Developer\nDaksh Solution Pvt Ltd\nJanuary 2019 to January 2022\n\nEducation\n\nMaster's\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• SKILLS\n\nOnline Profile\n\nhttp://to.my\n\nharihcst@gmail.com\n*used power BI for visualisation\n• 7834916433 * Created relationship, actions, data\n• Village-rukunpur daragah post-baha blending, filter, parameter, hierarchies, calculated\nriyabad ghazipur(UP) fields, sorting, grouping, live connection.and in memory in both power BI and excel.\n\n• Indexing, and table partitioning -oprimizing report Power BI, SQL and DAX, Database Created all type\n\nof Graff and understanding in which knowledge MS Office suite situation its apply.\n\n• Employed solid understanding of relational database\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,17,"PERSON"],[25,38,"LOCATION"],[374,386,"ROLE"],[387,409,"ORGANISATION"],[410,438,"DURATION"],[521,539,"EMAIL"],[575,585,"CONTACT"],[885,888,"SKILLS"],[893,896,"SKILLS"],[971,980,"SKILLS"]]}],["Hariprakash Yadav\nSadat, Uttar Pradesh\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Hariprakash-Yadav/7715ce0775a08904\n\nI want work with a reputed organization where I can learn and \nupgrade my skills and also contribute to.my knowledge and \nexperience to achieve organizational goal and achieved a highest \nposition in that\n\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\n\nWork Experience\n\nBI Developer\nDaksh Solution Pvt Ltd\nJanuary 2019 to January 2022\n\nEducation\n\nMaster's\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• SKILLS\n\nOnline Profile\n\nhttp://to.my\n\nharihcst@gmail.com\n*used power BI for visualisation\n• 7834916433 * Created relationship, actions, data\n• Village-rukunpur daragah post-baha blending, filter, parameter, hierarchies, calculated\nriyabad ghazipur(UP) fields, sorting, grouping, live connection.and in memory in both power BI and excel.\n\n• Indexing, and table partitioning -oprimizing report Power BI, SQL and DAX, Database Created all type\n\nof Graff and understanding in which knowledge MS Office suite situation its apply.\n\n• Employed solid understanding of relational database\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,17,"PERSON"],[25,38,"LOCATION"],[374,386,"ROLE"],[387,409,"ORGANISATION"],[410,438,"DURATION"],[521,539,"EMAIL"],[575,585,"CONTACT"],[731,733,"LOCATION"],[813,819,"SKILLS"],[885,888,"SKILLS"],[893,896,"SKILLS"],[898,906,"SKILLS"],[971,980,"SKILLS"],[1043,1062,"SKILLS"]]}]]}