{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Jamal Pathan\nPune, Maharashtra\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Jamal-Pathan/15f4b709361014de\n\nWork Experience\n\nMarketing Executive\nForbes Marshall Private Limited\nApril 2020 to Present\n\nProjects & Existing grid customers - Steam System Division (Middle East, Africa, South Asia & South East\nAsia):\n\nMarket analysis and enabling Sales generation to supplement growth of the Food & Beverage process\nIndustry segment. Making various technical & marketing tools to provide effective solutions & concepts\nfor  different  segments  of  process  industry  like  Beverages,  Brewery,  Dairy,  Edible  Oil  Refineries,\nConfectioneries etc., with effective product proposals covering equipment specific solutions with help of\na P&ID (technical drawings) and other marketing tools with deliverables to the end users. This resulted\nimprovement in the strike rate by 35% and surpassing 19-20 achievement in 2020-21 H1 and 2020-21\nachievement in 2021-22 H1 itself!\n\nMarketing Executive\nForbes Marshall Private Limited - Pune, Maharashtra\nMarch 2013 to Present\n\nMarketing Executive - Global Projects\nForbes Marshall Private Limited\nOctober 2017 to March 2019\n\nMiddle East, Africa, South Asia & South East Asia):\nGreen Field Projects & Expansion Projects for Forbes Marshall International operations\n• Identification of key greenfield projects and selective categorisation based on numerous parametric.\n• Defining project pitch for each industry segment with distinguished package solution.\n• Demonstrating key benefits to each identified client with right design of the system to optimize overall\nplant efficiency with the help of a P&ID (technical drawings) and other demonstrating tools.\n• Cross referencing similar nature of projects executed in the past.\n• Ensuring thorough adaptability to Customer buying process.\n• This resulted in an unprecedented growth of 15% Year on Year.\n\nMarketing Associate - Actual Users & Small Projects\nForbes Marshall Private Limited\nApril 2015 to October 2017\n\nMiddle East, Africa):\nAs a business owner for assigned countries, identified target customers and analysed market scenarios to\nsupplement business growth, documented customer benefits after innovative solutions implementation\nand travelled extensively to demonstrate related benefits to build a strong customer base.\n\n\fMarketing Associate - Integral Branding & Market Research Analysis for\nInternational Operations\nForbes Marshall Private Limited\nApril 2014 to March 2015\n\n• Market Research & Analysis for International Operations\n-  Country  wise  business  analysis  for  Egypt,  Kenya,  Middle  East,  Indonesia  &  Malaysia  for  business\nexpansion with respect to actual user grid, corporate plants and OEMs for steam and process control\nsystems.\n- Developing 5-year plan with marketing and sales strategies for the above mentioned 5 focused markets\nwith right approach for Steam Systems Business.\n• Marketing, Branding & Digital Tools: Design & Development of steam system and process control loops\nfor various process industries demonstrating ideal solutions with benefits. Developing Mobile Apps and\nweb portal calculators for finding various energy parametric.\n\nGraduate Trainee Engineer\nForbes Marshall Private Limited\nMarch 2013 to April 2014\n\n•  Developing  Marketing  Tool:  Developing  Steam  System  Data  Base  (SSDB)  Calculator.  Which  helped\nfield sales engineers to complete the technical proposals in a simple yet effective manner with thorough\nunderstanding of studied plant depicting the losses and potential to improve on the same.\n•  Intensive  Customer  visits  West  Region  domestic  sales  branches,  India  with  Branch  Engineers  for\nGeneration and promotion of Business related to products & specific proposals\n• Product support & review\n\nEducation\n\nBachelor of Engineering in Mechanical Engineering\nVisvesvaraya Technological University\n2007 to 2011\n\nHigher Secondary Certificate\nBasaveshwar Science College, Pre-University, State Boards\n2004 to 2007\n\nCertificate of Secondary Education in Indian\nSt. Anne's Convent High School, State Boards\n2003 to 2004\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• Marketing Sales Generation Pre-Sales Activities Business Development Industrial & Automation\nProducts Project Engineering Project Sales Strategic Planning Revenue Growth Expert Marketing\nand Sales executive driving strategic initiatives for optimizing sales & business development of\nindustrial process control and energy conservation solutions; delivering support for pre-sales\nactivities, securing project sales, planning, executing, and managing business operations with focus\non achieving targets for revenue growth and sales generation. PROFILE SNAPSHOT\n\n• Develop Business growth plan and formulate initiatives for the assigned product and Industry\n\nverticals to meet the sales targets.\n\n\f• Work seamlessly with field sales and other support functions to technically analyse the key sales\nproposals and requirements, RFPs / Tenders and provide strategic inputs to win the proposals.\n\n• Adept at project engineering & management from planning, defining project scope, budgeting,\n\ndeploying cost controls, planning & managing resources, identifying & eliminating risks, for ensuring\ntimely delivery.\n\n• Preparing pitch for the proposals against the competition with distinctive deliverables to the end\ncustomer with the deep understanding of the process or the products for effective strike rates.\n\n• Support in building Key Account Customers (KAM), OEMs globally by cross referencing and promoting\n\neffective sales proposals.\n\nand Industry vertical.\n\n• Monthly/Quarterly/Yearly forecast and analysis of orders and projections for the assigned product\n\n• International exposure in leading global sales team and developing business across South Asia,\n\nSouth East Asia, Middle East and North Africa territories. KEY DELIVERABLES\n\n• Good Knowledge of process industries (Food, Beverages, Breweries, Pharmaceutical, Chemicals,\n\nTextiles, Edible Oil refineries, Hospitality etc.) and technical understanding of key process equipment\nused.\n\n• Developing Teams in International & Indian territories in-line with organisation initiatives for\n\nsustained sales activities and revenue growth.\n\n• Experience in Brand strategy and positioning as market leader in Steam systems and process control\n\nsolutions.\n\nmarket customers.\n\n• Combined Sales and Technical approach for effective proposals.\n\n• Good understanding of Indian and International (South Asia, South East Asia, Middle East, Africa)\n\n• Excellent communication and presentation skills. PRODUCTS HANDLED Boilers, Heat Exchangers,\nValves, Control Valves, Basic process Control instrumentations, Industrial IOT & software services,\nSteam and Condensate ancillaries, Steam Filters, mechanical pumps, Flow measuring devices,\ncustomized packaged steam & heat recovery solutions. CAREER GRAPH Microsoft Office (Word,\nExcel, PowerPoint)\n\n• Business development\n\n• Communication skills\n\n• Marketing\n\n• Microsoft Excel\n\n• Negotiation\n\n• Sales\n\nOnline Profile\n\nhttp://www.linkedin.com/in/jamal-pathan-743b4197\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[13,17,"LOCATION"],[19,30,"LOCATION"],[124,143,"ROLE"],[144,175,"ORGANISATION"],[176,197,"DURATION"],[236,257,"PROJECTS"],[259,270,"LOCATION"],[272,278,"LOCATION"],[280,290,"LOCATION"],[293,308,"LOCATION"],[312,327,"SKILLS"],[965,984,"ROLE"],[985,1016,"ORGANISATION"],[1019,1023,"LOCATION"],[1025,1036,"LOCATION"],[1037,1058,"DURATION"],[1060,1079,"ROLE"],[1098,1129,"ORGANISATION"],[1130,1156,"DURATION"],[1158,1169,"LOCATION"],[1171,1177,"LOCATION"],[1179,1189,"LOCATION"],[1192,1207,"LOCATION"],[1883,1902,"ROLE"],[1935,1966,"ORGANISATION"],[1967,1993,"DURATION"],[1995,2006,"LOCATION"],[2008,2014,"LOCATION"],[2314,2333,"ROLE"],[2410,2441,"ORGANISATION"],[2442,2466,"DURATION"],[2569,2574,"LOCATION"],[2577,2582,"LOCATION"],[2585,2597,"LOCATION"],[2600,2609,"LOCATION"],[2614,2622,"LOCATION"],[2760,2766,"DURATION"],[2900,2909,"SKILLS"],[2911,2919,"SKILLS"],[3166,3191,"ROLE"],[3192,3223,"ORGANISATION"],[3224,3248,"DURATION"],[3779,3828,"EDUCATION"],[3829,3866,"INSTITUTION"],[3867,3879,"DURATION"],[3881,3909,"EDUCATION"],[3910,3937,"INSTITUTION"],[3939,3953,"INSTITUTION"],[3955,3967,"INSTITUTION"],[3968,3980,"DURATION"],[3982,4016,"EDUCATION"],[4027,4057,"INSTITUTION"],[4072,4084,"DURATION"],[4108,4117,"SKILLS"],[4118,4134,"SKILLS"],[4135,4155,"SKILLS"],[4156,4176,"SKILLS"],[4177,4209,"SKILLS"],[4210,4229,"SKILLS"],[4230,4243,"SKILLS"],[4244,4262,"SKILLS"],[4263,4277,"SKILLS"],[4285,4294,"SKILLS"],[4299,4314,"SKILLS"],[4465,4472,"SKILLS"],[4557,4576,"SKILLS"],[5750,5760,"LOCATION"],[5763,5778,"LOCATION"],[5780,5791,"LOCATION"],[5796,5808,"LOCATION"],[6444,6454,"LOCATION"],[6456,6471,"LOCATION"],[6473,6484,"LOCATION"],[6486,6492,"LOCATION"],[6846,6862,"SKILLS"],[6864,6868,"SKILLS"],[6870,6875,"SKILLS"],[6877,6887,"SKILLS"],[6892,6912,"SKILLS"],[6916,6936,"SKILLS"],[6940,6949,"SKILLS"],[6953,6968,"SKILLS"],[6972,6983,"SKILLS"],[6987,6992,"SKILLS"]]}]]}