{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Jayashree Das\nBhubaneshwar, Orissa\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Jayashree-Das/0ceb08e766b6a5c3\n\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\n\nWork Experience\n\nJunior Developer\nN-Technology, Research Centre Pvt. Ltd.\nFebruary 2021 to Present\n\n• Work and design various electronics components and sensors used in various projects\n• Develop both hardware and software for controllers\n• Understand the circuit design and functionality of all the products and their respective components\n• Assist in the development of different IoT products\n• Working knowledge on IoT strategy, standards, and protocols\n\nSTUDENT MENTOR\n• Guide practically as well as theoretically about their projects\n• Make students understand basic components and sensors used in projects\n• Give ideas on design and work on their required area\n\nSKILL\n•  Having  excellent  exposure  in  hardware  design  for  processor  interfacing  devices  and  their\ntroubleshooting\n• Knowledge of core architecture of AVR controller and work with every functional block including ADC,\nTimer, and PWM.\n• Experience with embedded system protocols like USART, SPI, and I2C\n• Hands-on experience with developing boards such as ESP8266 and Arduino\n• Good understanding and working knowledge on IoT architecture as well as protocols\n• Design and oversee the development of IoT platform ecosystem including sensors, gateways, actuators,\nand mesh\nnetworks\n• Ability to work with all IoT-level products with required internet protocols\n• Experience with Embedded-C language\n\nEducation\n\nM-TECH in Engineering\nCOLLEGE OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY - Bhubaneshwar, Orissa\n2018 to 2020\n\nB-TECH in Branch\nKMBB COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY - KHORDA, ODISHA, IN\n2013 to 2017\n\n\fTRIVENI ACADEMY +2 SCIENCE COLLEGE - Bhubaneshwar, Orissa\n2011 to 2013\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• Atmel Studio-7\n\n• AVR Loader v1.0\n\n• Arduino-IDE\n\n• Proteus-8\n\n• Blynk-app\n\n• Arduino RC\n\n• Embedded C\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[14,26,"LOCATION"],[28,34,"LOCATION"],[160,176,"ROLE"],[177,216,"ORGANISATION"],[217,241,"DURATION"],[1104,1109,"SKILLS"],[1111,1114,"SKILLS"],[1120,1123,"SKILLS"],[1177,1184,"SKILLS"],[1189,1196,"SKILLS"],[1243,1259,"SKILLS"],[1462,1480,"SKILLS"],[1499,1518,"SKILLS"],[1531,1537,"EDUCATION"],[1553,1590,"INSTITUTION"],[1593,1605,"LOCATION"],[1607,1613,"LOCATION"],[1614,1626,"DURATION"],[1628,1634,"EDUCATION"],[1645,1687,"INSTITUTION"],[1698,1704,"LOCATION"],[1709,1721,"DURATION"],[1724,1758,"INSTITUTION"],[1761,1773,"LOCATION"],[1775,1781,"LOCATION"],[1782,1794,"DURATION"],[1818,1832,"SKILLS"],[1836,1851,"SKILLS"],[1855,1866,"SKILLS"],[1870,1879,"SKILLS"],[1883,1892,"SKILLS"],[1896,1906,"SKILLS"],[1910,1920,"SKILLS"]]}]]}