{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Jessnamol Joy\nKottayam, KERALA, 686613, IN\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Jessnamol-Joy/6ffb477abd43f76c\n\nTo devote my abilities to the institution which admits me so as to achieve a high level of personal and\nprofessional satisfaction and to obtain a high level of performance. \nPersonal Strength \n \n✓ Optimistic \n✓ Effective communication skills \n✓ Hard Working \n✓ Good Leadership Quality \n✓ Self Confidence \n✓ Adaptive\n\nWilling to relocate to: Thiruvananthapuram, Kerala - Kochi, Kerala - Bengaluru, Karnataka\n\nPersonal Details\n\nDate of Birth: 1997-06-02\nEligible to work in: India\nHighest Career Level: Fresher\nIndustry: Technology\n\nWork Experience\n\nPHP Developer\nNesote Technologies Pvt Ltd - Kottayam, Kerala\nJuly 2021 to November 2021\n\nDeveloper\n\nEducation\n\nHigher Secondary(12th Pass) in Science\nSt.michelesSt. Michael’s Higher Secondary School, Kaduthuruthy - Kaduthuruthy, Kerala\nJune 2013 to Present\n\nMaster's in MSc.Computer Science\nMG university - Kottayam, Kerala\nJune 2018 to July 2020\n\nBachelor's in Computer Science\nCollage of Applied sciences kaduthuruthy - Kaduthuruthy, Kerala\nJune 2015 to March 2018\n\n\fSkills / IT Skills\n\n• Language: Python, C, C++, Php, Java \nOperating System: Windows10, Linux \nApplication package & tool: MS Office, Power Point \nWeb technologies: Html, CSS, Xml \n \n.Areas of Interest \n \nProgramming \nsoftware development\n\n• PHP\n\n• JavaScript\n\n• HTML5\n\n• MySQL\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[24,30,"LOCATION"],[461,479,"LOCATION"],[481,487,"LOCATION"],[490,495,"LOCATION"],[497,503,"LOCATION"],[506,515,"LOCATION"],[517,526,"LOCATION"],[593,598,"LOCATION"],[668,681,"ROLE"],[682,709,"ORGANISATION"],[712,720,"LOCATION"],[722,728,"LOCATION"],[729,755,"DURATION"],[779,795,"EDUCATION"],[796,805,"EDUCATION"],[818,866,"INSTITUTION"],[883,895,"LOCATION"],[897,903,"LOCATION"],[904,924,"DURATION"],[926,958,"EDUCATION"],[959,972,"INSTITUTION"],[975,983,"LOCATION"],[985,991,"LOCATION"],[992,1014,"DURATION"],[1016,1046,"EDUCATION"],[1047,1087,"INSTITUTION"],[1090,1102,"LOCATION"],[1104,1110,"LOCATION"],[1111,1134,"DURATION"],[1169,1175,"SKILLS"],[1177,1178,"SKILLS"],[1180,1183,"SKILLS"],[1185,1188,"SKILLS"],[1190,1194,"SKILLS"],[1214,1223,"SKILLS"],[1225,1230,"SKILLS"],[1260,1269,"SKILLS"],[1271,1282,"SKILLS"],[1302,1306,"SKILLS"],[1308,1311,"SKILLS"],[1313,1316,"SKILLS"],[1379,1382,"SKILLS"],[1386,1396,"SKILLS"],[1400,1405,"SKILLS"],[1409,1414,"SKILLS"]]}]]}