{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Kamaljeet Kaur\nKurukshetra, Haryana\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Kamaljeet-Kaur/1c334b5223d96412\n\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\n\nWork Experience\n\nPython Developer\nInfosys - Pune, Maharashtra\nJune 2018 to December 2021\n\nWhile  working  into  Infosys,  I  got  exposed  to  multiple  technologies  related  to  web  development,\nNetworking and database.\nSkillset : Python, javascript, Mongodb, React, Django, nodejs\n\nEducation\n\nMaster's Degree in Computer Applications\nLovely professional University - Phagwara, Punjab\nJune 2021 to Present\n\nBachelor's Degree in Information Technology\nKurukshetra University - Kurukshetra, Haryana\nJune 2015 to June 2018\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• CSS\n\n• Git\n\n• JSON\n\n• JavaScript\n\n• MySQL\n\n• React\n\n• MongoDB\n\n• Node.js\n\n• Python\n\n• Machine learning\n\n• User Interface (UI)\n\n• php\n\n• APIs\n\n• GitHub\n\n• REST\n\n\f• Bootstrap\n\nLanguages\n\n• English - Fluent\n• German - Beginner\n• Hindi - Fluent\n• Punjabi - Fluent\n\nOnline Profile\n\nhttp://github.com/kkaur1998\n\nCertifications and Licenses\n\nFull Stack Web Development Intern\nFebruary 2021 to Present\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[28,35,"LOCATION"],[162,178,"ROLE"],[179,186,"ORGANISATION"],[189,193,"LOCATION"],[195,206,"LOCATION"],[207,233,"DURATION"],[379,385,"SKILLS"],[387,397,"SKILLS"],[399,406,"SKILLS"],[408,413,"SKILLS"],[415,421,"SKILLS"],[423,429,"SKILLS"],[442,482,"EDUCATION"],[483,513,"INSTITUTION"],[526,532,"LOCATION"],[533,553,"DURATION"],[555,598,"EDUCATION"],[599,621,"INSTITUTION"],[637,644,"LOCATION"],[645,667,"DURATION"],[691,694,"SKILLS"],[698,701,"SKILLS"],[705,709,"SKILLS"],[713,723,"SKILLS"],[727,732,"SKILLS"],[736,741,"SKILLS"],[745,752,"SKILLS"],[756,763,"SKILLS"],[767,773,"SKILLS"],[777,793,"SKILLS"],[797,811,"SKILLS"],[813,815,"SKILLS"],[820,823,"SKILLS"],[827,831,"SKILLS"],[835,841,"SKILLS"],[845,849,"SKILLS"],[1026,1059,"CERTIFICATE"],[1060,1084,"DURATION"]]}]]}