{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Kantamaneni Venkata Trinadh\nHyderabad, Telangana\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Kantamaneni-Venkata-Trinadh/e8d9d9c14a9256ac\n\n• Having 3.5 Years of Experience in the IT industry and Business Intelligence. \n• Expertise in generating reports using Tableau. \n• Experience in creating hierarchies, charts, table calculations, trend lines and calculated measures in\ntableau. \n• Experience in Tableau report developing, testing and deploying reporting solutions on Tableau\nServer. \n• Created Customized and interactive dashboards using multiple data sources. \n• Having knowledge on Excel and SQL Server. \n• Outstanding analytical and problem-solving skills, capable of learning new technologies. \n• Restricted data for users using Row level security and User filters. \n• Developed Tableau workbooks from multiple data sources using Data Blending. \n• Installation and configuration of tableau products, Tableau desktop and tableau server in different\nenvironment Dev, Stage and Prod. \n• Experience using Tableau tool to handle the various data feeds from different data sources using\nTableau Desktop tool. \n• Experience in Create/Manage Groups, Users, workbooks and projects, Data base Views, Data\nSources and Data Connections\n\nI have 3.5 years of experience as tableau developer. I used to generate reports and build dashboards\nusing multiple data sources.\n\nWilling to relocate to: Bengaluru, Karnataka - -\n\nWork Experience\n\nTableau Developer\nLejara Global IT Solutions Pvt. Ltd - Hyderabad, Telangana\nSeptember 2018 to Present\n\nEducation\n\nBachelor's in mechanical\nK L University - Hyderabad, Telangana\nPresent\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• BI Tools: Tableau Desktop, Tableau Server, Tableau Online\n\n• Databases: SQL server (3 years)\n\n• Operating Systems: Win7, win10\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,27,"PERSON"],[28,37,"LOCATION"],[39,48,"LOCATION"],[149,172,"DURATION"],[260,268,"SKILLS"],[590,595,"SKILLS"],[600,611,"SKILLS"],[1242,1251,"DURATION"],[1269,1287,"ROLE"],[1390,1399,"LOCATION"],[1401,1410,"LOCATION"],[1433,1450,"ROLE"],[1451,1486,"ORGANISATION"],[1489,1498,"LOCATION"],[1500,1509,"LOCATION"],[1510,1535,"DURATION"],[1548,1572,"EDUCATION"],[1573,1587,"INSTITUTION"],[1590,1599,"LOCATION"],[1601,1610,"LOCATION"],[1652,1667,"SKILLS"],[1669,1683,"SKILLS"],[1685,1699,"SKILLS"],[1714,1724,"SKILLS"],[1726,1733,"DURATION"],[1757,1761,"SKILLS"],[1763,1768,"SKILLS"]]}]]}