{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Keerthana PG\nErnakulam, Kerala\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Keerthana-PG/612d96064a8fd20f\n\nWilling to relocate to: UAE - UAE -\n\nWork Experience\n\nDeveloper\nHappy Marketer Digital Private Limited\nMarch 2021 to Present\n\n•  Identied  and  eliminated  performance  bottlenecks  by  determining  root  causes  and  remediating\nproblematic code.\n• Performed testing tasks and developed complex features routinely.\n• Implemented and updating Google tagging modules as per the request from client.\n• Working with Google analytics\n• Android application testing\n• Software & Website Development\n• Collaborated with other developers to identify and alleviate software errors and inefciencies.\n•  Introduced  agile  methodologies  and  development  best  practices  to  division  to  enhance  product\ndevelopment.\n•  Designed,  developed  and  implemented  software  applications  for  website  based  on  analyzed\nrequirements and understanding of industry technical standards.\n\nFull Stack Developer\nAMSTER GROUP\nDecember 2018 to February 2021\n\n• Developed programs from ground up using measured, market-focused approach to eliminate waste\nand streamline implementation cycle.\n•  Consulted  with  engineering  team  members  to  determine  system  loads  and  develop  improvement\nplans.\n• Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues.\n• Contributed ideas and suggestions in team meetings and delivered updates on deadlines, designs and\nenhancements.\n•  Revised,  modularized  and  updated  old  code  bases  to  modern  development  standards,  reducing\noperating costs and improving functionality.\n•  Minimized  resource  and  time  losses  by  addressing  employee  or  production  issue  directly  and\nimplementing timely solutions.\n• End to end software and website development\n\nEducation\n\nBachelor's in Engineering\nSree Narayana Gurukulam college of Engineering - Ernakulam, Kerala\nJuly 2014 to May 2018\n\n\fSkills / IT Skills\n\n• .NET\n\n• C\n\n• HTML5\n\n• Java\n\n• JavaScript\n\n• PHP\n\n• SQL\n\n• Css\n\n• Agile\n\n• Typescript\n\nOnline Profile\n\nhttps://vavega.in\n\nhttps://www.amsteroverseas.com\n\nhttps://www.crm-amsteroverseas.com\n\nhttps://www.dlschool.online\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[24,30,"LOCATION"],[137,140,"LOCATION"],[161,170,"ROLE"],[171,209,"ORGANISATION"],[210,231,"DURATION"],[983,1003,"ROLE"],[1004,1016,"ORGANISATION"],[1017,1047,"DURATION"],[1808,1833,"EDUCATION"],[1834,1880,"INSTITUTION"],[1894,1900,"LOCATION"],[1901,1922,"DURATION"],[1947,1951,"SKILLS"],[1955,1956,"SKILLS"],[1960,1965,"SKILLS"],[1969,1973,"SKILLS"],[1977,1987,"SKILLS"],[1991,1994,"SKILLS"],[1998,2001,"SKILLS"],[2005,2008,"SKILLS"],[2012,2017,"SKILLS"],[2021,2031,"SKILLS"]]}]]}