{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Mohammed Razaa Dumaswala\nSurat, Gujarat\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Mohammed-Razaa-Dumaswala/e80a5ad139561740\n\nSEO Trainee searching for the chance to fill the position with a reputable organization to use my skills\nand training to make positive contributions to the company.\n\nPersonal Details\n\nHighest Career Level: Fresher\n\nWork Experience\n\nDigital Marketing\nXplore Institute - Surat, Gujarat\nAugust 2021 to December 2021\n\n• Fresher\n• 4 month fresher training in Digital Marketing from Xplore Institute\n\nEducation\n\nHigher Secondary(12th Pass)\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• SEO\n\n• SEM\n\n• Digital marketing\n\n• Google Analytics\n\nLanguages\n\n• Hindi , Gujarati and English - Intermediate\n\n• Fast Learner, Hardworking and Efficient. Good Management skills, • Keyword Research, •\n\nGoogle web master Tool, • On Page and Off page Optimization, • Google AdWords, • Seo Tools\n(Ahrefs ,Semrush, Keyword Planner, Moz), • Search Engine Marketing (SEM) and Social Media\nMarketing (SMM) (Less than 1 year)\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,24,"PERSON"],[25,30,"LOCATION"],[32,39,"LOCATION"],[128,139,"ROLE"],[360,377,"ROLE"],[378,394,"ORGANISATION"],[397,402,"LOCATION"],[404,411,"LOCATION"],[412,440,"DURATION"],[454,461,"DURATION"],[482,499,"ROLE"],[505,521,"ORGANISATION"],[534,550,"EDUCATION"],[551,560,"EDUCATION"],[585,588,"SKILLS"],[592,595,"SKILLS"],[599,616,"SKILLS"],[620,636,"SKILLS"],[744,761,"SKILLS"],[765,781,"SKILLS"],[786,808,"SKILLS"],[849,863,"SKILLS"],[878,884,"SKILLS"],[886,893,"SKILLS"],[895,910,"SKILLS"],[912,915,"SKILLS"],[920,943,"SKILLS"],[945,948,"SKILLS"],[954,976,"SKILLS"],[978,981,"SKILLS"],[984,1000,"DURATION"]]}]]}