{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Mondeep Boruah\nNodeJs Backend Developer\nBengaluru, Karnataka\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Mondeep-Boruah/a9a106fdc7603c5d\n\nI'm a Software Engineer having 4 years of expertise in web development in an Agile environment.\nExperienced \nin both F/E and B/E technologies. Having rich hands on exposure in backend REST API development\nusing \nNode.Js. Having good hands on exposure to single page application development using Angular 6+ &\nReactJs \nHaving exposure to both SQL(MySQL & MSSQL) and NoSQL(MongoDB & CassandraDB) databases.\nHaving good \nexperience in Integration development using MuleSoft. I'm passionate to learning new IT skills and\ncurrently \ngrowing as a professional.\n\nWork Experience\n\nSOFTWARE DEVELOPER\nICF Next - Bengaluru, Karnataka\nFebruary 2021 to Present\n\nIndia.\n\nProject Title E-KYC\nDescription It is a Fin-Tech web application that helps the client to verify its customer with the help of\nan ID like Aadhaar, PAN etc.\nResponsibilities • Individually handled the development of RESTFul APIs for backend\n• Integrated the APIs with third party services.\n• Provided support on UI development.\n\nAPPLICATION DEVELOPMENT ANALYST\nACCENTURE - Bengaluru, Karnataka\nOctober 2017 to February 2021\n\nIndia.\n\nProject Title Gitex\nDescription It is a data visualization web application. Main objective of this application is to track the\nmobility of people around different regions of UAE during covid-19. It has\ndifferent modules like tapestry, mobility, mode of transport, accident prediction\netc.\nResponsibilities • Developed the backend RESTful APIs with an individual effort.\n• Provided support in API integration with UI.\nProject Title MyNav-ID\n\n\fDescription MyNav-ID is an intelligent diagnostic web application which provides the user with discussions\nrelated to different cloud platforms like AWS, AZURE, GCP etc\nResponsibilities • Developed RESTful APIs for the backend\n• Development of UI components and integrating those with backend APIs.\n• Created functionalities using Node.Js for uploading files to Azure BLOB\nstorage.\nProject Title Rakuten\nDescription Omni channel web application which provides the users with facilities like raising a\nticket on network issues, buying a product, raise a query etc. It is a telecom based\nproduct.\nResponsibilities • Developed and enhanced the micro-services and RESTful APIs.\n• Developed UI components in Angular 6 and integrating those with backend\nNodeJs APIs.\n• Wrote Unit test cases using MOCHA and CHAI frameworks.\n\nProject Title H&PS\nDescription It is an Accenture internal a content management hybrid application which\nprovides various public service information to the employees\nResponsibilities • Developed RESTful APIs for hybrid mobile application and web admin\napplication using NodeJs and Express\n• Created DB tables for storing the data in MySQL.\n• Wrote Unit test cases using MOCHA and CHAI.\n• Participated in code deployment to AWS EC2 instance\n\nProject Title Humarashop\nDescription Hindustan Unilever E-commerce platform which allows the user to order and buy\nproduct from stores nearby to their location.\nResponsibilities • Developed and enhanced RESTful APIs to integrate Darwin to Hybris\nbackend, UI to Hybris backend using Mulesoft\n• Deployed APIs to Mulesoft cloudhub\n• Provided support in Grafana monitoring\n\nEducation\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• JavaScript\n\nMaster of Computer Applications in Computer Applications\nAssam Engineering College - Guwahati, Assam\n2014 to 2017\n\n• PRIMARY: NodeJs, Express, Javascript, ES6 \n\nSEONDARY: Angular 6+, ReactJs, Core Java, MySQL, NoSQL, MongoDB, Mulesoft, Agile, SAFe, Git \nTOOLS: JIRA, Git, VS Code, Eclipse, Postman, Workbench\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[15,39,"ROLE"],[40,49,"LOCATION"],[51,60,"LOCATION"],[145,162,"ROLE"],[170,177,"DURATION"],[194,209,"SKILLS"],[323,331,"SKILLS"],[351,359,"SKILLS"],[435,445,"SKILLS"],[448,455,"SKILLS"],[481,484,"SKILLS"],[485,490,"SKILLS"],[493,498,"SKILLS"],[504,509,"SKILLS"],[510,517,"SKILLS"],[520,531,"SKILLS"],[601,610,"SKILLS"],[712,730,"ROLE"],[731,739,"ORGANISATION"],[742,751,"LOCATION"],[753,762,"LOCATION"],[763,787,"DURATION"],[789,795,"LOCATION"],[811,816,"PROJECTS"],[1125,1156,"ROLE"],[1157,1166,"ORGANISATION"],[1169,1178,"LOCATION"],[1180,1189,"LOCATION"],[1190,1219,"DURATION"],[1221,1227,"LOCATION"],[1243,1248,"PROJECTS"],[1660,1668,"PROJECTS"],[1820,1823,"SKILLS"],[1825,1830,"SKILLS"],[1832,1835,"SKILLS"],[1869,1881,"SKILLS"],[1956,1969,"SKILLS"],[2002,2009,"SKILLS"],[2067,2074,"PROJECTS"],[2374,2383,"SKILLS"],[2419,2425,"SKILLS"],[2462,2467,"SKILLS"],[2472,2476,"SKILLS"],[2504,2508,"PROJECTS"],[2823,2829,"SKILLS"],[2860,2865,"SKILLS"],[2870,2875,"SKILLS"],[3334,3344,"SKILLS"],[3346,3402,"EDUCATION"],[3403,3428,"INSTITUTION"],[3431,3439,"LOCATION"],[3441,3446,"LOCATION"],[3447,3459,"DURATION"],[3472,3478,"SKILLS"],[3480,3487,"SKILLS"],[3489,3499,"SKILLS"],[3501,3504,"SKILLS"],[3517,3527,"SKILLS"],[3529,3536,"SKILLS"],[3538,3547,"SKILLS"],[3549,3554,"SKILLS"],[3556,3561,"SKILLS"],[3563,3570,"SKILLS"],[3572,3580,"SKILLS"],[3582,3587,"SKILLS"],[3589,3593,"SKILLS"],[3595,3598,"SKILLS"],[3607,3611,"SKILLS"],[3613,3616,"SKILLS"],[3618,3625,"SKILLS"],[3627,3634,"SKILLS"],[3636,3643,"SKILLS"],[3645,3654,"SKILLS"]]}]]}