{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Muskan Shaikh\nMarketing Executive\nPune, Maharashtra\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Muskan-Shaikh/e2ec4df02d715a9b\n\nWilling to relocate to: Doha Qatar\n\nWork Experience\n\nMarketing Executive\nZiMetrics - Pune, Maharashtra\nJanuary 2020 to Present\n\nZimetrics is an Enterprise IT support services organization offering a bouquet of IT services in Software\ndevelopment, IoT, ML, Big data analytics, cloud platforms Mobility solutions, and capability\nbuilding. Zimetrics supports clients in India, the USA, Canada, and Australia with their IT\ninfrastructure needs.\n\nRoles and Responsibilities\n(Marketing Executive)\n• Responsible for managing, creating, and designing the website of a company\n\n• Designing, planning, executing different marketing campaigns/strategies\n\n• Hunting suitable clients/customers and connecting/communicating with them\n\n• Pitching, lead generation through different platforms\n\n• Searching and Enrolling for the different US/India events\n\n• Creating personalized reach out templates\n\n• Performing and managing rainmaker activities\n\n• Exploring different tools which can effectively increase the reach and results\n\n• Experience in pitching AdTech and MedTech companies\n\n• Expert in handling company's LinkedIn, Facebook, Twitter, AmbitionBox, Glassdoor(IND/US),\n\n• Clutch, Crunchbase, Good firms, Trustpilot, Quora presence\n\n• Increase the company's social media connections and help in targeting essential talent\n\n• Assisted in the making of visiting cards\n\n\f• Attending different LinkedIn self-development marketing trainings\n\nRoles and Responsibilities\n\n(Account Manager)\n\n• Successfully connecting with new clients starting right from mining and hunting\n\n• Creating NDA, SOWs, PO\n\n• Using different strategies for lead generation\n\n• Solutioning and Managing projects within client relationships, working to carry out client goals while\nmeeting company goals\n\n• Invoicing, Keeping records of client transactions\n\n• Focusing on the activities which help in consumer satisfaction and customer relation\n\n• Operating as the point of contact for assigned customers\n\n• Developing and maintaining long-term relationships with accounts\n\n• Making sure clients receive requested products and services in a timely fashion\n\n• Communicating client needs and demands to the employer company\n\n• Forecasting and tracking client account metrics\n\n• Identifying opportunities to grow business with existing clients\n\n• Coordinating with staff members working on the same account to ensure consistent service\n\nEducation\n\nMaster's in Marketing\nSavitribai Phule Pune University - Pune, Maharashtra\nJune 2019 to April 2021\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• Marketing\n\n• Business development\n\n• Communication skills\n\n• Computer skills\n\n• Customer service\n\n\f• Negotiation\n\n• Digital Marketing\n\n• Sales\n\n• Microsoft Excel\n\n• English\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[14,33,"ROLE"],[34,38,"LOCATION"],[40,51,"LOCATION"],[153,157,"LOCATION"],[158,163,"LOCATION"],[182,201,"ROLE"],[202,211,"ORGANISATION"],[214,218,"LOCATION"],[220,231,"LOCATION"],[232,255,"DURATION"],[257,266,"ORGANISATION"],[496,501,"LOCATION"],[507,510,"LOCATION"],[512,518,"LOCATION"],[524,533,"LOCATION"],[599,618,"ROLE"],[1586,1601,"ROLE"],[2531,2552,"EDUCATION"],[2553,2585,"INSTITUTION"],[2588,2592,"LOCATION"],[2594,2605,"LOCATION"],[2606,2629,"DURATION"],[2653,2662,"SKILLS"],[2666,2686,"SKILLS"],[2690,2710,"SKILLS"],[2714,2729,"SKILLS"],[2733,2749,"SKILLS"],[2754,2765,"SKILLS"],[2769,2786,"SKILLS"],[2790,2795,"SKILLS"],[2799,2814,"SKILLS"]]}]]}