{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Anil Paudel                        \r\n\r\nElectrical Engineer with 4years Experience  \r\n\r\nD.O.B.: 23-Nov-1989 \r\nNationality: Nepal \r\nLocation: Dang, Nepal \r\nMobile: +977 9851172992 \r\nEmail: anilpo@gmail.com \r\nNepal Passport no: 07057162 \r\n\r\nPROFILE \r\n\r\nOBJECTIVE \r\n\r\nEDUCATION \r\n\r\nLANGUAGES \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\nI am an accomplished Electrical engineer with 4 years of experience as a Project Engineer \r\n(Electrical operation and maintenance Project). I have proven success in organizing; planning \r\nand executing electrical maintenance task in given time frame. I am searching for an \r\nopportunity where my experience and skills would be put in use. \r\n\r\nApplying 4 years of Electrical operation and maintenance experience in a reputed organization \r\nwhere a culture of freedom and working for initiatives is ensured, facilitating my contribution \r\nand skills through thoughts and action to the company's target and fulfillment of the \r\norganization's goal, as well as self development by playing a significant role in building the \r\norganization's vision. \r\n\r\nKhwopa College of Engineering (Tribhuvan University), Bhaktapur, Nepal \r\nBachelor in Electrical Engineering May 2013 \r\n\r\n  \r\nEnglish – Excellent reading, writing and speaking (IELTS Overall score: 7) \r\nHindi – Excellent reading, writing and speaking \r\n \r\n\r\nCOMPUTER SKILLS \r\n\r\n  Microsoft office package \r\n\r\n  Auto Cad Draft (2D) \r\n\r\nPROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE \r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n \r\n \r\n\r\nAnil Paudel \r\n\r\nPage 1 of 2 \r\n\r\nElectrical Maintenance Engineer (Electrical O&M Project) \r\nCosmic Electrical Engineering Associates Pvt. Ltd (2014- Present) \r\nCosmic Electrical Engineering Associates Pvt. Ltd. (CEEA), Kathmandu (Nepal), a renowned \r\nElectrical Contractor.  \r\n\r\nI am working as Project Engineer for Electrical operation and maintenance Project representing \r\nCEEA at B.P. Koirala institute of health Science, Ghopa , Dharan. \r\n\r\n\fResponsibilities and Role details: \r\n\r\n  Conduct Operation and maintenance of all generators, Auto Mains Failure (AMF) panels, \r\nElectrical Panels, Sub Panels, Underground (XLPE, PILC) and overhead cables and so on. \r\n\r\n  Maintaining periodical maintenance schedules of Electrical equipment’s like a circuit \r\n\r\nbreaker, transformer, generators, motors etc. and executing them. \r\n\r\n  Conduct and maintain safe work place to minimize accidents and avoid surprises. \r\n\r\n  Preparation of the monthly work progress report, salary sheet for the entire team and \r\n\r\nmaintain logbook of the work process. \r\n\r\nElectrical Engineer, Rolpa Cement Pvt. Ltd (2013-2014) \r\nRolpa Cement Pvt. Ltd is the 500 TPD Cement plant located in Rolpa, Nepal \r\n\r\nResponsibilities and Role details: \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\nInstallation & maintenance of Electrical equipment's (Circuit Breakers, OLR, Contractors, 3 \r\nphase Induction motors). \r\n\r\n  Design of Electrical panel board for Distribution system medium voltage (400V) and low \r\n\r\nvoltage (220V), and also lightening design. \r\n\r\n  Motor control circuit design for 3 phase Induction motor. \r\n\r\n  Operation and maintenance of DIESEL GENERATOR of 1700*2 KVA \r\n\r\n  Record keeping and managing MIS report. \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n  \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\nREFERENCE \r\n \r\nMr. Netra B. Khada  \r\n(Chief Engineer of Electrical Engineering Department)  \r\nBP. KOIRALA INSTITUTE OF HEALTH SCIENCE Dharan, Nepal  \r\nnetra_70@yahoo.com \r\n+9779842038951 \r\n \r\nMr. Bindu Sagar Shakya  \r\nGeneral Manager  \r\nRolpa Cement Pvt Ltd Rolpa, Nepal  \r\nbshakya@rolpacement.com  \r\n+9779803481329  \r\n\r\nOTHER INTERESTS \r\n\r\n \r\nWatching Movies, Playing Football, Travelling, Trekking.  \r\n \r\n \r\n \r\n\r\nAnil Paudel \r\n\r\nPage 2 of 2 \r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[39,58,"ROLE"],[64,70,"DURATION"],[162,177,"CONTACT"],[187,203,"EMAIL"],[343,350,"DURATION"],[370,386,"ROLE"],[649,656,"DURATION"],[660,680,"ROLE"],[1046,1075,"INSTITUTION"],[1077,1097,"INSTITUTION"],[1100,1109,"LOCATION"],[1111,1116,"LOCATION"],[1119,1153,"EDUCATION"],[1494,1516,"ROLE"],[1520,1569,"ORGANISATION"],[1571,1584,"DURATION"],[1588,1638,"ORGANISATION"],[1723,1739,"ROLE"],[1812,1852,"ORGANISATION"],[2502,2523,"ORGANISATION"],[2525,2534,"DURATION"],[2538,2559,"ORGANISATION"],[3146,3164,"PERSON"],[3225,3271,"ORGANISATION"],[3282,3300,"EMAIL"],[3303,3317,"CONTACT"],[3323,3345,"PERSON"],[3349,3394,"ORGANISATION"],[3405,3428,"EMAIL"],[3432,3446,"CONTACT"]]}]]}