{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[[" \r\n\r\nCurriculum Vitae \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\nNayaz ur Rahman C.I \r\nIndia, Chikmagalur \r\nKarnataka, 577101\r\nMob :  +91-9591673017 / +91-7975820467\r\nE-mail: nayazrahmannrf@gmail.com \r\nSkype ID : nayazrahmannrf@gmail.com\r\n\r\nPROFILE SNAPSHOT  \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n• Detailed   oriented  efficient  and   organized  professional  and  extensive   experience   in\r\n\r\n \r\n• Possess strong analytical and problem solving skills, with the ability to make well\r\n\r\nAccounts system.\r\n\r\nthought out decisions.\r\n\r\n• Excellent written and verbal communication skills.\r\n\r\n• Highly trustworthy, discreet and ethical.\r\n\r\n• Resourceful in the completion of projects, effective at multi-tasking.\r\n\r\nCARRER OBJECTIVE \r\n\r\nExpert in all aspects of accounting including Accounts  receivables,  Accounts payables,\r\npayroll in Accounting, bank reconciliation. etc. Bring with me a meticulous approach to\r\naccounting problem solving and attention to finer details of accounts. \r\n\r\nEDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND \r\n\r\n 10th from  Mountain view High School, Chikmagalur, STATE Board in 2008.\r\n\r\n\f \r\n\r\nCurriculum Vitae \r\n\r\n 12th (PUC) from Mountain view Pre university College, Chikmagalur, Karnataka State\r\n\r\nBoard in 2010.\r\n\r\n BBM (Marketing) (Bachelor of Business Management) from Mountain View Institute\r\nof Management Studies From Kuvempu university Chikmagalur Karnataka, 2013.\r\n\r\n MBA (Finance) (Master of Business Administration)  from Don Bosco Institution of\r\nTechnology   From   Visvesvaraya   Technological   University,   Bangalore,   Karnataka,\r\n2015.\r\n\r\nOther Course:  \r\n\r\n Successfully completed  Excel Course in 2014.\r\n Successfully completed Tally ERP 9 - V.A.T, G.S.T in 2018.\r\n\r\nACADEMIC PROJECTS\r\n\r\nMBA PROJECT REPORT\r\n\r\nProject Title \r\nProject Area\r\nCompany    \r\nDuration      \r\nDescription  \r\n\r\n:   A study on “Receivables management”.\r\n:   Finance.\r\n:   Amalgamated Bean Coffee Trading Company Limited.\r\n:   2 Months.\r\n:\r\n\r\n Analyzed the organization financial stability, Liquidity and Prospective growth.\r\n To find the growth of Receivables, Current assets and total assets in percentage.\r\n To identify receivables turnover ratio and period.\r\n To forecast the sales, debtors, Current assets and total assets value.\r\n\r\nACADEMIC ACCOLADES\r\n\r\n Had been a part of national Entrepreneurial network.\r\n Participated in inter collegiate fest. \r\n Active participation in coordinating fest and placement in College.\r\n\r\nFUNCTIONAL EXPERTISE \r\n\r\n \r\nWells Fargo India Solutions private limited, \r\n\r\n \r\n  Bangalore, Karnataka, India. \r\n \r\n\r\n Accountant  ( April 2016 -  February 2018).\r\n\r\n• Maintaining basic accounts, book keeping.\r\n\r\n\f \r\n\r\n•\r\n\r\n•\r\n\r\n•\r\n\r\n•\r\n\r\n•\r\n\r\nCurriculum Vitae \r\n\r\n• Accounts Practice in software, M S Excel.\r\n•\r\n• Oversaw   bank   Reconciliation   and   Cash   Reconciliation   statement,   cash   collections   &\r\n\r\nPerform Daily Accounting Transactions Such as creating & posting vouchers. \r\n\r\ndeposits.\r\n\r\n• Maintain Accounts receivable and Accounts payables ledgers, checking, verifying and\r\n\r\nposting Invoices.\r\nPrepare journal entries & Reconciles general ledgers and subsidiary accounts. \r\nPrepare   statements   and   updating   Daily   Accounting   Report     and   updating   of   personal\r\nbooks etc. \r\n\r\n• Checking balance sheet and P&L account.\r\n•\r\n\r\nPays employees by receiving and verifying expense reports and requests for advances;\r\npreparing checks. \r\nPrepare monthly / Weekly and other periodical financial reports.\r\n\r\n• Maintaining of Files such as Tax reports, payroll, insurance policies, expenses reports.\r\n• Checking and verifying appropriate Tax of suppliers and customers (VAT, GST, TDS,\r\n\r\nand ESIC).\r\nFollow up of Debtors and creditors.\r\nProtect organizations + value by keeping information confidential.\r\n\r\n• Managing and recording of employees expenses report and credit card statements. \r\n• Making payment to vendors follow up, collection and allocation of payments.\r\n• Monitored   and   reviewed   accounting   and   system   generated   reports   for   accuracy   and\r\n\r\ncompleteness. \r\n\r\n• Manage the filing, storage and security of documents , Respond to inquiries , Manage the\r\n\r\nrepair and maintenance of computer and office equipment. \r\n\r\nC.N Coffee Trading Co,  Chikmagalur, Karnataka, India. \r\n\r\n Accountant ( March 2018- May 2018)\r\n\r\n• Maintaining basic accounts, book keeping.\r\n• Accounts Practice in Tally ERP 9 software, M S Excel.\r\n•\r\n• Maintain Accounts receivable and Accounts payables ledgers, checking, verifying and\r\n\r\nPerform Daily Accounting Transactions Such as creating & posting vouchers. \r\n\r\n•\r\n\r\nposting Invoices.\r\nPrepare journal entries & Reconciles general ledgers and subsidiary accounts.  \r\nFollow up, collection and allocation of payments.\r\n\r\n•\r\n• Monitored   and   reviewed   accounting   and   system   generated   reports   for   accuracy   and\r\n\r\ncompleteness. \r\n\r\n\f \r\n\r\nCurriculum Vitae \r\n\r\nCOMPUTER PROFICIENCY & TECHNICAL TRAINING \r\n\r\n      Operating Systems \r\n\r\n:       Windows XP, Windows 7, Windows 8.\r\n\r\n      Office packages                   :       Microsoft Office, M S Excel. Tally ERP 9.\r\n\r\nPERSONAL INFORMATION \r\n\r\nFather’s Name\r\nDate of Birth   \r\n     \r\nNationality \r\nGender \r\n         \r\nMarital Status      \r\nLanguages Known \r\nPassport Number   \r\nPlace of Issue       \r\nDate of Expiry      \r\n \r\nPERSONAL ATTRIBUTES \r\n\r\n           :  Imtiyaz Ahmed C.R.\r\n\r\n:  10st November, 1992. \r\n:  Indian. \r\n:  Male. \r\n:  Single.\r\n:  English, Hindi, Kannada. \r\n:  N 4399155.     \r\n:  Bangalore.\r\n:  12th November 202.\r\n\r\n• Highly energetic, motivated individual with the ability to adapt any work place.\r\n• An exemplary character and conduct with a high level of dependability and trust. \r\n\r\n STRENGTH\r\n \r\n• A   team   builder,   Inter   communication   skill,   Fast   learner   and   flexible   with   times   and\r\n\r\nenvironment. \r\n\r\n• Reference and testimonials  should be provided as on the demand. \r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[31,46,"PERSON"],[53,58,"LOCATION"],[60,71,"LOCATION"],[74,83,"LOCATION"],[100,114,"CONTACT"],[117,131,"CONTACT"],[141,165,"EMAIL"],[179,203,"EMAIL"],[961,965,"EDUCATION"],[972,997,"INSTITUTION"],[999,1010,"LOCATION"],[1065,1069,"EDUCATION"],[1081,1117,"INSTITUTION"],[1119,1130,"LOCATION"],[1132,1141,"LOCATION"],[1171,1186,"EDUCATION"],[1188,1219,"EDUCATION"],[1226,1272,"INSTITUTION"],[1278,1296,"INSTITUTION"],[1297,1308,"LOCATION"],[1309,1318,"LOCATION"],[1331,1344,"EDUCATION"],[1346,1379,"EDUCATION"],[1387,1423,"INSTITUTION"],[1433,1474,"INSTITUTION"],[1478,1487,"LOCATION"],[1491,1500,"LOCATION"],[1557,1569,"CERTIFICATE"],[1605,1624,"CERTIFICATE"],[1778,1803,"PROJECTS"],[1877,1886,"DURATION"],[2414,2457,"ORGANISATION"],[2468,2477,"LOCATION"],[2479,2488,"LOCATION"],[2490,2496,"LOCATION"],[2506,2516,"ROLE"],[2520,2547,"DURATION"],[2654,2683,"SKILLS"],[2685,2695,"SKILLS"],[2899,2927,"SKILLS"],[3206,3228,"SKILLS"],[3428,3448,"SKILLS"],[3520,3558,"SKILLS"],[4165,4186,"INSTITUTION"],[4189,4200,"LOCATION"],[4202,4211,"LOCATION"],[4213,4219,"LOCATION"],[4226,4236,"ROLE"],[4239,4259,"DURATION"],[4266,4292,"SKILLS"],[4311,4352,"SKILLS"],[4354,4364,"SKILLS"],[4900,4917,"SKILLS"],[4930,4940,"SKILLS"],[4942,4951,"SKILLS"],[4953,4963,"SKILLS"],[5015,5031,"SKILLS"],[5035,5043,"SKILLS"],[5044,5056,"SKILLS"],[5305,5318,"PERSON"],[5442,5452,"LOCATION"]]}]]}