{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Abdul Khan\nBalaghat, M.P, 481102, IN\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Abdul-Khan/c9f8a567cf71f481\n\n\"To establish a symbiotic relationship with the organization I work with for organization as \nwell as growth and success\"\n\nWork Experience\n\nPhp Developer\nSatpuda polytechnic college - Balaghat, Madhya Pradesh\nAugust 2017 to Present\n\nERP(Enterprise Recourse Planning System) for school and college\n2017 to 2021\n\nWebsite Development 2017-2021.\n\nEducation\n\nB.Sc. in Information Technology\nHigher Secondary (PCM) - Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh\nJanuary 2017 to Present\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• AJAX\n\n• HTML5\n\n• MySQL\n\n• PHP\n\n• Wordpress\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,10,"PERSON"],[11,36,"LOCATION"],[251,264,"ROLE"],[265,292,"ORGANISATION"],[295,319,"LOCATION"],[320,342,"DURATION"],[344,384,"ROLE"],[389,407,"ORGANISATION"],[408,420,"DURATION"],[422,441,"ROLE"],[442,452,"DURATION"],[465,496,"EDUCATION"],[497,519,"EDUCATION"],[522,544,"LOCATION"],[545,568,"DURATION"],[592,596,"SKILLS"],[600,605,"SKILLS"],[609,614,"SKILLS"],[618,621,"SKILLS"],[625,634,"SKILLS"]]}]]}