{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["ATUL KUMAR PRAJAPATI\r\n\r\nMobile : +918874398659\r\nE-mail :  ak70546@gmail.com                                                                                                                                        \r\n\r\nTo make a sound position in corporate world and work enthusiastically in team to achieve goal of the organization/MNC with devotion\r\nand hard work.\r\n\r\nObjective: \r\n\r\nProfessional  Qualification: \r\n\r\nCourse\r\n\r\nSpecialization\r\n\r\nInstitute\r\n\r\nDuration\r\n\r\nAggregate % \r\n\r\nB.Tech.\r\n\r\nMechanical Engineering\r\n\r\nIndus Institute of Technology and Management,\r\nKanpur (Uttar Pradesh)\r\n\r\n(2011-15)\r\n\r\n71.54\r\n\r\nEducational Qualification: \r\n\r\nStandard\r\n\r\nSchool/Board\r\n\r\nS. I. College, Deoria (U.P. Board)\r\n\r\nM. A. Inter College, Deoria (U.P. Board)\r\n\r\n10th\r\n\r\n12th\r\n\r\n•\r\n\r\nWork Experience: \r\n\r\nCompany Name:             Omax Autos Limited.(Railway division)\r\nDepartment:                    Quality.\r\nDesignation:                    Quality Engineer.\r\nDuration:                         01/07/2015 to Present. \r\n\r\nPercentage\r\n\r\n57.50\r\n\r\n67.40\r\n\r\nYear\r\n\r\n2009\r\n\r\n2011\r\n\r\nM/s Omax Autos Ltd. (Railway division) is an approved supplier for Indian railways which supplies Heavy fabricated parts like \r\nBio Digester Retention Tanks, Fuel tanks, SS End Wall, Ms End Wall, Long Hood, Front Part, Under Frame Front Part, Water \r\ntank 450Lts and 350Lts,Dual cab& many more.\r\n\r\nAll site and documentation work.\r\nExcellent knowledge and experience leading a team of QC Inspectors.\r\nResponsible for new purchasing, fixtures, instrument and also co-ordinate with suppliers.\r\nRaw Material Inspection, In process inspection & PDI inspection.\r\n\r\nResponsibilities:\r\n\r\n•\r\n•\r\n•\r\n•\r\n• Welding Inspection (TIG & MIG specially).\r\n•\r\n•\r\n•\r\n•\r\n•\r\n\r\nHandling various Customer Audits, Visits & Process Audits.\r\nImplementation Kaizen activities and 5-S maintain.\r\nCreation of procedures, forms & checklists.\r\nExcellent interpersonal and communication skills.\r\nClose Co-Ordination with Engineering Office, client & sub-contractors to resolve outstanding Engineering and material \r\nrelated open issues, which are critical to project milestones.\r\nImplement Electronic Document Management System using MS-Excel/MS Word.\r\n\r\nTechnical Competencies:\r\n\r\n\f•\r\n\r\nSuccessfully completed ASNT LEVEL-II course:-\r\n\r\n▪ Ultrasonic Testing (UT)\r\n▪ Magnetic particle Testing (MPT)\r\n▪ Liquid Penetration Testing (PT)\r\n▪ Radiographic Testing (RT)\r\n▪ Visual Testing (VT)\r\n\r\nAttended a training course on Auto CAD Mechanical.\r\nTwo weeks training course on Programming & Operation of CNC Turning.\r\n\r\nWorkshop/ Training Attended:\r\n\r\nOne month training program on Reduction Plant (Pot roomMechanical Maintenance) from Hindalco Industries Limited, \r\nSonbhadra (UP).\r\nExperience of one month Industrial training in Auto Parts, from J.S. Auto Pvt. Ltd. Kanpur (UP).\r\nAttended a two weeks training course on Quality control & Engineering Inspection.\r\nParticipated in zonal round of RoboTryst- 2013 organized by Rob sapience Technologies Pvt. Ltd. Held at IITM Bilhaur, \r\nKanpur.\r\n\r\nPresented final year project as “Working model of line follower wheel chair”. In this project wheel chair move on black color\r\npath. On this wheel chair handicap person comfortably move from one place to another place.\r\n\r\n• Winner of (2nd Prize) Poster Drawing competition held on 22nd of April, 2014 at IITM, Bilhaur, Kanpur.\r\n• Winner of Football in Sport@INDUS’14 held at IITM, Bilhaur, Kanpur.\r\n•\r\n\r\nPaper presentation in YOJANA-2015 held at IITM.\r\n\r\n•\r\n•\r\n\r\n•\r\n\r\n•\r\n•\r\n•\r\n\r\n•\r\n\r\n•\r\n•\r\n•\r\n\r\n•\r\n•\r\n•\r\n\r\nB.tech Project Detail: \r\n\r\nExtra-Curricular Activities:\r\n\r\nSketching\r\nListening to music\r\nRiding bikes\r\n\r\nHobbies:\r\n\r\nStrength:\r\n\r\nAdaptability to all environment\r\nHardworking\r\nPersistence\r\n\r\nPersonal Information: \r\nFather’s Name: \r\nD.O.B: \r\nPassport No.:\r\nMarital Status: \r\nNationality: \r\nLanguages known: \r\n\r\nMr. Suresh Prajapati\r\n21 June 1994\r\nN0921350\r\nSingle\r\nIndian\r\nHindi, English\r\n\r\nAddress:\r\n\r\nVillage- Bhalua, Post- Parasiya mishr, District- Deoria, (U.P.)\r\n\r\nDeclaration:\r\nI certify that the information furnished above is correct and complete to the best of my knowledge and belief.\r\n\r\nDate:\r\n\r\nPlace:    \r\n\r\n                                                                                      (Atul Kumar Prajapati)\r\n\r\n\f\f",{"entities":[[0,20,"PERSON"],[33,46,"CONTACT"],[58,75,"EMAIL"],[483,516,"EDUCATION"],[520,564,"INSTITUTION"],[567,573,"LOCATION"],[575,588,"LOCATION"],[594,601,"DURATION"],[646,670,"EDUCATION"],[674,687,"INSTITUTION"],[689,695,"LOCATION"],[712,717,"EDUCATION"],[718,731,"INSTITUTION"],[733,741,"LOCATION"],[756,768,"EDUCATION"],[824,861,"ORGANISATION"],[936,953,"ROLE"],[989,1011,"DURATION"],[2173,2190,"SKILLS"],[2250,2270,"CERTIFICATE"],[2457,2477,"CERTIFICATE"],[2508,2547,"CERTIFICATE"],[2613,2661,"CERTIFICATE"],[2667,2694,"ORGANISATION"],[2698,2707,"LOCATION"],[2762,2772,"CERTIFICATE"],[2779,2798,"ORGANISATION"],[2799,2805,"LOCATION"],[2853,2894,"CERTIFICATE"],[2956,2991,"ORGANISATION"],[3000,3012,"INSTITUTION"],[3016,3023,"LOCATION"],[3059,3104,"PROJECTS"],[3431,3464,"PROJECTS"]]}]]}