{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["                                                 \r\n\r\nCurriculum Vitae\r\n\r\nName     : SHARIQ AYAZ\r\nEmail      : shariq11cv@gmail.com\r\nContact  : 7204331440\r\n           \r\n-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\r\n\r\nOBJECTIVE:\r\n\r\nTo excel career in an organization which provides a challenging work environment in a global\r\nscenario and allows as an individual to grow professionally and to serve the organization to the\r\nbest   of   my   abilities   and   become   professionally   trained   to   handle   critical   situations   and\r\nresponsibilities.\r\n\r\nACADEMIC CREDENTIALS:\r\n\r\nBACHELOR OF ENGINEERING in CIVIL ENGINEERING from Shri Dharmasthala \r\nManjunatheshwara College of Engineering and Technology, Dharwad.\r\n\r\nAcademic Level\r\n\r\nUniversity\r\n\r\nPercentage\r\n\r\nYear\r\n\r\n  B.E. Degree,\r\n  CIVIL Engg.\r\n\r\n VTU,BELGAU\r\nM\r\n\r\n71\r\n\r\n2015 \r\n\r\n(12th)  C.I.S.C.E\r\n\r\nI.C.S.E\r\n\r\n60.75\r\n\r\n2010\r\n\r\n (10th)  C.I.S.C.E\r\n\r\nI.C.S.E\r\n\r\n72.75\r\n\r\n2008\r\n\r\nName of\r\nInstitute\r\nShri Dharmasthala\r\nManjunatheshwara\r\nCollege Of\r\nEngineering &\r\nTechnology(Dharwad)\r\n\r\nSt. Xavier’s School ,\r\nBokaro\r\n\r\nSt. Xavier’s School ,\r\nBokaro\r\n\r\nSOFTWARE SKILLS:\r\n\r\nLanguages:\r\n\r\n\r\n Software: \r\n Operating System:   Windows 98/XP/Vista/Windows7/Window8.1\r\n\r\n\r\n  Introductory knowledge of C.\r\n  MS-OFFICE (Word, Power Point, Excel).\r\n\r\nTechnical:                AutoCAD 2012, REVIT ARCHITECTURE 2012, SOLID EDGE\r\n\r\nINDUSTRIAL VISITS AND TRAINING:\r\n\r\n1.  Vocational   Training   at  Bokaro   Steel   Plant,   SAIL,BOKARO  (15   Days)  from  5th  August\r\n2013 to 17th August 2013.\r\n\r\n2.   Industrial Training at  PWD & IWT Dept.,Dharwad  (1 month) from  6th  June to 7th  July,\r\n2014.\r\n\r\nPROJECTS UNDERTAKEN:\r\n\r\nWorked on Mini Project title   “SHED TYPE STRUCTURES BAMBOO VS. STEEL” \r\nAnd Major Project title   “ALTERNATIVES TO RIVER SAND”\r\n\r\n\fCO-CURRICULAR:\r\n\r\n12th & May 13th ,2013.\r\n\r\n Two days workshop on \"BUILDING PLANNING AND DRAWING\" conducted on  May\r\n\r\n One   day   training   programme   on  “CONSTRUCTION   SAFETY”  conducted   on  01st\r\nin   association   with  “CONSTRUCTION   INDUSTRY   DEVELOPMENT\r\n\r\nMay,2014, \r\nACADEMY”,BANGALORE.\r\n\r\n One   day   workshop/field   visit   on  “PLUMBING   OF   RESIDENTIAL   BUILDINGS”\r\nconducted on 23rd February, 2014, In association with “CONSTRUCTION INDUSTRY\r\nDEVELOPMENT ACADEMY”,BANGALORE.\r\n\r\n One day training programme on “ELECTRICAL WIRING & ACCESSORIES” conducted\r\non  08th  March   ,   2014,   in   association   with  “ANCHOR   ELECTRICALS   PVT   LTD.,\r\n(MEMBER OF PANASONIC ECO SOLUTIONS,JAPAN)”.\r\n\r\nPAPER PRESENTATION:\r\n  \r\nA SEMINAR on the topic “AIRPORT MARKINGS”.\r\n\r\nSTRENGTHS:\r\n \r\nGood in analysing things, good in decision making & managing the things.\r\nAbility to handle conflict situations.\r\n\r\nHOBBIES:\r\n\r\n Drawing and sketching Portraits.\r\n Reading Novels.\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nListening Music and Singing.\r\nSwimming.\r\nPlaying PC games.\r\n\r\nEXPERTISE:\r\n\r\nTeam management skill, Convincing skill, Analytical skill. \r\n\r\nPERSONAL DETAILS:\r\n\r\nNAME\r\nFATHER’S NAME     \r\n          MOTHER’S NAME     \r\n\r\n  \r\n\r\nGENDER\r\n\r\n          DATE OF BIRTH      \r\nNATIONALITY\r\nMARITAL STATUS\r\nLANGUAGE KNOWN\r\n\r\n          E-MAIL ADDRESS\r\n          CONTACT NO.\r\n                                                              \r\n\r\n                                               \r\n\r\nSHARIQ AYAZ\r\n\r\n:\r\n:         Anwar Hussain.\r\n:         Julekha Anwar.\r\n:\r\n:\r\n: \r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\n\r\nMale.\r\n26/09/1992\r\nIndian.\r\nUnmarried.\r\nEnglish, Hindi, Urdu and Arabic (read only).\r\nshariq11cv@gmail.com\r\n7204331440\r\n\r\n2\r\n\r\n\f           :   \r\nPermanent Address\r\n                                                         \r\n                                                        \r\n                                                         \r\n                                                     \r\n                                    \r\n\r\nQR.NO. – 821\r\nSECTOR- 1/C\r\nBOKARO STEEL CITY,\r\nJHARKHAND, PIN-827001\r\nMOBILE: +91 8986871265\r\n\r\nI here by declare that the information given above is true to the best of my knowledge\r\nand belief.\r\n\r\nDATE : 21.06.2015\r\n     \r\n\r\nPLACE: VOI                                                                                                 SHARIQ AYAZ\r\n\r\n3\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[84,95,"PERSON"],[110,130,"EMAIL"],[143,153,"CONTACT"],[671,715,"EDUCATION"],[721,795,"INSTITUTION"],[797,805,"LOCATION"],[865,892,"EDUCATION"],[897,900,"INSTITUTION"],[901,910,"LOCATION"],[937,957,"EDUCATION"],[1020,1024,"EDUCATION"],[1123,1130,"LOCATION"],[1135,1154,"INSTITUTION"],[1158,1164,"LOCATION"],[1168,1197,"INSTITUTION"],[1254,1312,"SKILLS"],[1321,1349,"SKILLS"],[1353,1389,"SKILLS"],[1394,1432,"SKILLS"],[1434,1457,"SKILLS"],[1459,1503,"SKILLS"],[1512,1533,"CERTIFICATE"],[1540,1562,"ORGANISATION"],[1566,1570,"LOCATION"],[1571,1577,"LOCATION"],[1579,1636,"DURATION"],[1645,1664,"CERTIFICATE"],[1669,1684,"ORGANISATION"],[1685,1692,"LOCATION"],[1694,1740,"DURATION"],[1799,1838,"PROJECTS"],[1867,1895,"PROJECTS"],[1968,1997,"CERTIFICATE"],[2061,2084,"CERTIFICATE"],[2133,2171,"ORGANISATION"],[2196,2206,"LOCATION"],[2253,2294,"PROJECTS"],[2309,2328,"DURATION"],[2350,2394,"ORGANISATION"],[2395,2405,"LOCATION"],[2441,2474,"CERTIFICATE"],[2490,2512,"DURATION"],[2541,2575,"ORGANISATION"],[2673,2692,"PROJECTS"],[2711,2735,"SKILLS"],[2737,2760,"SKILLS"],[2763,2783,"SKILLS"],[2785,2823,"SKILLS"],[2981,3002,"SKILLS"],[3004,3020,"SKILLS"],[3022,3039,"SKILLS"],[3912,3980,"LOCATION"],[3990,4004,"CONTACT"]]}]]}