{
    "classes": [
        "PERSON",
        "LOCATION",
        "SKILLS",
        "CONTACT",
        "EMAIL",
        "ROLE",
        "ORGANISATION",
        "DURATION",
        "CERTIFICATE",
        "PROJECTS",
        "EDUCATION",
        "INSTITUTION"
    ],
    "annotations": [
        [
            "Buvaneswari Sanjeev\nChennai, Tamil Nadu\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Buvaneswari-Sanjeev/7729a99b2e0a7503\n\nA7, Aaksheya Air India Apartment, \n \nNorth Mada Street, Srinagar Colony, \n \nSaidapet, Chennai-600 015. \n \nOBJECTIVE \n \n• Outgoing Telemarketer/Sales Leads offering superb customer service skills and passion for\nexceeding all \ngoals. With a unique ability to relate to all customers/clients results in high sales. Friendly and\nenthusiastic to learn \nto new quickly career skills.\n\nWork Experience\n\nSALES & MARKETING\nWEBINDIA INTERNET SERVICES PVT LTD\nJune 2021 to December 2021\n\nMANAGER\n• Manage digital sales streaming accounts to improve brand positioning and June 2021 - December 2021\ngrowth\n• Successfully spearhead campaigns on social media platforms including\nFacebook, Twitter and Instagram.\n• Through campaign lead we have to speak for Digital Marketing like, SEO, SMO,\nFace Book, Linkedin promotions.\n• Sourcing New Leads for Website Desiging,\n• On Daily Basis have to send 30 mails for New Clients.\n\nASSITANT SALES MANAGER\nTALK MEDIA PVT LTD\nFebruary 2014 to March 2020\n\n• Acquiring new clients and negotiating with them for securing profitable business.\n• Maintaining and managing existing accounts to ensure business sustainability.\n• Maintaining cordial relationship with customers to sustain the profitability of the business.\n• Will achieve my weekly target individually and team target.\n• Good in handling team members.\n• Retaining the client by giving them the best services.\n\nSENIOR TELE MARKETING\n88 DB INDIA PRIVATE LIMITED\nOctober 2012 to December 2013\n\n\f• Generate new business leads and creating advertising solution.\n• Have to generate website lead for business.\n• Introduce new ideas and strategies with senior manager to demonstrate how\ncompany can drive revenue for clients.\n\nTele Marketing Executive\n88DB India Pvt Ltd - Chennai, Tamil Nadu\nSeptember 2010 to September 2012\n\n• Generate new business leads and creating advertising solution.\n• Introduce new ideas and strategies with senior manager to demonstrate how\ncompany can drive revenue for clients.\n• Taking care of Engineering Expo Stall booking.\n\nTele Marketing Executive\nICICI LOMBARD GENERAL INSURANCE COMPANY LIMITED\nMay 2009 to July 2010\n\n• Good in selling General Insurance\n• Will advice the correct Insurance product to the correct clients.\n• Every year renewal will be informed to my existing clients.\n• Over the call we have to sell the insurance to the credit card clients.\n\nEducation\n\nB.COM\nMADURAI KAMARAJ UNIVERSITY - Madurai, Tamil Nadu\nApril 2009\n\nHigher Secondary(12th Pass) in Physical Science\nMadurai Kamaraj University - Nagercoil, Tamil Nadu\nJune 2004 to March 2006\n\n• Windows, MS Office, MS Access, HTML, DTP,\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• TALLY\n\n• Business development\n\n• English\n\n• Leadership\n\n• Marketing\n\n• Negotiation\n\n• Microsoft Excel\n\n• Sales\n\n• Management\n\n\fLanguages\n\n• Tamil - Expert\n• Englisg - Fluent\n\n\f",
            {
                "entities": [
                    [
                        0,
                        19,
                        "PERSON"
                    ],
                    [
                        20,
                        39,
                        "LOCATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        123,
                        225,
                        "LOCATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        520,
                        537,
                        "ROLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        538,
                        572,
                        "ORGANISATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        573,
                        599,
                        "DURATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        684,
                        709,
                        "DURATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        890,
                        893,
                        "SKILLS"
                    ],
                    [
                        895,
                        898,
                        "SKILLS"
                    ],
                    [
                        1032,
                        1054,
                        "ROLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1055,
                        1073,
                        "ORGANISATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        1074,
                        1101,
                        "DURATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        1516,
                        1537,
                        "ROLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1538,
                        1565,
                        "ORGANISATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        1566,
                        1595,
                        "DURATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        1825,
                        1849,
                        "ROLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        1850,
                        1868,
                        "ORGANISATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        1871,
                        1890,
                        "LOCATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        1891,
                        1923,
                        "DURATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        2155,
                        2179,
                        "ROLE"
                    ],
                    [
                        2180,
                        2227,
                        "ORGANISATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        2228,
                        2249,
                        "DURATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        2503,
                        2508,
                        "EDUCATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        2509,
                        2535,
                        "INSTITUTION"
                    ],
                    [
                        2538,
                        2557,
                        "LOCATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        2558,
                        2568,
                        "DURATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        2570,
                        2617,
                        "EDUCATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        2618,
                        2644,
                        "INSTITUTION"
                    ],
                    [
                        2647,
                        2668,
                        "LOCATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        2669,
                        2692,
                        "DURATION"
                    ],
                    [
                        2696,
                        2703,
                        "SKILLS"
                    ],
                    [
                        2708,
                        2714,
                        "SKILLS"
                    ],
                    [
                        2716,
                        2725,
                        "SKILLS"
                    ],
                    [
                        2727,
                        2731,
                        "SKILLS"
                    ],
                    [
                        2733,
                        2736,
                        "SKILLS"
                    ],
                    [
                        2761,
                        2766,
                        "SKILLS"
                    ],
                    [
                        2770,
                        2790,
                        "SKILLS"
                    ],
                    [
                        2847,
                        2862,
                        "SKILLS"
                    ],
                    [
                        2866,
                        2871,
                        "SKILLS"
                    ]
                ]
            }
        ]
    ]
}