{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Aniket Deshmukh\nJalgaon, Maharashtra\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Aniket-Deshmukh/1fce6d0ad5f8fdd9\n\ndigital marketing and promotional activity to improving product demand\n\nWork Experience\n\nMarketing Manger\nchaudhri toyota ltd - Jalgaon, Maharashtra\nFebruary 2017 to Present\n\nMarketing Manager\nsamrudhi pipe ltd\nJune 2016 to April 2017\n\nEducation\n\nMaster's in mba marketing\nnorth maharashtra univarcity - Jalgaon, Maharashtra\nFebruary 2015 to July 2017\n\n• microsoft office, c++,seo,social media marketing\n\n• Search Engine Optimization (SEO)\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• C++\n\n• Digital Marketing\n\n• Marketing\n\n• Google AdWords\n\n• SEO\n\n• SEM\n\n• JavaScript\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,15,"PERSON"],[16,36,"LOCATION"],[116,158,"ROLE"],[205,221,"ROLE"],[222,241,"ORGANISATION"],[244,264,"LOCATION"],[265,289,"DURATION"],[291,308,"ROLE"],[309,326,"ORGANISATION"],[327,350,"DURATION"],[363,388,"EDUCATION"],[389,417,"INSTITUTION"],[420,440,"LOCATION"],[441,467,"DURATION"],[471,487,"SKILLS"],[489,492,"SKILLS"],[493,497,"SKILLS"],[497,519,"SKILLS"],[523,555,"SKILLS"],[586,603,"SKILLS"],[620,634,"SKILLS"],[652,662,"SKILLS"]]}]]}