{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["K.J.MOHAMMED IRFAN\r\nEmail:mdirfan38@gmail.com\r\n\r\nMobile: +971 569656278,+971582134662\r\nPalm Deira, Dubai, UAE\r\n\r\n=============================================================\r\n=========================================\r\nObjective:-\r\n\r\nTo join an organization on that will recognize and utilize my skills fully and \r\noffer me  a position which requires innovative and creative ideas. Willing to\r\nwork as a key player in challenging and creative environment.\r\n\r\n \r\nTechnical Skills\r\n\r\n    :-   \r\n\r\nPersonal Skills:-\r\n\r\nExperience :-\r\n\r\n Hardware troubleshooting.\r\n\r\n Network troubleshooting. \r\n\r\n Programming - Java, C++, Android, .Net Framework, HTML.\r\n\r\n MS Office – Word, PowerPoint, Excel. \r\n\r\n Tally ERP 9.\r\n\r\n Web Design Adobe Creative suite - Photoshop, Dream Viewer.\r\n\r\n OPERATING SYSTEM WINDOWS FAMILY – XP TO WINDOWS 10\r\n\r\n Excellent skills in it support Works.\r\n\r\n Ability   to   easily   assimilate   new   ideas,   concepts,   methods   and\r\n\r\ntechnology.\r\n\r\n Excellent written and verbal communication skills.\r\n\r\n Highly organized and efficient.\r\n\r\n Ability to work independently or as part of team.\r\n\r\n Proven leadership skills and ability to motivate\r\n\r\n1. Paperex   General   Trading   LLC.   (Nov   2014   –   May\r\n\r\n2016)\r\n\r\nWarehouse Assistant (Sales)\r\nDubai, UAE.\r\nwww.paperex.ae. \r\n\r\n2. Plestar, Inc (Jun 2012 – Apr 2013)\r\n\r\nTeam Leader in BPO Industry.\r\n\r\n3. Sundaram Clayton Limited (SCL) TVS (May 2011 to Jan 2012)\r\n\r\nQuality Dept Data Entry Operator.\r\n\r\n4. S.R. Business Service (Jan 2012 – Jun 2012)\r\n\r\n\fExperience Profile:-\r\n\r\nProcess Associate in KPO Industry.\r\n\r\nQuality Control Management\r\nGoods Inward & Outward Statement\r\nGoods Loading & Unloading Supervising & Auditing \r\nMonitoring the labors works\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nGood ability to handle day to day Accounts in Tally\r\nMIS Reporting\r\nCash Reconciliation Statement (Inward & Outward Statement)\r\nCash Management\r\nPreparation of Bank Reconciliation Statement\r\nMaintain Inventory (Stock Reconciliation Statement)\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nEducation :-\r\n\r\nApr 2008 – May 2011\r\nPOLYTECHNIC COLLEGE, India.\r\n\r\nDIPLOMA IN COMPUTER ENGG  - SANKAR \r\n\r\nJun 2007 – Mar 2008\r\n\r\nSSLC – M.N.Abdul Rahman Higher Secondary School, India\r\n\r\nPersonal Details :-\r\n\r\nDate of Birth\r\n\r\n: 25.03.1992\r\n\r\nNationality\r\n\r\n: Indian\r\n\r\nReligion\r\n\r\nMarried Status\r\n\r\n: Muslim\r\n\r\n: Single\r\n\r\nLanguages Known : English, Hindi, Tamil & Malayalam\r\n\r\nPassport Status\r\n\r\n: 13/05/2010 – 12/05/2020\r\n\r\nDriving Licence\r\n\r\n: UAE Driving Licence (Manual)\r\n\r\nVisa Status \r\n\r\n: Visit Visa\r\n\r\nVisa Validity\r\n\r\n : 02/02/2017 -\r\n\r\n20/4/2017\r\n\r\nDeclaration :-\r\n\r\nbest of my knowledge.\r\n\r\nI hereby declare that the above details are true and correct to the \r\n\r\nSignature\r\n\r\n\f                                                                                                                                                                \r\n(K.J.Mohammed Irfan)                                                                                                                              \r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,18,"PERSON"],[26,45,"EMAIL"],[57,71,"CONTACT"],[72,85,"CONTACT"],[87,109,"LOCATION"],[535,560,"SKILLS"],[566,590,"SKILLS"],[597,652,"SKILLS"],[658,694,"SKILLS"],[701,713,"SKILLS"],[719,777,"SKILLS"],[783,833,"SKILLS"],[1183,1217,"ORGANISATION"],[1221,1249,"DURATION"],[1254,1281,"ROLE"],[1319,1331,"ORGANISATION"],[1333,1352,"DURATION"],[1357,1385,"ROLE"],[1392,1426,"ORGANISATION"],[1428,1448,"DURATION"],[1453,1486,"ROLE"],[1493,1514,"ORGANISATION"],[1516,1535,"DURATION"],[1565,1582,"ROLE"],[1586,1599,"ORGANISATION"],[2062,2081,"INSTITUTION"],[2093,2117,"EDUCATION"],[2162,2202,"INSTITUTION"]]}]]}