{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Afsana Shaikh\nMumbai, Maharashtra\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Afsana-Shaikh/36409795b9e6dc99\n\nWork Experience\n\nSales & Marketing\nPrabhat Dairy - Chembur, Mumbai, Maharashtra\nJanuary 2018 to Present\n\nEducation\n\nHigher Secondary(12th Pass)\nYashwant Rao Chavan Maharashtra Open University - Chembur, Mumbai, Maharashtra\nJanuary 2018 to December 2021\n\nHigher Secondary(12th Pass) in Marketing\nYashwant Rao Chavan Maharashtra Open University - Chembur, Mumbai, Maharashtra\nJanuary 2018 to December 2021\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• Marketing\n\n• Sales\n\n• Business development\n\n• Management\n\nCertifications and Licenses\n\nMarketing\nJanuary 2018 to Present\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[14,33,"LOCATION"],[128,145,"ROLE"],[146,159,"ORGANISATION"],[162,190,"LOCATION"],[191,214,"DURATION"],[227,243,"EDUCATION"],[255,302,"INSTITUTION"],[305,333,"LOCATION"],[334,363,"DURATION"],[538,547,"SKILLS"],[551,556,"SKILLS"],[560,580,"SKILLS"],[584,634,"CERTIFICATE"],[635,658,"DURATION"]]}]]}