{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Dipika Das\nInternational City, Dubai\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Dipika-Das/a26573c49574e2e8\n\nWork Experience\n\nDotnet Developer\nSentientGeeks Private Limited - Kolkata, West Bengal\nDecember 2018 to Present\n\nProjects Exposure\n\nBWAC - gpspatrol.bwacsys.net\nTools&Skills: ASP .net Boilerplate,ASP.NET,C#,SQL Server 2017, JQuery,\nPrevounce.com\nTools&Skills : ASP .net Boilerplate,ASP.NET,C#,MySQL, JQuery,Angular 2.x\nBOM TOOLS- Windows form\nTools&Skills : ASP .net Windows form, C#,Sql server, SQL Lite, JQuery,BOM API\nPatrick – web application\nTools&Skills: ASP .net Boilerplate,ASP.NET Core,C#,SQL Server 2017, JQuery,\netc. so many projects I’ve worked.\n\nEducation\n\nMaster's in Master of Computer Applications\nRegent Education and Research Foundation - Kolkata, West Bengal\nMay 2016 to May 2019\n\nBCA\nHIJLI COLLEGE - Kolkata, West Bengal\n2015\n\nArts Stream\nAtulmoni Polytechnic\n2012\n\nBhadutala Vivekananda High school - Kolkata, West Bengal\n2009\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• Development: C#, ASP.NET MVC, WebAPI, WebService\n\n• Platforms&Framework: ASPnetBoilerplate, ASP.NET Core, windows application\n\n• UIDevelopment: CSS, HTML, AJAX, JavaScript, JQuery, JSON, Angular 7\n\n• Data: SQLServer, Entity Framework, My SQL\n\n\f• WebServers: Web site hosting to AWS, AWS services.\n\n• Source Repository: BitBucket, GitHub, TFS\n\nOnline Profile\n\nhttps://www.linkedin.com/in/d\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,10,"PERSON"],[11,36,"LOCATION"],[128,144,"ROLE"],[145,174,"ORGANISATION"],[177,197,"LOCATION"],[198,222,"DURATION"],[243,271,"PROJECTS"],[286,289,"SKILLS"],[290,294,"SKILLS"],[295,306,"SKILLS"],[315,317,"SKILLS"],[318,333,"SKILLS"],[335,341,"SKILLS"],[343,356,"SKILLS"],[411,417,"SKILLS"],[418,429,"SKILLS"],[507,515,"SKILLS"],[681,724,"EDUCATION"],[725,765,"INSTITUTION"],[768,788,"LOCATION"],[789,809,"DURATION"],[811,828,"INSTITUTION"],[831,851,"LOCATION"],[852,856,"DURATION"],[858,869,"EDUCATION"],[870,890,"INSTITUTION"],[1126,1129,"SKILLS"],[1131,1135,"SKILLS"],[1137,1141,"SKILLS"],[1143,1153,"SKILLS"],[1163,1167,"SKILLS"],[1169,1178,"SKILLS"],[1217,1223,"SKILLS"],[1260,1263,"SKILLS"],[1301,1310,"SKILLS"],[1312,1318,"SKILLS"],[1320,1323,"SKILLS"]]}]]}