{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Aastha Manjrekar\nBadlapur, Maharashtra\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Aastha-Manjrekar/bee62f86edd87fcf\n\nWork Experience\n\nnetwork marketing\nAvon,Mi lifestyle,Imc - Badlapur, Maharashtra\n2017 to Present\n\nI have experience in Network Marketing\n\nEducation\n\nBachelor in mass Media\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• Ms-Cit (4 years)\n\n• Communication skills\n\n• English\n\n• Customer service\n\n• Microsoft Word\n\n• Typing\n\n• Hindi\n\n• Computer skills\n\nLanguages\n\n• English,Marathi,Hindi - Fluent\n\nAdditional Information\n\nI have other working experience in other field too\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,16,"PERSON"],[17,38,"LOCATION"],[136,153,"ROLE"],[154,158,"ORGANISATION"],[159,161,"ORGANISATION"],[162,171,"ORGANISATION"],[172,175,"ORGANISATION"],[178,199,"LOCATION"],[200,215,"DURATION"],[268,290,"EDUCATION"],[314,320,"SKILLS"],[389,403,"SKILLS"]]}]]}