{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["CURRICULAM VITAE\r\n\r\nS. SYED ABBAS\r\n\r\nMob No: 8122939313\r\n\r\nOther No: 9486427686\r\n\r\n  & \r\nMail ID: \r\n \r\n \r\n \r\n abbasrafi2012@gmail.com\r\n \r\n    \r\n \r\nMohamedrafi.abbas2011@gmail.com\r\n\r\nObjective\r\n      \r\n         Seeking    for     challenging     position     with    strong     desire    to     make     a\r\nsubstantial  and  positive  impact  towards  the  success  of  the  organization\r\nand  my  own  career  growth.\r\n\r\n SUMMARY\r\n\r\n           I  have  more  than  2  years  of  experience  as  an DUCTMAN, which\r\nincludes 2 years experience in (INDIA & UAE).\r\n\r\nEducational Qualification\r\n\r\n  Diplomo in Civil Engineering (D.C.E.)\r\n  S.S.L.C.\r\n\r\nTechnical Details\r\n     \r\n\r\n   \r\n\r\n  ITI  AC  Mechanic  (N.C.V.T.)\r\n\r\n    \r\n in India\r\n \r\n\r\nExperience \r\n \r\n                                       \r\n                                       Worked as Ac Mechanic\r\n\r\n                                       A.R.A.S P V & Co\r\n\r\n                                       Vannara Pettai, Thirunelveli.\r\n\r\n                                       August 2009 to December 2009,\r\n\r\nIn Abroad (Uae)\r\n\r\n                                         ETA, HRD, Dubai\r\n\r\n                                         From June 2010  to dececmber 2011\r\n\r\n                                         Designation, DUCTMAN (H.V.A.C.).\r\n\r\n\fWorked Places in (UAE)\r\n          \r\n\r\n                                           \r\n\r\n Dubai Metro.\r\n\r\n CCAD (Cleveland Clinic Abudhabi) \r\n\r\nPersonal Details\r\n\r\nName                                   :  S. SYED ABBAS\r\n\r\nFather Name                       :  S. SYED MOHAMMED\r\n\r\nDate of Birth                       :   27/09/1991\r\n\r\nReligion                               :   Muslim\r\n\r\nLanguages Known            :   Tamil, English, Hindi, &  Malayalam\r\n\r\nNationality                          :   Indian\r\n\r\nMarital Status                     :   Single\r\n\r\nSex                                        :   Male\r\n\r\nPermanent Address          :   7-A, Mohamed ali street,\r\n\r\n          Town,\r\n\r\n                                                 Tirunelveli (Dist)- 627006.\r\n\r\n                                                 Tamil Nadu, India.\r\n\r\nPASSPORT DETAILES : \r\n\r\nPassport No                        :   H 9178822\r\n\r\nDate of Issue                       :   03.03.2010\r\n\r\nDate of Expiry                    :   02.03.2020\r\n\r\nCERTIFICATION :\r\n\r\nDeclaration\r\n\r\n AUTOCAD (DRAFTING  SOFTWARE).\r\n\r\n     I  here  by  declare  that  the  all  the  information  given  above  are  true\r\nand  correct  to  the  best  of  my  Knowledge  and  belief.\r\n\r\n                                                                                                                   \r\nYours Sincerely\r\nPlace: Tirunelveli.                                                                                        \r\n                 \r\nDate:                                                                                                             ( S. \r\nSYED ABBAS)\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[20,33,"PERSON"],[45,55,"CONTACT"],[69,79,"CONTACT"],[110,133,"EMAIL"],[147,178,"EMAIL"],[465,473,"DURATION"],[498,505,"ROLE"],[523,530,"DURATION"],[546,551,"LOCATION"],[554,557,"LOCATION"],[595,623,"EDUCATION"],[637,645,"EDUCATION"],[692,704,"ROLE"],[730,735,"LOCATION"],[848,859,"ROLE"],[902,918,"ORGANISATION"],[1191,1219,"DURATION"],[1277,1284,"ROLE"],[2358,2386,"CERTIFICATE"]]}]]}