{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Aman Sharma\nBhopal, Madhya Pradesh\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Aman-Sharma/d42c54dbb1b74309\n\nWork Experience\n\nMarketing\nTours and Travels - Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh\nJuly 2017 to Present\n\nMarketing for tour packages for 3 years\n\nRailways reservation/E-ticket work for 1 year\nSales experience as a salesman for 1 year\n\nEducation\n\nHigher Secondary(12th Pass) in Maths+Computer science\nFather Agnel School CBSE bhopal - Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh\nApril 2017\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• MARKETING\n\n• ADVERTISING\n\n• MARKETING STRATEGY\n\n• EVENT PLANNING\n\n• PUBLIC RELATIONS\n\n• Microsoft office\n\n• Ms word\n\n• Ms excel\n\n• Customer Handling\n\n• Customer Support\n\n• Google Analytics\n\n• Research\n\n• Sales\n\nAdditional Information\n\nSKILLS / IT SKILLS \n \n\n\fMarketing Strategy, Google Analytics, Customer Service, MS Office, Salesforce, Event Planning,\nAdvertising, \nPublic Relations, Ms excel\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[12,34,"LOCATION"],[127,136,"ROLE"],[137,154,"ORGANISATION"],[157,179,"LOCATION"],[180,200,"DURATION"],[202,211,"ROLE"],[216,229,"ORGANISATION"],[234,241,"DURATION"],[243,277,"ORGANISATION"],[282,288,"DURATION"],[311,319,"ROLE"],[324,330,"DURATION"],[343,359,"EDUCATION"],[397,421,"INSTITUTION"],[422,453,"LOCATION"],[454,464,"DURATION"],[488,497,"SKILLS"],[501,512,"SKILLS"],[538,552,"SKILLS"],[576,592,"SKILLS"],[596,603,"SKILLS"],[607,615,"SKILLS"],[640,656,"SKILLS"],[660,676,"SKILLS"],[814,824,"SKILLS"],[856,872,"SKILLS"]]}]]}