{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Curriculum Vitae\r\n\r\nSathish Kumar N.Y.\r\n\r\nMobile: +919566298457 \r\nE-Mail: sathisheeeb@yahoo.co.in\r\n\r\nProfile\r\n\r\n2 Years Professional Experience with plethora of A I D C ( Automated Identification\r\n\r\nand Data Capturing ) product knowledge.\r\n\r\nCareer Objective          \r\n\r\nInclined to seek a challenging job in an organization which guides me to apply the\r\nmaximum of my knowledge, to get job satisfaction and to the future development of\r\nmy career and the organization\r\n\r\nJob Summary\r\n\r\nfor past 2 Years\r\n\r\nWorking in an A I D C (automated Identification and Data Capture) solution provider\r\n\r\nTo handle various types of barcode printers, Scanners, Hand Held Devices and R F ID\r\n\r\nReaders & Tags, as per the customization for end customers.\r\n\r\nAttending client calls to Technical support online and warranty support\r\n\r\nCoordinate   with   Internal   Software   team   bring   out   efficient   performance   of   the\r\n\r\nHardware with the software.  \r\n\r\nBrands Handled\r\n\r\nZebra, Motorola, CITIZEN, Honeywell, Intermec\r\n\r\n\fExperience Summary\r\n\r\nCompany\r\n\r\nDuration\r\n\r\nRR Infosol, Chennai\r\n\r\nAug 2014 to till now\r\n\r\nDesignation\r\n\r\nTechnical Service & Support Engineer  \r\n\r\nCompany\r\n\r\nDuration\r\n\r\n: GK Power Expertise Pvt. Ltd., Chennai\r\n\r\nFeb 2014 to Aug 2014\r\n\r\nDesignation\r\n\r\nTesting & Commissioning Engineer.\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\nResponsibilities\r\n\r\nTesting, commissioning, scheme checking & retrofitting of Alstom & \r\nSchneider relays for generators & transformers.\r\n\r\nCompany\r\n\r\nDuration\r\n\r\n: Hwashin Automotive India Pvt. Ltd., Chennai\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\nJun 2009 to Jun 2010\r\n\r\nDesignation\r\n\r\n: Weld shop maintenance trainee.\r\n\r\nQualification\r\n\r\n B.E. Electrical & Electronics Engineering (at Sree Sastha College of \r\n\r\nEngineering, Chennai, in 2013)- 75%\r\n\r\n Diploma in Electrical & Electronics Engineering (at Central Polytechnic College,\r\n\r\nChennai, in 2009)- 84.96%\r\n\r\nAdditional Qualification\r\n\r\n Testing & commissioning course for electrical equipment\r\n\r\n Training on protection relays Level-1 in ALSTOM\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nIn-plant training in Lucas Indian Service Ltd., Chennai\r\n\r\n    \r\n\r\nComputer Skill\r\n\r\n Languages C\r\n\r\n Completed course Embedded Software Design and Development in NIELIT\r\n\r\n  Hardware: MSP430F5529 Microcontroller  Launchpad\r\n\r\n PC Hardware and software installation, Server,CCTV Installation.\r\n\r\n PLC programming & SCADA & Good working skill in Electrical CAD & MS Office  \r\n\r\n\f       \r\n\r\n       \r\n\r\nPersonal Details \r\n\r\nDate of Birth\r\n\r\n:   18.06.1990\r\n\r\nNationality\r\n\r\nMarital Status\r\n\r\nAddress \r\n\r\n:   Indian\r\n\r\n:   Single\r\n\r\n:   No.326, TNHB Avadi,\r\nChennai – 600054,\r\nIndia.\r\n\r\nPassport Details\r\n\r\n:   Passport No. L4311881, valid till 23.09.2023\r\n\r\nLanguages Known\r\n\r\n:   Tamil, Telugu & English\r\n\r\nStrengths \r\n\r\n:   Friendly, flexible, self-motivated, team working, punctual, \r\ngood communication skill, enthusiastic to learn new things.\r\n\r\nI hereby declare that all the above given information are true to the best of my \r\n\r\nknowledge and belief.\r\n\r\nPlace: \r\n\r\nDate:\r\n\r\n                   \r\n\r\n(SATHISH KUMAR N.Y.)\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[20,33,"PERSON"],[50,63,"CONTACT"],[74,97,"EMAIL"],[112,119,"DURATION"],[161,219,"SKILLS"],[497,504,"DURATION"],[522,591,"ORGANISATION"],[972,977,"ORGANISATION"],[979,987,"ORGANISATION"],[989,996,"ORGANISATION"],[998,1007,"ORGANISATION"],[1009,1017,"ORGANISATION"],[1067,1077,"ORGANISATION"],[1079,1086,"LOCATION"],[1090,1110,"DURATION"],[1129,1165,"ROLE"],[1196,1224,"ORGANISATION"],[1226,1233,"LOCATION"],[1237,1257,"DURATION"],[1276,1309,"ROLE"],[1508,1542,"ORGANISATION"],[1544,1551,"LOCATION"],[1560,1580,"DURATION"],[1601,1631,"ROLE"],[1654,1695,"EDUCATION"],[1700,1738,"INSTITUTION"],[1740,1747,"LOCATION"],[1752,1756,"DURATION"],[1768,1815,"EDUCATION"],[1820,1847,"INSTITUTION"],[1852,1859,"LOCATION"],[1864,1868,"DURATION"],[2028,2074,"CERTIFICATE"],[2115,2126,"SKILLS"],[2132,2173,"CERTIFICATE"],[2178,2199,"SKILLS"],[2216,2254,"SKILLS"],[2330,2345,"SKILLS"],[2348,2353,"SKILLS"],[2378,2392,"SKILLS"],[2395,2404,"SKILLS"]]}]]}