{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Aman Raj\nGodda, Jharkhand\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Aman-Raj/50230c3d03035bd5\n\nWork Experience\n\nShopify Developer\nTPS Technologies - Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh\nApril 2021 to Present\n\nE-commerce Company\n- Understanding of various design patterns and custom Shopify theme development.\nStrong knowledge of liquid programming language.\n-Generate custom-tailored Shopify theme and altering pre-existing template.\nAct as Shopify expert, specializing in all facets of the e-commerce platform.\nStrong hands to Install & Customize new Shopify theme.\nFast learner & interested in new technologies\nThe ability to remain cool under pressure.\n\nShopify Developer\nMarket 99\n\nShopify expert\nE-commerce Company - New Delhi, Delhi\nMarch 2021 to April 2021\n\nUnderstanding of various design patterns and custom Shopify theme development.\nStrong knowledge of liquid programming language.\n-Generate custom-tailored Shopify theme and altering pre-existing template.\nAct as Shopify expert, specializing in all facets of the e-commerce platform.\nStrong hands to Install & Customize new Shopify theme.\n\nFreelance Developer\nSelf Employed\nApril 2019 to February 2021\n\nBhopal, Madhya Pradesh\nDeveloping Websites For Clients\n- Coded websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and jQuery languages.\nDesigned,  implemented  and  monitored  web  pages,  plugins  and  functionality  for  continuous\nimprovement.\nCreated websites in wordpress too\n\nwww.enhancv.com Powered by\n\n\fEducation\n\nTechno Misson International School - Bhagalpur, Bihar\n2014\n\nB.E/B.TECH in My Higher Secondary Education\nRKDF University - Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh\n\n• Java Html 5 CSS 3 Javascript JQuery Bootstrap Shopify Shopify Liquid Wordpress Tool / Technology\n\nNever Look Back Stubborn\n\n• I Never think about what i wasted, I always think about\n\n• Once i Start Something, Its not over, till its over kind of what i can achieve thing for me. Quick\n\n• I never stop pushing myself. i always grab things quickly to groom and make myself even better\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\nLearner\n\neveryday.\n\nOnline Profile\n\nhttp://www.amanshaurya.com\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[16,25,"LOCATION"],[115,132,"ROLE"],[133,149,"ORGANISATION"],[152,174,"LOCATION"],[175,196,"DURATION"],[646,663,"ROLE"],[664,689,"ORGANISATION"],[715,727,"LOCATION"],[728,752,"DURATION"],[1092,1111,"ROLE"],[1112,1125,"ORGANISATION"],[1126,1153,"DURATION"],[1155,1177,"LOCATION"],[1396,1438,"PROJECTS"],[1452,1497,"ORGANISATION"],[1500,1516,"LOCATION"],[1517,1521,"DURATION"],[1523,1533,"EDUCATION"],[1540,1566,"EDUCATION"],[1567,1582,"INSTITUTION"],[1585,1607,"LOCATION"],[1611,1615,"SKILLS"],[1616,1622,"SKILLS"],[1623,1628,"SKILLS"],[1629,1639,"SKILLS"],[1640,1646,"SKILLS"],[1647,1656,"SKILLS"],[1665,1679,"SKILLS"],[1680,1694,"SKILLS"],[2034,2076,"EMAIL"]]}]]}