{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Resume\r\n\r\nNazir alam\r\n\r\nWard no.14,\r\nMakhdumpur gulzarbagh p.o + p.s:-makhdumpur,Dis-\r\nJehanabad,Bihar-804422\r\nPh No. +918804541663,9162527706\r\nE-Mail-naziralam280@gmail.com\r\n\r\nCARRIER OBJECTIVE\r\nTo secure a suitable and stable position leading toward a successful\r\nCareer utilizing all my education capabilities in overall success of  my company and \r\nprofessional growth.\r\n\r\nEducational Qualifications:\r\n\r\n 10th passed from BSEB Board in 2008\r\n 12th Passed from BSEB Board in 2012\r\n\r\nExperience:\r\n\r\n 1 Years experience in munjal showa ltd, manesar,Haryana as \r\n\r\nan mechanical engg.\r\n\r\n 6 month vocational traning in railways workshop in gaya, \r\n\r\nBihar\r\n\r\nTechnical Qualification:\r\n\r\n Complete two years ITI in ‘’FITTER’’ FROM MAGADH ITI \r\n\r\nGAYA during the session from 2008 to 2010\r\n\r\n   .\r\n \r\n   Complete three years Diploma in ‘’Mechanical engg’’ from K.K POLYTECHNIC\r\n \r\n \r\nNalanda Bihar during the session from 2012 to 2015  \r\n                \r\nSTRENGTH \r\n\r\n Accepting Challenges As opportunity\r\n Honest, commitment to work\r\n Believe in Teamwork\r\n\r\nPersonal Details:\r\n\r\n: 16/03/1993\r\n: Mr Nazim uddin\r\n: Male\r\n:\r\n\r\nDate of Birth\r\nFather's Name\r\nSex\r\nIndian\r\nNationality\r\nLanguages Known : English , Hindi, & Urdu.    .\r\nMarital Status\r\nReligion                              :      Muslim\r\n\r\n: Unmarried\r\n\r\nDECLARATION\r\n\r\nI hereby declare that the above information given above is true and to the best of \r\n\r\n\f nazir alam\r\n \r\n \r\n \r\nPlace:…/…/…                                                                              \r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[10,20,"PERSON"],[24,109,"LOCATION"],[118,142,"CONTACT"],[144,173,"EMAIL"],[410,421,"EDUCATION"],[427,437,"INSTITUTION"],[441,445,"DURATION"],[449,460,"EDUCATION"],[466,476,"INSTITUTION"],[480,484,"DURATION"],[505,512,"DURATION"],[527,543,"ORGANISATION"],[545,560,"LOCATION"],[571,587,"ROLE"],[595,619,"CERTIFICATE"],[623,640,"ORGANISATION"],[644,659,"LOCATION"],[702,711,"DURATION"],[719,729,"ROLE"],[735,745,"ORGANISATION"],[779,791,"DURATION"],[816,827,"DURATION"],[828,835,"EDUCATION"],[839,858,"EDUCATION"],[864,879,"INSTITUTION"],[887,894,"LOCATION"],[895,900,"LOCATION"],[925,937,"DURATION"]]}]]}