{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Athul Das\nErnakulam, Kerala\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Athul-Das/f5b8b5207447bf6b\n\nWork Experience\n\nDEVELOPER\nTATA CONSULTANCY SERVICES\nNovember 2018 to Present\n\nExperience in working on ignio Automation (Development, Testing, Enhancement)\nactivities.\nExperience in Groovy, Bash, DAX Scripting.\nExperience in Power BI development.\nExperience in supporting Applications in Production.\nEngaged with various US based clients operating under the Energy and Digital\nsector.\nTrained in Ui-Path Automation, Pega RPA and Certified in Ignio Automation.\n\nTCS INTERNAL CERTIFICATIONS\n● Digital: Mobile Computing Android Foundation\n● UiPath: Level 1 Foundation Training\n● BIPM: Microsoft Power BI Intermediate\n● MFDM AI Beginner Foundation Curriculum\n● Foundation certificate in Electricity Management\n● Agile Way of Working\n\nEducation\n\nBSc. in Computer Science\nSwamy Saswathikananda College - Ernakulam, Kerala\n2018\n\nAISSCE in Computer Science Stream\nStella Maris Convent School - Ernakulam, Kerala\n2015\n\nAISSE\nStella Maris Convent School - Ernakulam, Kerala\n2013\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• Communication Skills -Helps in direct involvement with clients, better ability to convey ideas.\n\n• Team Management Skills -Better understanding of the team structure, workflow and interpersonal\n\nhelps in activity delegation.\n\n\f• Real Time monitoring of deliverables from teammates complying to SLAs.\n\n• Brain Storming Skills -Ability to identify improvement areas in a team and to develop solutions.\n\n• Excellent Document Skills -Often helps in recording activities and processes. Groovy Java Bash\n\nAndroid Power BI Power Automate SQL PostgreSQL MS PowerPoint MS Word MS Excel LANGUAGE\n\n• English\n\n• Malayalam\n\n• Hindi\n\n• Hardworking\n\n• Quick Learner\n\n• Adaptable and Friendly 2\n\n• Java\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,9,"PERSON"],[10,27,"LOCATION"],[118,127,"ROLE"],[128,153,"ORGANISATION"],[154,178,"DURATION"],[205,221,"ORGANISATION"],[284,290,"SKILLS"],[292,296,"SKILLS"],[298,312,"SKILLS"],[327,348,"SKILLS"],[498,516,"SKILLS"],[593,637,"CERTIFICATE"],[640,675,"CERTIFICATE"],[676,715,"CERTIFICATE"],[718,756,"CERTIFICATE"],[759,807,"CERTIFICATE"],[843,867,"EDUCATION"],[868,897,"INSTITUTION"],[900,917,"LOCATION"],[918,922,"DURATION"],[924,950,"EDUCATION"],[951,985,"INSTITUTION"],[988,1005,"LOCATION"],[1006,1010,"DURATION"],[1012,1017,"EDUCATION"],[1018,1045,"INSTITUTION"],[1048,1065,"LOCATION"],[1066,1070,"DURATION"],[1582,1586,"SKILLS"],[1625,1628,"SKILLS"],[1629,1639,"SKILLS"],[1640,1653,"SKILLS"],[1654,1661,"SKILLS"],[1662,1670,"SKILLS"]]}]]}