{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Amit Jain\nAs a Web Developer\nNew Delhi, Delhi\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Amit-Jain/894c9cf916f36cb2\n\nWork Experience\n\nAs a Web Developer\nIn Eternal Concepts Pvt. Ltd. Lajpat Nagar Delhi - Delhi, Delhi\nJanuary 2010 to December 2011\n\nIn Technoweb Solutions Darya ganj New Delhi.\nRoll: As a Web Designer\n\nTechnical  Qualifications  •  Completed  MULTIMEDIA  &  WEBDESIGNING  From  Oxford  Software  Institute\nKings Way Camp New Delhi\n\nEducation\n\nB.com\nUNIVERSITY OF DELHI - Delhi, Delhi\n\nAdditional Information\n\nAdditional Qualifications \nThree months certificate Course in Basic Computer from Achievers Academy Darya Ganj New Delhi. \n \nBasic Aware (ms office, and internet) \n \nAbout my Self \n \nAddress: 4608, Ansari Road, Darya Ganj, \nNew Delhi-110002 \n \nContact No.: 9716535774 \n \nE. Mail Address: amitjh68@gmail.com \n \nReligion: Jain \n \nDate: . (AMIT JAIN) \n \nPlace: ..\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,9,"PERSON"],[15,28,"ROLE"],[29,45,"LOCATION"],[141,154,"ROLE"],[158,184,"ORGANISATION"],[185,218,"LOCATION"],[219,248,"DURATION"],[253,272,"ORGANISATION"],[273,294,"LOCATION"],[361,388,"EDUCATION"],[396,438,"INSTITUTION"],[439,448,"LOCATION"],[461,466,"EDUCATION"],[467,486,"INSTITUTION"],[489,501,"LOCATION"],[554,566,"DURATION"],[567,603,"CERTIFICATE"],[609,626,"INSTITUTION"],[627,648,"LOCATION"],[652,689,"CERTIFICATE"],[815,833,"EMAIL"]]}]]}