{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["CURRICULUM-VITAE\r\n\r\nVillage – Tejpurwa, \r\nPost – Kishunpur Telaur, \r\nPS – Patepur, Distt. – Vaishal, \r\nBihar-843102\r\nContact No. 07404118574,\r\n                   07053727888\r\nEmail. alam1286@gmail.com\r\n\r\nSeeking of careen in field of teaching in a globally challenging environment where\r\nmy knowledge and expertise blend with my life at the same time providing an ample\r\nspace from me to learn and grow.\r\n\r\nMD. EJAZ AHAMAD\r\n\r\nCAREER OBJECTIVE\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nEDUCATION QUALIFICATION\r\n\r\nPursuing B.A. from B.U Muzaffarpur Bihar\r\n10+2 Pass from Inter Council Patna\r\n10 Pass from Bihar School Examination Board Patna\r\n\r\nSOFTWARE SKILL SET\r\n\r\nOperating System\r\nPackages\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\nWindow XP\r\n\r\n:\r\nMs-Office\r\n\r\n Working as a Plumber in Ahluwalia Contractors (India) Limited from last 5 years to till\r\n\r\n Net Suffering\r\n\r\nEXPERIENCE \r\n   \r\n\r\ndate.\r\n\r\nPERSONAL DETAILS\r\n\r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\n\r\nAbdul Razzaque \r\n02/04/1994\r\nUnmarried \r\nMale\r\nIndian \r\nMuslim  \r\nHindi & Urdu \r\nPlaying Cricket   \r\n\r\nFather’s Name\r\nDate of Birth\r\nMarital Status\r\nSex\r\nNationality  \r\nReligion\r\nLanguage \r\nHobbies\r\n\r\nPlace: Bihar\r\nDate:\r\n\r\n(Md. Ejaz Ahamad)\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[129,140,"CONTACT"],[162,173,"CONTACT"],[182,200,"EMAIL"],[407,422,"PERSON"],[506,510,"EDUCATION"],[516,519,"INSTITUTION"],[520,531,"LOCATION"],[532,537,"LOCATION"],[539,543,"EDUCATION"],[554,573,"INSTITUTION"],[575,577,"EDUCATION"],[588,618,"INSTITUTION"],[685,694,"SKILLS"],[701,710,"SKILLS"],[729,736,"ROLE"],[740,761,"ORGANISATION"],[783,795,"DURATION"],[1126,1141,"PERSON"]]}]]}