{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Ekta Merai\nSurat, Gujarat\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Ekta-Merai/6d63f374d6d100c5\n\nWork Experience\n\nShopify Developer-wordpress Developer\nTecocraft Infusion Pvt Ltd - Surat, Gujarat\nJanuary 2021 to Present\n\nDeveloped site from the scratch in Wordpress and shopify.\n● Worked with Shopify AJAX API, Admin REST API\n● Worked with CLI, Themekit, GITHUB\n● Developed custom, private and public apps.\n● Communicate with clients and collect the requirements.\n● Customized the theme in shopify\n● Improved the site speed in shopify and wordpress site\n● Fixed the bugs on sites\n\nShopify Developer-wordpress Developer\nDay dream soft Pvt Ltd - Surat, Gujarat\nApril 2019 to December 2020\n\nDeveloped site from the scratch in Wordpress and shopify.\n● Communicate with clients and collect the requirements.\n● Customized the plugin in wordpress.\n● Customized the theme in shopify\n● Improved the site speed in shopify and wordpress site\n● Fixed the bugs on sites\n\nPHP Developer\nBroadview Innovation Pvt Ltd - Surat, Gujarat\nJuly 2017 to June 2018\n\nDeveloped customization option and integrated payment gateway according to client\nrequirement for online booking system.\n• Tested \"Cleanto\" booking system.\n\nEducation\n\nICT\nJ. P. Dawer Institute of Information Science & Technology - Surat, Gujarat\nJune 2015 to April 2017\n\nBCA in Photography\nUsha Institute of Applied Science & Dhiru-Sarla Institute of Management & Commerce valsad - valsad,\nGUJARAT, IN\n\n\f• HTML, CSS, PHP, Liquid, Shopify, Shopify 2.0, WordPress, Ajax, jQuery, Mysql, REST API, Admin Ajax\n\nJune 2012 to February 2015\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\nAPI.\n\n• Shopify private app, public app, custom app\n\n• HTML to Shopify website development by using section and metafield\n\n• HTML to Wordpress website development by using ACF custom field\n\n• eCommerce website development by using Woocommerce\n\n• Different type of shopify theme and APPs integration and customization\n\n• Payment Method: Paypal, Stripe, PayU, Airpay, 2chckout, EBS\n\nOnline Profile\n\nhttp://www.linkedin.com/in/ekta-merai\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,10,"PERSON"],[11,25,"LOCATION"],[117,154,"SKILLS"],[155,181,"ORGANISATION"],[184,198,"LOCATION"],[199,222,"DURATION"],[224,281,"PROJECTS"],[304,312,"SKILLS"],[314,328,"SKILLS"],[331,346,"SKILLS"],[348,356,"SKILLS"],[358,364,"SKILLS"],[584,621,"ROLE"],[622,644,"ORGANISATION"],[647,661,"LOCATION"],[662,689,"DURATION"],[961,974,"ROLE"],[975,1003,"ORGANISATION"],[1006,1020,"LOCATION"],[1021,1043,"DURATION"],[1176,1200,"PROJECTS"],[1213,1216,"EDUCATION"],[1220,1274,"INSTITUTION"],[1277,1291,"LOCATION"],[1292,1315,"DURATION"],[1317,1335,"EDUCATION"],[1336,1369,"ORGANISATION"],[1372,1418,"ORGANISATION"],[1419,1447,"LOCATION"],[1452,1456,"SKILLS"],[1458,1461,"SKILLS"],[1463,1466,"SKILLS"],[1476,1483,"SKILLS"],[1485,1496,"SKILLS"],[1509,1513,"SKILLS"],[1523,1528,"SKILLS"],[1552,1578,"DURATION"],[1608,1627,"PROJECTS"],[1629,1639,"PROJECTS"],[1641,1651,"PROJECTS"]]}]]}