{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["MUSTAFA AHMAD \r\n\r\nCONTACT \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\nKEY SKILLS \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\nmustafaemco@gmail.comS \r\n\r\n00918447380882 \r\n\r\nHTTPS://WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/AH\r\nMAD-MUSTAFA-2B67B6B6/ \r\n\r\nOverall 35 years of experience in Civil ,Oil and Gas Facilities Maintenance \r\nof Upstream and down steam office ,Process, Building facilities in Middle \r\nEast, Bangladesh and India \r\nManaged  technical  maintenance  (PPM,  AMC  and  Critical  equipment)  of \r\nElectrical, HVAC, Civil and Landscaping at various roles.  \r\n\r\nLead  the  team  to  develop  the  functional  specification  for  the \r\nComputerized Facilities management System (CAFM) and rolling out (Work \r\ninvolves preparation of Asset register , PPM master, Testing and \r\n\r\nimprovements) \r\n\r\nManaged  technical  maintenance  (PPM,  AMC  and  Critical  equipment)  of \r\nElectrical, HVAC, Civil and Landscaping at various roles. \r\n\r\nTrained internal auditor for ISO 9001:2008 and OHSAS 14001 \r\n\r\nOil & Gas safety standards such as PTW, LOTO, Confined Space entry etc. \r\n\r\nEXPERIENCE \r\n\r\nLANGUAGES \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\nENGLISH, ARABIC, HINDI \r\n\r\n \r\nmanagement, \r\n\r\nSite \r\nProject \r\nand \r\nProcurement \r\nEngineering, \r\nConstruction, \r\nLayout  &  design, \r\nSurveys  &  Estimation,  Budget  & \r\nForecasting,  Quality  Control,  Client \r\nRelationship  Management,  Tender \r\nManagement, \r\nRisk  Management, \r\nReport  Preparation,  Laisoning,  Labor \r\nManagement \r\n\r\nCONSTRUCTION MANAGER- EMCO, QATAR \r\nDec 2005 to July 2017 \r\nSupervision of Maintenance work for, RASGAS Company \r\n\r\nRas Laffan Industrial City Doha- Qatar \r\n\r\nConstruction M  anager in Qatar foundation MEP and Civil Works.  \r\n\r\nSite Manager in Qatar Shell GTL Civil Maintenance Works. \r\n\r\nTRADE ENGINEER- FAWAZ REFRIGERATION KUWAIT \r\nApril 2003 to Dec 2005 \r\nSupervision of Maintenance work for Kuwait University, Keifan, \r\nHawally, Adaliya & Jabriya Medical \r\n\r\nPROJECT  CO-COORDINATOR-  AL  MANSOURYAH  EST.  FOR \r\nTRADING AND CONTRACTING, KSA \r\nApril 1999 to Feb 2003 \r\nKing Fahed Specialist Hospital Project, Dammam \r\n\r\nExecution  work  include  –  Structural  and  Interior  of  main \r\nhospital  building,  Screening  clinic,  underground  shelter, \r\nRehabilitation   and Radiology center Recreation Center, Staff \r\nhousing  complex,  Sewerage  treatment  plant  and  site \r\ndevelopment including survey \r\n\r\nRESIDENT ENGINEER- C.P. KUKREJA ASSOCIATES DELHI AND \r\nBANGLADESH \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n \r\n \r\n \r\n\r\n\f \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\nPERSONAL DETAILS \r\n\r\nPASSPORT NO. : G-9439485 \r\nVALIDITY: 20TH JULY 2018 \r\n\r\nDOB: 01-07-1958 \r\n\r\nTECHNICAL SKILLS \r\n\r\nPRIMAVERA \r\n\r\nSAP (PRODUCTION) \r\n\r\nMS PROJECT \r\n\r\nMS OFFICE \r\n\r\nPROFESSOINAL MEMBERSHIP \r\n\r\nINSTITUTE OF VALUERS \r\n\r\nNEW DELHI \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\nFeb 1993 to March 1999 \r\nSupervision of a centrally Air Conditioned modern building at \r\nSector  16A,  Noida  belongs  to  SGS  Thomson  Micro-Electronics \r\nPvt. Ltd. Supervision of Apollo Group of Hospitals  \r\n\r\nProject Planning of \"Continental Hospital Ltd.\" 500 bed multi-\r\nspecialty ultra-modern hospital \r\n\r\nSR. CIVIL ENGINEER- VASTUKALA CONSULTANTS, DELHI \r\nJan 1984 to Jan 1993 \r\nPreparation of tenders, Quantity surveying, Preparation of bill, \r\nProject  Planning  and  Site  supervision  of  Residential,  Factory \r\nbuilding, Hospital (Batra Hospital) \r\n\r\nSURVEYOR/DESIGN ASSISTANT- MIDMAC S.A.R.L, IRAQ \r\nJan 1983 to Dec 1983 \r\nSurvey works of Roads, Kerbstone and Sewer work \r\n\r\nSITE  ENGINEER-  AL  SWAYEH  EST.  FOR  TRADING  AND \r\nCONTRACTING, KSA \r\nAug 1978 to June 1982 \r\nWater supply work mainly of UPVC, A/C Pipe line, Overhead, \r\nunderground water tank and Dug well. \r\n\r\nASSISTANT QUALITY SURVEYOR- INDIAN HOTEL CO, DELHI \r\nNov 1977 to Jul 1978 \r\nSupervision of five star hotel (Taj Mahal Project) and Quantity \r\nSurveying work \r\n\r\nJUNIOR ENGINEER- HOWE INDIA PVT.LTD, DELHI \r\nFeb 1976 to Oct 1977 \r\nSupervision of grain soils Project of Food Corporation of India \r\nat Khurja Mandi, Gobind Garh and Moga, Punja \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\nBACHELOR OF ENGINEERING IN CIVIL \r\nJAMIA MILIA ISLAMIA \r\nDIPLOMA IN CIVIL ENGINEERING \r\n\r\nJAMIA MILIA ISLAMIA \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n2 \r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[83,105,"EMAIL"],[110,124,"CONTACT"],[135,182,"EMAIL"],[195,203,"DURATION"],[379,457,"PROJECTS"],[465,486,"PROJECTS"],[583,624,"PROJECTS"],[697,707,"PROJECTS"],[752,813,"PROJECTS"],[890,940,"SKILLS"],[1101,1149,"SKILLS"],[1169,1186,"SKILLS"],[1190,1212,"SKILLS"],[1215,1238,"SKILLS"],[1296,1315,"SKILLS"],[1396,1417,"ROLE"],[1418,1422,"ORGANISATION"],[1424,1429,"LOCATION"],[1432,1453,"DURATION"],[1456,1487,"ROLE"],[1493,1507,"ORGANISATION"],[1512,1550,"LOCATION"],[1555,1577,"ROLE"],[1581,1618,"ORGANISATION"],[1624,1636,"ROLE"],[1640,1680,"ORGANISATION"],[1685,1700,"ROLE"],[1701,1720,"ORGANISATION"],[1721,1727,"LOCATION"],[1730,1752,"DURATION"],[1755,1786,"ROLE"],[1791,1808,"ORGANISATION"],[1859,1883,"ROLE"],[1885,1936,"ORGANISATION"],[1944,1966,"DURATION"],[1969,2007,"PROJECTS"],[2309,2327,"ROLE"],[2328,2351,"ORGANISATION"],[2557,2587,"SKILLS"],[2592,2602,"SKILLS"],[2607,2633,"SKILLS"],[3588,3615,"ROLE"],[3616,3631,"ORGANISATION"],[3641,3661,"DURATION"],[3664,3675,"ROLE"],[3679,3714,"ORGANISATION"],[3749,3765,"ROLE"],[3766,3784,"ORGANISATION"],[3794,3814,"DURATION"],[3937,3969,"EDUCATION"],[3972,3991,"INSTITUTION"],[3994,4022,"EDUCATION"],[4027,4046,"INSTITUTION"]]}]]}