{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Bavithra Graham\nWeb Developer and Content Creator\nBengaluru, Karnataka\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Bavithra-Graham/fda56f9bb950ac7b\n\nPersonal Details\n\nDate of Birth: 1993-08-24\nEligible to work in: India\nHighest Career Level: 5+ years experience\nIndustry: IT Operations & Helpdesk, Project Management, Software Development\nTotal years of experience: 5\n\nWork Experience\n\nWebsite Developer\nFFMedias - Sivakasi, Tamil Nadu\nApril 2016 to September 2019\n\n• Creative website development\n• Content Management\n\n• WordPress and Drupal Expert\n• BigCommerce and PHP Specialist\n• Template creation using Backbone JS\n\nPHP Web Developer\nSelvam Infotech Pvt Ltd - Sivakasi, Tamil Nadu\nSeptember 2014 to March 2016\n\n• PHP Website development\n• Content drafting specialist\n• Code Review and bug tracking\n• Deployment to specific server\nInvolved  in  complete  End-to-End  Website  development  as  an  independent  resource  including  content\ncreation as per the client needs.\n\nEducation\n\nBachelor's in Information Technology\nMepco Schlenk Engineering College - Sivakasi, Tamil Nadu\nAugust 2010 to April 2014\n\n\fSkills / IT Skills\n\n• Wordpress\n\n• Bigcommerce\n\n• PHP\n\n• Drupal\n\n• Html5\n\n• Css\n\n• Jquery\n\n• Backbone JS\n\nLanguages\n\n• English - Expert\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,15,"PERSON"],[16,29,"SKILLS"],[34,49,"SKILLS"],[50,70,"LOCATION"],[243,251,"DURATION"],[273,297,"SKILLS"],[299,317,"SKILLS"],[319,339,"SKILLS"],[387,404,"SKILLS"],[405,413,"ORGANISATION"],[416,436,"LOCATION"],[437,465,"DURATION"],[522,531,"SKILLS"],[609,620,"SKILLS"],[622,625,"SKILLS"],[626,639,"ROLE"],[640,663,"ORGANISATION"],[666,686,"LOCATION"],[687,715,"DURATION"],[719,722,"SKILLS"],[990,1026,"EDUCATION"],[1027,1060,"INSTITUTION"],[1063,1083,"LOCATION"],[1084,1109,"DURATION"],[1147,1158,"SKILLS"],[1169,1175,"SKILLS"],[1179,1184,"SKILLS"],[1188,1191,"SKILLS"],[1195,1201,"SKILLS"]]}]]}