{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Priyadharshini P\r\nChennai, Tamil Nadu\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Priyadharshini-P/ee5cb63da88bc704\r\n\r\n9 years of experience in Oracle SQL and PL/SQL \r\n• 1 year experience in developing Java - Spring Boot Applications. \r\n• Demonstrated strong leadership abilities in the projects handled with minimal supervision. \r\n• Showcased the potential to handle projects both independently and in teams. \r\n• Effectively handled overlapping deadlines in a fast-paced environment and handled \r\nmultiple assignments simultaneously. \r\n• Experienced in both Waterfall and Agile Methodologies.\r\n\r\nPersonal Details\r\n\r\nEligible to work in: India\r\nHighest Career Level: 5+ years experience\r\nTotal years of experience: 10\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nDevelopment Lead\r\nStandard Chartered Global Business Services India - Chennai, Tamil Nadu\r\nMarch 2019 to Present\r\n\r\n• Development and Enhancement Activities\r\n• Complete ownership of the assigned projects\r\n• Impact Analysis for the business requirement\r\n• Preparation of Design, flow/sequence diagram and creation of granular\r\nResponsibilities sub task for user stories.\r\n• Coordinating with other interface teams and supporting the System\r\nIntegration Testing, User Acceptance Testing and Production Roll-out\r\n• Mentoring new resources/other developers for their technical and functional queries\r\n\r\nDeveloper\r\nCapgemini\r\nJuly 2015 to March 2019\r\n\r\n• Development and Enhancement activities.\r\n• Data -Designing for the development activities.\r\n• Test case preparation, Test execution and test log preparation for unit\r\ntesting.\r\nResponsibilities\r\n• Defect fixes for production issues.\r\n• Creating the Change request and co-ordinating with the respective\r\ninterface team for on-time and smooth production roll out.\r\n• Daily/Weekly/Monthly Status Report Tracker\r\n\r\n\fDeveloper\r\nTata Consultancy Services - Chennai, Tamil Nadu\r\nOctober 2011 to July 2015\r\n\r\n• Development, Enhancement and Maintenance of all scripts required for\r\nthe complete refresh of an environment.\r\n• Documentation of all environmental refresh activities for all\r\napplications.\r\n• To coordinate and work with various teams (Application. Infrastructure, and Release Management) to\r\nsolve all environment\r\nResponsibilities related issues.\r\n• Root Cause Analysis for environment issues.\r\n• Monitoring the usage of servers.\r\n• Weekly/Monthly Health Check Report generation for active\r\nenvironments.\r\n• Created a knowledge transfer plan and facilitated knowledge transfer on\r\nall activities.\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nBachelor's in Information Technology\r\nVelammal Engineering College - Chennai, Tamil Nadu\r\nApril 2007 to May 2011\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Primary Skills : Oracle SQL , PL/SQL Secondary Skills : Java Spring Boot , Unix Operating System:\r\nWindows, Unix, LinuxMessaging Services: IBM MQ, MQ TDE, Oracle AQ, SolaceTools: Toad, SQL\r\nDeveloper, IntelliJ Idea, Maven, Jenkins, Putty,FTP tools, Postman, Microsoft Office SuiteBug Tracker:\r\nHP Quality Center, JIRAVersion Control: IBM Rational Clear case, SVN, GIT- Bit BucketDocumentation:\r\nConfluence\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,16,"PERSON"],[18,25,"LOCATION"],[27,37,"LOCATION"],[121,128,"DURATION"],[146,156,"SKILLS"],[161,167,"SKILLS"],[172,178,"DURATION"],[204,208,"SKILLS"],[211,222,"SKILLS"],[575,580,"SKILLS"],[669,677,"DURATION"],[717,719,"DURATION"],[742,758,"ROLE"],[760,778,"ORGANISATION"],[779,809,"ORGANISATION"],[812,819,"LOCATION"],[821,831,"LOCATION"],[833,854,"DURATION"],[1341,1350,"ROLE"],[1352,1361,"ORGANISATION"],[1363,1386,"DURATION"],[1785,1813,"ROLE"],[1815,1840,"ORGANISATION"],[1843,1850,"LOCATION"],[1852,1862,"LOCATION"],[1864,1889,"DURATION"],[2510,2546,"LOCATION"],[2548,2576,"INSTITUTION"],[2579,2586,"LOCATION"],[2588,2598,"LOCATION"],[2600,2622,"DURATION"],[2667,2677,"SKILLS"],[2706,2722,"SKILLS"],[2749,2756,"SKILLS"],[2758,2762,"SKILLS"],[2764,2778,"SKILLS"],[2789,2792,"SKILLS"],[2835,2838,"SKILLS"],[2866,2871,"SKILLS"],[2873,2880,"SKILLS"]]}]]}