{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Praveen Vadlamudi\r\nHubli, Karnataka\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Praveen-Vadlamudi/1440b714f0f6ec61\r\n\r\nTo start my Accounts career by joining a well settled and highly professional organization in form to\r\nlearn from the various instances and provided by the organization and to return back in manifold by\r\nextending my sincere and dedicated services.\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate to: Bengaluru, Karnataka - Gadag, Karnataka - Hubli, Karnataka\r\n\r\nPersonal Details\r\n\r\nDate of Birth: 1997-09-27\r\nEligible to work in: India\r\nHighest Career Level: 1-2 years experience\r\nIndustry: Accounting, Advertising, PR, MR, Event Management, Architecture, Interior Design, Banking\r\n& Finance, Business Operations, Call Center, Customer Service, Electrical Engineering, Export,\r\nImport, IT Operations & Helpdesk, IT-Hardware & Networking, Installation & Maintenance, Internet,\r\nEcommerce, Management, Marketing, Software Development, Sports\r\nTotal years of experience: 3\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nMarketing Executive\r\nShalom Entrrprisea - Hubli, Karnataka\r\nNovember 2019 to Present\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nBACHELOR OF COMMERCE-B.COM in COMMERCE\r\nNEHRU ARTS, SCIENCE, COMMERCE AND BBA COLLEGE HUBLI\r\nDecember 2020 to 2021\r\n\r\nSCIENCE & COMMERCE\r\nCOLLEGE HUBLI\r\nMay 2017\r\n\r\nSECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE in ORGANISATION ENGLISH\r\nMEDIUM HIGH SCHOOL HUBLI\r\nApril 2013\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• CSS BASICS\r\n\r\n\f• TALLY ERP-9.0\r\n\r\n• MS-OFFICE 2007\r\n\r\n• Possess good relationship building and interpersonal skills.\r\n\r\n• Hardworking and quick learner.\r\n\r\n• Commitment towards work.\r\n\r\n• Sincerity and Self-Confidence.\r\n\r\n• Quick adaptability to challenging situation.\r\n\r\n• Good Team Player and Self-Motivated.\r\n\r\n• Computer skills\r\n\r\n• Marketing\r\n\r\n• Communication skills\r\n\r\n• Business development\r\n\r\n• Sales\r\n\r\nOnline Profile\r\n\r\nhttp://COMMERCE-B.COM\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,17,"PERSON"],[19,24,"LOCATION"],[26,35,"LOCATION"],[396,405,"LOCATION"],[407,416,"LOCATION"],[419,424,"LOCATION"],[426,435,"LOCATION"],[438,443,"LOCATION"],[445,454,"LOCATION"],[555,564,"DURATION"],[587,597,"ROLE"],[599,610,"ROLE"],[612,614,"ROLE"],[616,618,"ROLE"],[620,636,"ROLE"],[638,650,"ROLE"],[652,667,"ROLE"],[669,676,"ROLE"],[680,687,"ROLE"],[689,708,"ROLE"],[723,739,"ROLE"],[741,763,"ROLE"],[798,806,"ROLE"],[834,846,"ROLE"],[849,860,"ROLE"],[884,894,"ROLE"],[896,905,"ROLE"],[907,927,"ROLE"],[964,965,"DURATION"],[988,1007,"ROLE"],[1009,1027,"ORGANISATION"],[1030,1035,"LOCATION"],[1037,1046,"LOCATION"],[1048,1072,"DURATION"],[1089,1115,"EDUCATION"],[1163,1174,"EDUCATION"],[1175,1180,"LOCATION"],[1182,1203,"DURATION"],[1235,1240,"LOCATION"],[1242,1250,"DURATION"],[1286,1326,"INSTITUTION"],[1327,1332,"LOCATION"],[1688,1703,"SKILLS"],[1709,1718,"SKILLS"],[1724,1744,"SKILLS"]]}]]}