{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Rohit Divekar\r\nMumbai, Maharashtra\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Rohit-Divekar/2102781f0998dc47\r\n\r\nChemical engineer, experienced in chemical production, safety, sales and marketing of specialty \r\nchemicals. Currently working in chemical transportations and safety. Approaching pool of chemical \r\ncompanies for enroll for safer environment in logistics sector.\r\n\r\nPersonal Details\r\n\r\nDate of Birth: 1996-03-09\r\nEligible to work in: India\r\nHighest Career Level: 2-5 years experience\r\nIndustry: Chemical Engineering\r\nTotal years of experience: 3\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nSales & Marketing Manager\r\nLogistics Safety - Mumbai, Maharashtra\r\nFebruary 2020 to Present\r\n\r\nSales & Marketing Executive- 1 Year\r\nNandadeep Chemicals Pvt Ltd- Vashi, Navi Mumbai\r\n\r\nProduction Engineer- 1.5 Year\r\nRoyal Carbon Black Pvt Ltd- Patalganga MIDC, Rasayani\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nBachelor's in Chemical engineering\r\nBatu - Lonere\r\nMarch 2013 to March 2017\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Chemical logistics safety.\r\n\r\n• Sales-Marketing speciality chemicals\r\n\r\n• Industry safety.\r\n\r\n• Innovative\r\n\r\n• Complex problem solver\r\n\r\n• Service-focused\r\n\r\n• English\r\n\r\n\f• Business development\r\n\r\n• Management\r\n\r\n• Marketing\r\n\r\n• Microsoft Excel\r\n\r\n• Negotiation\r\n\r\n• Sales\r\n\r\n• Leadership\r\n\r\n• Hindi\r\n\r\nOnline Profile\r\n\r\nhttp://www.linkedin.com/in/rohit-divekar-4a1a5164\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[15,21,"LOCATION"],[23,34,"LOCATION"],[115,132,"ROLE"],[149,168,"SKILLS"],[448,453,"LOCATION"],[477,486,"DURATION"],[509,529,"ORGANISATION"],[558,559,"DURATION"],[582,587,"ROLE"],[590,625,"ROLE"],[628,634,"LOCATION"],[636,647,"LOCATION"],[649,673,"DURATION"],[677,705,"ROLE"],[714,742,"ORGANISATION"],[743,748,"LOCATION"],[750,761,"LOCATION"],[765,785,"ROLE"],[786,794,"LOCATION"],[796,823,"ORGANISATION"],[824,834,"LOCATION"],[841,849,"ORGANISATION"],[866,900,"EDUCATION"],[902,906,"LOCATION"],[909,915,"LOCATION"],[917,941,"DURATION"],[954,963,"SKILLS"],[969,995,"SKILLS"],[1001,1037,"SKILLS"],[1043,1059,"SKILLS"]]}]]}