{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["rajneesh suthar\r\nBanswara, Rajasthan\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/rajneesh-suthar/5f0fe69349783f39\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nnetwork marketing\r\nMicroTek - Banswara, Rajasthan\r\nFebruary 2020 to August 2021\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nHigher Secondary(12th Pass) in biology\r\nglobal collage badodiya - Banswara, Rajasthan\r\nNovember 2020 to Present\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• typing\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,15,"PERSON"],[17,25,"LOCATION"],[27,36,"LOCATION"],[138,155,"ROLE"],[157,165,"ORGANISATION"],[168,176,"LOCATION"],[178,187,"LOCATION"],[189,217,"DURATION"],[234,250,"EDUCATION"],[251,260,"EDUCATION"],[265,272,"EDUCATION"],[274,288,"INSTITUTION"],[289,297,"LOCATION"],[300,308,"LOCATION"],[310,319,"LOCATION"],[321,345,"DURATION"],[373,379,"SKILLS"]]}]]}