{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Rohan Sarfare\r\nRatnagiri, Maharashtra\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Rohan-Sarfare/f3bfec68264f6db8\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nMarketing\r\nNestle Pvt Ltd - Mumbai, Maharashtra\r\nJune 2019 to Present\r\n\r\n•\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nHigher Secondary(12th Pass) in Commerce\r\nUniversity of Mumbai - Mumbai, Maharashtra\r\nJanuary 2011 to February 2012\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\nsharing my skill ability.\r\n\r\n• Work and learn that contribute best for the growth of the organization by continue developing and\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[15,24,"LOCATION"],[26,37,"LOCATION"],[137,146,"ROLE"],[148,162,"ORGANISATION"],[165,171,"LOCATION"],[173,184,"LOCATION"],[186,206,"DURATION"],[228,244,"EDUCATION"],[245,254,"EDUCATION"],[259,279,"INSTITUTION"],[283,289,"LOCATION"],[292,298,"LOCATION"],[300,311,"LOCATION"],[313,342,"DURATION"],[355,364,"SKILLS"]]}]]}