{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Pantra Sravani\r\nBengaluru, Karnataka\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Pantra-Sravani/a3725cd6305926e7\r\n\r\nSecure a responsible career opportunity to fully utilize my training and skills, while making a significant\r\ncontribution to the success of the company.\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate to: Bengaluru, Karnataka\r\n\r\nPersonal Details\r\n\r\nDate of Birth: 1998-08-28\r\nEligible to work in: India\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nMarketing Executive\r\nCloud Collab Technologies - Bengaluru, Karnataka\r\nMarch 2021 to Present\r\n\r\nB2B marketing search,cold calling,team handling,scheduliy\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nComputer applications\r\nEMERALDS Degree College\r\n2015 to 2018\r\n\r\nEconomics, Commerce\r\nMANGAL Junior College\r\n2013 to 2015\r\n\r\nSSC\r\nVIJAYA English medium high school\r\n2013\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Accounting principles\r\n\r\n• Marketing techniques\r\n\r\n• Self confidence\r\n\r\n• Creative thinking\r\n\r\n• Hard working\r\n\r\n• Business development\r\n\r\n\f• Communication skills\r\n\r\n• Computer skills\r\n\r\n• Marketing\r\n\r\n• Microsoft Excel\r\n\r\n• English\r\n\r\nLanguages\r\n\r\n• English - Fluent\r\n• Kannada - Beginner\r\n• Telugu - Native\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[16,25,"LOCATION"],[27,36,"LOCATION"],[298,307,"LOCATION"],[309,318,"LOCATION"],[418,437,"ROLE"],[439,464,"ORGANISATION"],[467,476,"LOCATION"],[478,487,"LOCATION"],[489,510,"DURATION"],[514,534,"SKILLS"],[611,634,"INSTITUTION"],[636,648,"DURATION"],[673,694,"INSTITUTION"],[696,708,"DURATION"],[712,715,"EDUCATION"],[717,750,"INSTITUTION"],[811,820,"SKILLS"],[952,967,"SKILLS"],[973,982,"SKILLS"],[988,1003,"SKILLS"]]}]]}