{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Praveen Yalla\r\nHyderabad, Telangana\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Praveen-Yalla/9a24952b6d8326ca\r\n\r\n5.0 years’ experience in the IT industry as UI / UX / Interactive / Front-end developer. \r\nProficient in building Web User Interface (UI) using front-end technologies like HTML5, DHTML, CSS3,\r\nJavaScript, XML, DHTML, XHTML, jQuery, AJAX, JSON, Angular Material Design. \r\nExpertise in working with the JavaScript and various MVC JavaScript frameworks AngularJS, Angular 5\r\nand Dojo Toolkit. \r\nHave a strong hold in developing single-page applications (SPAs) using various JavaScript frameworks\r\nlike AngularJS, Angular 5.\r\n\r\n2015 - Present\r\nHTML 5, CSS3, basic javaScripting was every day of my job.\r\nCreating Responsive websites which sets in multiple devices.\r\nDesigning & Developing websites that are user-friendly, effective and appealing.\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nUI developer\r\nabhraInc - Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh\r\nDecember 2015 to Present\r\n\r\nUI developer\r\nIton Technologies - Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh\r\nMay 2013 to December 2015\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nBachelor of Science in Computer\r\nSri KrishnaDevaraya University\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Photoshop (3 years)\r\n\r\n• HTML5 & CSS3 (3 years)\r\n\r\n• javascript & jquery (2 years)\r\n\r\n• Bootstrap & Ajax (2 years)\r\n\r\n• AngularJS (2 years)\r\n\r\n\fOnline Profile\r\n\r\nhttp://praveen-yalla.github.io\r\n\r\nAdditional Information\r\n\r\nSkills \r\nHTML5 \r\nCSS3 \r\nJAVASCRIPT \r\nJQUERY \r\nBOOTSTRAP \r\nAJAX \r\nANGULARJS \r\nADOBE PHOTOSHOP \r\nANGULAR2\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[15,24,"LOCATION"],[26,35,"LOCATION"],[116,137,"DURATION"],[160,162,"ROLE"],[165,167,"ROLE"],[184,204,"ROLE"],[288,293,"SKILLS"],[295,300,"SKILLS"],[302,306,"SKILLS"],[309,319,"SKILLS"],[321,324,"SKILLS"],[326,331,"SKILLS"],[333,338,"SKILLS"],[340,346,"SKILLS"],[348,352,"SKILLS"],[354,358,"SKILLS"],[360,384,"SKILLS"],[440,465,"SKILLS"],[466,475,"SKILLS"],[477,486,"SKILLS"],[492,505,"SKILLS"],[615,624,"SKILLS"],[626,636,"SKILLS"],[640,654,"DURATION"],[656,662,"SKILLS"],[664,668,"SKILLS"],[914,926,"ROLE"],[939,948,"LOCATION"],[950,964,"LOCATION"],[966,990,"DURATION"],[994,1006,"ROLE"],[1008,1025,"ORGANISATION"],[1028,1037,"LOCATION"],[1039,1053,"LOCATION"],[1055,1080,"DURATION"],[1188,1197,"SKILLS"],[1213,1220,"SKILLS"],[1241,1260,"SKILLS"],[1276,1292,"SKILLS"],[1308,1317,"SKILLS"]]}]]}