{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["CURRICULUM-VITAE\r\n\r\nMOHAMMAD SAHABUDDIN\r\n\r\nMob:- +91-8574866998 ,+91-7271859326\r\nE-mail:-msahabu@gmail.com\r\n________________________________________________________________\r\n\r\nObjective:\r\n    \r\n \r\n                    \r\nHighly motivated professional looking forward to work on challenging and \r\ncreative research related assignments where I can apply my knowledge \r\nand experience in an organization which provides ample growth \r\nopportunities.\r\n\r\nProfessional Experience:\r\n\r\nSaudi Al-Terais Industrial Trading and Contracting Co.\r\nElectrical Engineer\r\n\r\nEmployer: \r\nDesignation:\r\nProject: Working in Ministry of Defence and Aviations projects \r\nDawadmi, Riyadh,K.S.A  \r\nDuration:        October 2014 - August 2016\r\n\r\nSaudi Al-Terais  Industrial Trading and Contracting Co.\r\nElectrical Engineer\r\n\r\nEmployer: \r\nDesignation:\r\nProject: Marafiq Blanket Project for upgrading electrical distribution \r\nnetwork Yanbu,\r\nDuration: May 2014 - September 2014\r\n\r\n \r\nEmployer: Saudi Oger Ltd., Riyadh, K.S.A\r\nDesignation: \r\nProject:\r\nRiyadh.\r\nDuration:  September 2011 - December 2012\r\n\r\nSenior Technician Medium Voltage Electrical\r\n\r\nPrincess Noura Bint Abdul Rahman University for Women, \r\n\r\nEmployer:         Saudi Oger Ltd., Riyadh, K.S.A\r\nDesignation:    Senior Technician Medium Voltage Electrical\r\nProject:             National Gaurd Battalions, Riyadh.\r\nDuration:          January 2013 - November 2013\r\n\r\nProfessional Summary: \r\n\r\n Worked as Senior Technician Medium Voltage Electrical in Saudi \r\n\r\n Electrical Senior Technician in Medium Voltage in Facilities \r\n\r\nOger Ltd., Riyadh, K.S.A.\r\n\r\nMaintenance Division.\r\n\r\n\fMonitoring and maintaining of Substations and Main Stations and \r\ntesting and commissioning as per electrical drawing and also \r\nincludes maintenance of transformers, switch gears, circuit \r\nbreakers, capacitor banks, and all protection devices.\r\n\r\n Studied on Power Plant Engineering which deals with Generation, \r\n\r\nTransmission, Distribution and Utilization of Power in three years as \r\nmain subjects during graduation.\r\n\r\n Design of Electrical Circuits and Constructions.\r\n Handling of Mini Projects and various seminars.\r\n Conducted various practical experiments and execution on Electrical\r\n\r\nsubjects.\r\n\r\nPrevious Experience:\r\n\r\n Working experience as a Service Engineer in \"Oasis Techno Engineers \r\n\r\nPrivate Limited\", Lucknow from 02-6-2010 to 16-02-2011.\r\n\r\n Working experience as a Site engineer in S.N. Construction Organization,\r\n\r\nLucknow from 01-08-2008  to 15-04-2010\r\n\r\nDuties & responsibilities:-\r\n\r\n Worked on SIEMENS's low and high voltage type breakers like 11kv, \r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n132kv, 220kv.\r\nInstallations, commissioning and maintenance of indoor and outdoor\r\ntype breakers like SF6 circuit breakers and VACUUM type circuit \r\nbreakers at various types of substations like UPPCL, N.T.P.C., BHEL, \r\nTELCO, JINDAL STEELS etc. \r\n\r\n Worked on testing of VCB & SF6 type circuit breakers through \r\n\r\nvarious type of electrical equipments like timing kit and CRM kit, \r\nand also provided technical assistance and resolution.\r\n\r\nAcademic Skills:-\r\n\r\n Bachelor of Technology from B.S.A college of Engineering and \r\n\r\nTechnology Mathura with specialization in Electrical Engineering \r\nwith 64% in the year 2008\r\nIntermediate from U.P. Board securing Ist Division with 63% in 2002\r\n\r\n\r\n High School from U.P. Board securing Ist Division with 64% in 2000\r\n\r\nPersonal skills:-\r\n\r\n Comprehensive problem solving abilities.\r\n Excellent verbal & written communication skills.\r\n Willingness to learn.\r\n A Dynamic go-better and quick learner with ability to work under \r\n\r\npressure and meet deadlines.\r\n\r\n Basic Knowledge of computer such as MS Office, Email, & Internet \r\n\r\netc.\r\n\r\nProject & Seminar:-\r\n\r\n\f A \"PC BASED DC STEPPER MOTOR CONTROLLER\" final year project.\r\n A Seminar presented on \"CIRCUIT BREAKERS\" at B.S.A.C.E.T, Mathura.\r\n\r\n\r\nTechnical training of 4 weeks in \"PCS TECHNOLOGY LIMITED\" in New \r\n\r\nTechnical Training:-\r\n\r\n\r\nDelhi.\r\n\r\nHobbies:\r\n -  \r\n \r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nWatching cricket, net surfing & listening Music.\r\n\r\nPersonal Detail:-\r\n\r\nFather's Name\r\nDate of Birth\r\nNationality\r\nGender\r\nMarital status\r\nKnown Languages\r\n\r\n: -\r\n: -\r\n\r\n: -\r\n: -\r\n\r\nIndian\r\n\r\nMohammad Shamsuddin\r\n25 August 1984\r\n: -\r\nMale\r\nSingle\r\n: -\r\n\r\nHindi, English\r\n\r\nmsahabu@gmail.com\r\n+91-8574866998\r\n\r\n:\r\n:\r\n+91-7271859326\r\n\r\nContacts:-\r\nE-mail\r\nMobile\r\n\r\nPermanent Address: -\r\n\r\nAddress\r\nLucknow (U.P)\r\n\r\nPassport Details:-\r\n\r\nPassport No\r\nDate of Issue\r\nDate of Expiry\r\nPlace of Issue\r\n\r\nDeclaration:\r\n\r\nPin code - 226012, India.\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\n H7248205\r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\n\r\n16-10-2009\r\n15-10-2019\r\nLucknow\r\n\r\n: -          L-128, Sector-E, L.D.A Colony Kanpur Road \r\n\r\nI hereby declare that the above written particulars are true to the best of \r\nmy knowledge and belief.\r\n\r\n                                                                                                  \r\n\r\n(MOHAMMAD SAHABUDDIN)\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[20,39,"PERSON"],[49,79,"CONTACT"],[88,106,"EMAIL"],[475,529,"ORGANISATION"],[531,562,"ROLE"],[600,619,"ORGANISATION"],[624,642,"PROJECTS"],[645,652,"LOCATION"],[654,660,"LOCATION"],[661,666,"LOCATION"],[687,713,"DURATION"],[717,772,"ORGANISATION"],[774,805,"ROLE"],[832,855,"PROJECTS"],[922,947,"DURATION"],[964,979,"ORGANISATION"],[981,987,"LOCATION"],[989,994,"LOCATION"],[1021,1028,"LOCATION"],[1041,1071,"DURATION"],[1199,1214,"ORGANISATION"],[1216,1222,"LOCATION"],[1224,1229,"LOCATION"],[1247,1264,"ROLE"],[1265,1299,"PROJECTS"],[1313,1338,"ORGANISATION"],[1340,1347,"LOCATION"],[1368,1396,"DURATION"],[1438,1455,"ROLE"],[1485,1490,"LOCATION"],[1497,1525,"ROLE"],[1562,1571,"ORGANISATION"],[1573,1579,"LOCATION"],[1581,1587,"LOCATION"],[1879,1902,"ROLE"],[2283,2299,"ROLE"],[2304,2346,"ORGANISATION"],[2349,2356,"LOCATION"],[2362,2386,"DURATION"],[2416,2429,"ROLE"],[2433,2463,"ORGANISATION"],[2468,2475,"LOCATION"],[2481,2506,"DURATION"],[2553,2560,"ORGANISATION"],[3085,3107,"EDUCATION"],[3113,3160,"INSTITUTION"],[3161,3168,"LOCATION"],[3192,3214,"ROLE"],[3320,3331,"EDUCATION"],[3337,3347,"EDUCATION"],[3742,3780,"PROJECTS"],[3781,3800,"PROJECTS"],[3827,3845,"PROJECTS"],[3910,3934,"ORGANISATION"],[4202,4221,"PERSON"],[4283,4300,"EMAIL"],[4302,4316,"CONTACT"],[4326,4340,"CONTACT"],[4580,4602,"DURATION"],[4883,4902,"PERSON"]]}]]}