{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Rajat Rajput\r\nMandawar, Rajasthan\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Rajat-Rajput/c6ff59dd84e20c72\r\n\r\nA challenging work in any reputed organization where my skills and knowledge \r\ncan be enhanced in conjunction with company goal and objectives that result in \r\nincreased profitability.\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nMarketing Executive\r\nProfessional Abridgement\r\nSeptember 2018 to Present\r\n\r\nWorking Ariya Westan UP And Uttarakhand)\r\nJob Responsibility\r\n➢ Create marketing strategies through planning and research on various factors\r\nsuch as pricing, competition, marketing research and customer preferences.\r\n➢ Coordinate sales and business initiatives and integrate sales processes across\r\nthe company in the allocated Territory.\r\n➢ Promotion of new plan and enhancements to the customers.\r\n\r\nSales Information and product training\r\n\r\n➢ Assist in managing all resources to prepare sales information and product\r\ntraining\r\nsuch as:\r\n1. Dealer Manuals\r\n2. Distributor Meeting\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nB.com\r\nM.J.P.R University Bareilly - Bareilly, Uttar Pradesh\r\n2018\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Problem analysis, use of judgment and ability to solve problems efficiently.\r\n\r\n• Tolerant and flexible to different situations.\r\n\r\n• Self motivated, initiative, high level of energy.\r\n\r\n• Willing to Planning and organizing. Expert Areas of function\r\n\r\n• Marketing & Sales\r\n\r\n• User Friendly with operating system's: Windows XP and Window 7.\r\n\r\n\f• Basic knowledge of MS Word, MS Excel.\r\n\r\n• Process driven approach in problem solving.\r\n\r\n• Good learner.\r\n\r\n• Ability to lead.\r\n\r\n• Business development\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[14,33,"LOCATION"],[330,365,"ROLE"],[367,392,"DURATION"],[404,416,"ORGANISATION"],[417,435,"LOCATION"],[996,1001,"EDUCATION"],[1003,1021,"INSTITUTION"],[1022,1056,"LOCATION"],[1058,1062,"DURATION"],[1345,1475,"SKILLS"],[1571,1591,"SKILLS"]]}]]}