{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["RITIK Singh\r\nRaniganj, West Bengal\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/RITIK-Singh/f0c4e5965e2daed5\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nMarketing Executive\r\nIndira ivf Hospital pvt ltd - Asansol, West Bengal\r\nDecember 2018 to Present\r\n\r\nMarketing Executive\r\nMaa durga silicate manufacturing - Kolkata, West Bengal\r\nOctober 2017 to December 2018\r\n\r\nFashion Assistant and cashier\r\nShopperstop pvt ltd\r\nJuly 2015 to June 2017\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nBSc\r\nB H U\r\n\r\nMBA\r\nWbut\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Marketing\r\n\r\n• Communication skills\r\n\r\n• Business development\r\n\r\nAwards / Achievements\r\n\r\nBest cashier award\r\nOctober 2016\r\n\r\nBest cashier award 2015 -2016\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,21,"PERSON"],[23,34,"LOCATION"],[165,184,"ROLE"],[186,213,"ORGANISATION"],[216,223,"LOCATION"],[225,236,"LOCATION"],[238,262,"DURATION"],[266,285,"ROLE"],[287,319,"ORGANISATION"],[322,329,"LOCATION"],[331,342,"LOCATION"],[344,373,"DURATION"],[377,394,"ROLE"],[399,406,"ROLE"],[408,427,"ORGANISATION"],[429,451,"DURATION"],[468,471,"EDUCATION"],[473,478,"INSTITUTION"],[482,485,"EDUCATION"],[487,501,"SKILLS"],[504,513,"SKILLS"],[519,528,"SKILLS"],[534,554,"SKILLS"]]}]]}