{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Richa Pandey\r\nWhat I Do\r\nBengaluru, Karnataka\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Richa-Pandey/181cdee873baecd1\r\n\r\nPlanning and Executing all digital marketing including SEO/SEM, Marketing \r\n \r\nDatabase, E-mail Marketing, Social Media Marketing, Etc. \r\n \r\nReviewing, Designing and building Social Media presence. \r\n \r\nMeasuring and reporting all marketing campaigns. \r\n \r\nAnalysing end to end customer experience across multiple channels.\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nDigital Marketing Executive\r\nRR Productions Pvt Ltd - Bengaluru, Karnataka\r\nJuly 2017 to March 2020\r\n\r\nHandling SEO/SEM.\r\nOnline marketing of new products and services.\r\n\r\nCompany Growth Analysis.\r\nDigital campaigns handling.\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nHigh school diploma\r\nHarvard Business School online\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Digital marketing\r\n\r\n• Social media marketing\r\n\r\n• SEO\r\n\r\n• Content Marketing\r\n\r\n• Social Media Management\r\n\r\n• Advertising\r\n\r\n• Content creation\r\n\r\n• Blogging\r\n\r\n• Customer service\r\n\r\n\f• Typing\r\n\r\n• Windows\r\n\r\n• Customer service\r\n\r\n• Customer service\r\n\r\n• Marketing\r\n\r\n• Google AdWords\r\n\r\n• SEM\r\n\r\n• Google Analytics\r\n\r\nLanguages\r\n\r\n• English - Fluent\r\n\r\nCertifications and Licenses\r\n\r\nDigital marketing\r\nSeptember 2021 to Present\r\n\r\nProject management\r\nSeptember 2021 to Present\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[25,34,"LOCATION"],[36,45,"LOCATION"],[152,169,"SKILLS"],[180,187,"SKILLS"],[189,212,"SKILLS"],[214,230,"SKILLS"],[232,254,"SKILLS"],[266,275,"SKILLS"],[277,286,"SKILLS"],[291,322,"SKILLS"],[471,498,"ROLE"],[500,522,"ORGANISATION"],[525,534,"LOCATION"],[536,545,"LOCATION"],[547,570,"DURATION"],[583,591,"SKILLS"],[593,609,"SKILLS"],[643,667,"SKILLS"],[669,686,"SKILLS"],[713,732,"EDUCATION"],[734,757,"INSTITUTION"],[792,809,"SKILLS"],[815,837,"SKILLS"],[843,846,"SKILLS"],[852,869,"SKILLS"],[875,898,"SKILLS"],[904,915,"SKILLS"],[921,937,"SKILLS"],[943,951,"SKILLS"],[957,973,"SKILLS"],[980,986,"SKILLS"],[992,999,"SKILLS"],[1005,1021,"SKILLS"],[1027,1043,"SKILLS"],[1049,1058,"SKILLS"],[1064,1078,"SKILLS"],[1084,1087,"SKILLS"],[1093,1122,"SKILLS"],[1179,1196,"CERTIFICATE"],[1198,1223,"DURATION"],[1227,1245,"CERTIFICATE"],[1247,1272,"DURATION"]]}]]}