{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[[" \r\nCURRICULUM VITAE\r\n \r\n\r\nMohammed Abdul Aleem\r\n\r\nPhone:+971502214594 \r\n+91-8142756756\r\n\r\nEmail: mohd.aleem4u7@gmail.com\r\n\r\nVisa Expiry: February 2018\r\n\r\nObjective\r\n\r\nSelf-motivated, analytical and meticulous candidate  interested in working for a progressive \r\norganization to enhance skillset and grow as an individual.\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\n Completed Bachelor Of Technology in  Computer Science and Engineering  from\r\nJNTUH (Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University, Hyderabad, India) in 2013.\r\n\r\n Completed Intermediate from Board of Intermediate Education (2007-2009).\r\n Completed Xth in 2007 from Atomic Energy Central School (CBSE).\r\n\r\nTechnical Skills\r\n\r\n Languages : C, C++, Java, SAP ABAP\r\n\r\n Web Design and Database Tools : HTML, MySql\r\n\r\n MS-Office: Microsoft Office Word, Microsoft Office Excel, Microsoft Office Power\r\n\r\n Operating System : Win2008,2012,XP,Win7,Win8,Win10\r\n\r\nPoint.\r\n\r\nCertifications\r\n\r\n Cisco Certified Network Associate ( CCNA )\r\n Cisco ID: CSCO13114882\r\n\r\n         Page 1 of 3\r\n\r\n\fProfessional Experience\r\n\r\nTotal Experience: 2 Years 8 months\r\n\r\nFebruary 2014 – January 2016 (1 Year 11 Months)\r\n\r\nSerco Pvt. Ltd. – Hyderabad \r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nJoined Serco Pvt. Ltd. as an Analyst in February 2014.\r\n\r\n Worked for “Google Maps” for various projects.\r\n\r\n Dealt   with   the   Floorplans   of   different   businesses   by   analysing   &   designing   the\r\n\r\nconstructive data to improve Google Maps from the backend.\r\n\r\n Worked for projects which deal in interior structure of the building as to be helpful for\r\n\r\nthe end users in getting routed through them.\r\n\r\nMarch 2016 – December 2016 (9 Months)\r\n\r\nCognizant Technology Solutions - Hyderabad\r\n\r\n Worked with Cognizant Technology Solutions as a Senior Process Executive.\r\n\r\n Dealt with different tasks regarding businesses from markets like UK, USA with the\r\n\r\nclient being “GOOGLE”.\r\n\r\nAmerican Markets.\r\n\r\n Database Synchronization  with  the search  criteria  for end  users  in  European  &\r\n\r\n Ability to Troubleshoot Connectivity issues whenever there were problems with the\r\n\r\nComputers being an active member in the Tech Support Team.\r\n\r\n Worked as Factual QC for few months to crosscheck & maintain quality of data.\r\n\r\nProfessional Achievements\r\n\r\n Awarded “STAR TRAINEE” at  GOOGLE India  for Best Performance among the\r\n\r\nbatch.\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nI had been a MENTOR for Airport Projects at client location.\r\n\r\nI had been awarded with “SPOTLIGHT” award at Cognizant Technology Solutions \r\nfor my Quality & Productive Performance in the company.\r\n\r\n         Page 2 of 3\r\n\r\n\f Ability to rapidly build relationship and set up trust.\r\n Confident and determined to achieve the goal.\r\n A systematic, organized and dedicated team player with an analytical bent of mind\r\n\r\ndetermined to be part of growth-oriented organization.\r\n Communicate effectively, learning new concepts quickly.\r\n Believe in hard work with smartness. \r\n\r\nPersonal Skills\r\n\r\nPersonal Details\r\n\r\nName\r\nNationality\r\nMarital Status\r\nLanguages Known :  English, Hindi, Telugu and Urdu.                            \r\n                    \r\n\r\n:  Mohammed Abdul Aleem\r\n:  Indian\r\n:  Single\r\n\r\n         Page 3 of 3\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[26,46,"PERSON"],[56,86,"CONTACT"],[97,120,"EMAIL"],[350,393,"EDUCATION"],[398,415,"EDUCATION"],[417,422,"INSTITUTION"],[424,465,"INSTITUTION"],[467,476,"LOCATION"],[478,483,"LOCATION"],[560,569,"DURATION"],[575,588,"EDUCATION"],[602,630,"INSTITUTION"],[632,636,"EDUCATION"],[676,677,"SKILLS"],[679,682,"SKILLS"],[684,688,"SKILLS"],[690,698,"SKILLS"],[736,740,"SKILLS"],[742,747,"SKILLS"],[753,762,"SKILLS"],[764,785,"SKILLS"],[787,809,"SKILLS"],[811,833,"SKILLS"],[923,956,"CERTIFICATE"],[1067,1081,"DURATION"],[1085,1113,"DURATION"],[1115,1131,"DURATION"],[1136,1151,"ORGANISATION"],[1154,1163,"LOCATION"],[1180,1195,"ORGANISATION"],[1202,1209,"ROLE"],[1244,1257,"ORGANISATION"],[1623,1631,"DURATION"],[1636,1666,"ORGANISATION"],[1669,1678,"LOCATION"],[1696,1726,"ORGANISATION"],[1732,1757,"ROLE"],[1829,1831,"LOCATION"],[1833,1836,"LOCATION"],[1862,1871,"ORGANISATION"],[2258,2272,"ROLE"],[2277,2289,"LOCATION"],[2454,2484,"ORGANISATION"],[3106,3126,"PERSON"]]}]]}