{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Rajkumar Sen\r\nRaisen, m.p, 462046, IN\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Rajkumar-Sen/0669a108796303b4\r\n\r\nTo learn and function effectively in an organization and be able to deliver to the bottom-line. To\r\nconstantly upgrade my knowledge and skills and make a difference in whatever I do.\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nWeb Developer's\r\nFull stack developer\r\nOnline shopping application with NODEJS with MONGODB.\r\n➢ Students registration form\r\n➢ Employee salary slip.\r\n➢ Students marks details\r\n➢ Students details\r\n➢ Validation form\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nBCA in ENGINEERING\r\nCAREER COLLEGE AT BHOPAL - Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh\r\n\r\n• HTML5, CSS3, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY, BOOTSTRAP, AJAX, NODEJS, MONGODB\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• PHP &MYSQL\r\n\r\n• MS OFFICE TRAINING & WORKING\r\n\r\n• 3 month training in NARSH IT TECHNOLOGY AT HYDERABAAD on the basis UI DEVELOPER.\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[14,20,"LOCATION"],[22,25,"LOCATION"],[355,370,"ROLE"],[372,392,"ROLE"],[394,421,"PROJECTS"],[427,433,"SKILLS"],[439,447,"SKILLS"],[584,602,"EDUCATION"],[604,628,"INSTITUTION"],[631,637,"LOCATION"],[639,653,"LOCATION"],[659,664,"SKILLS"],[666,670,"SKILLS"],[672,682,"SKILLS"],[684,690,"SKILLS"],[692,701,"SKILLS"],[703,707,"SKILLS"],[709,715,"SKILLS"],[717,724,"SKILLS"],[752,755,"SKILLS"],[757,762,"SKILLS"],[768,777,"SKILLS"],[802,809,"DURATION"],[822,841,"ORGANISATION"],[845,855,"LOCATION"],[869,881,"ROLE"]]}]]}