{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["DIVYANSHU KUMAR\r\n\r\nCashier with INDIA Experience\r\n\r\nD.O.B: 02/12/1995\r\n\r\nNationality: INDIAN\r\n\r\nCurrent Location:- Amritsar Punjab INDIA.\r\n\r\nMobile: +91 9915913668 & +91 8578998849\r\n\r\nEmail: kumardivyanshu30@gmail.com\r\n\r\nINDIAN Passport No:- R0280774\r\n\r\nOVERVIEW\r\n\r\nOver two year of cashier experience, maximized work opportunities to develop proactive and\r\ncourteous customer approach using good communication skills  mathematical aptitude and\r\ncomputer knowledge.\r\n\r\nSPECIALIZED SKILLS\r\n\r\nSound knowledge of cash management principle and account balance.\r\n\r\nMultitasking without losing focus.\r\n\r\nKnowledge of accounting, bookkeeping and mathematics for data entry assignment.  \r\n\r\nCoursework in bookkeeping.\r\n\r\nCan manage internal/external relation successfully.\r\n\r\nAble to work independently and under pressure.\r\n\r\nAble to do other duties as assigned.\r\n\r\nObjective\r\n\r\nSeeking a stable position in a reputed financial firm, so that I can use my experience and\r\nknowledge for mutual benefits and growth.\r\n\r\nResponsibilities and performance\r\n\r\nProcessed transaction quickly and efficiency, maintained a friendly and cordial relationship\r\nwith the customer by greeting them and assisting them with all relevant issues.\r\n\r\nCrated a friendly/positive impression at the checkout educated customers about new schemes \r\nand promotional activities that benefit them.\r\n\r\nMaintained register and all books related to cash transaction and kept them up to date.\r\n\r\n\fUpdated the database regularly by manually documenting all transaction in the register as \r\nwell as the Computer System.\r\n\r\nMonitored all the cash reserves and ensured adequate cash reserve in all station.  \r\n\r\nProvide customers with outstanding service and assisted them in solving their queries and \r\ndoubts. \r\n\r\nEDUCATION\r\n\r\nPatel College Hilsa Nalanda Bihar \r\nB. Sc SCIENCE Aug 2017.\r\n\r\nRoyal Computer Study Center Hilsa Bihar\r\nDCA + DTP + Tally Apr 2012.\r\n\r\nLANGUAGES\r\n\r\nEnglish - Excellent reading, writing and speaking.\r\n\r\nHindi - Excellent reading, writing and speaking.\r\n\r\nCOMPUTER PROGRAMMING SKILLS\r\n\r\nOperating Systems: Window 9X, Windows 2000, Window XP, Linux.\r\n\r\nGraphics Tools: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe PageMaker.\r\n\r\nOffice Package: Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft PowerPoint.\r\n\r\nOTHER INTERESTS\r\n\r\nBike Riding, Reading Motivational Story & Watching Horror Movie.\r\n\r\nREFERENCES: Available upon request\r\n\r\nDIVYANSHU KUMAR\r\n\r\nDate:\r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n(Sign)\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,15,"PERSON"],[19,26,"ROLE"],[149,163,"CONTACT"],[166,180,"CONTACT"],[191,217,"EMAIL"],[271,279,"DURATION"],[392,410,"SKILLS"],[510,525,"SKILLS"],[611,621,"SKILLS"],[655,665,"ROLE"],[1783,1796,"INSTITUTION"],[1797,1802,"LOCATION"],[1803,1810,"LOCATION"],[1811,1816,"LOCATION"],[1819,1824,"EDUCATION"],[1846,1873,"INSTITUTION"],[1874,1879,"LOCATION"],[1880,1885,"LOCATION"],[2385,2400,"PERSON"]]}]]}