{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Sandeep Singh\r\nBallia, Uttar Pradesh\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Sandeep-Singh/97fa348fa94a6c7a\r\n\r\nTo acquire a challenging career with a solid company utilizing the opportunity to offer proven and\r\ndeveloping skills within the company. \r\n \r\nPersonal Qualities \r\n● Strong leadership and motivational skills. \r\n● Ability to work in team as well as in group. \r\n● Ability to motivate other by speech.\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate to: Noida, Uttar Pradesh - Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh - Delhi, Delhi\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nWeb Developer\r\nDMD Solutions pvt ltd - Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh\r\nJuly 2021 to Present\r\n\r\nsoftware developer One of the most difficult parts in writing a resume is composing the descriptions of\r\nyour jobs, volunteer work, projects, and other relevant experiences. Each description of your work history\r\nand volunteer experience should be clear and concise, yet descriptive. After reading your description,\r\na  prospective  employer  should  know  exactly  what  your  responsibilities  were,  what  skills  you  have\r\ndeveloped, where your strengths lie, and what you have achieved\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nMca\r\nIntergal University Lucknow - Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh\r\n2021\r\n\r\nBCA\r\nAllhabad University\r\n2019\r\n\r\nDiploma\r\nHewett Polytechnic lucknow\r\n2016\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Technical Qualification \r\n\r\nLanguages/Scripts: PHP, CSS, HTML, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, MYSQL, CodeIgniter. \r\nSoftware: Eclipse, Notepad++, Atom, Vscode \r\nDatabases: MySQL \r\nOperating Systems: Windows XP / 7/10\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,21,"PERSON"],[23,36,"LOCATION"],[443,448,"LOCATION"],[450,463,"LOCATION"],[466,473,"LOCATION"],[475,488,"LOCATION"],[491,496,"LOCATION"],[498,503,"LOCATION"],[526,539,"ROLE"],[541,562,"ORGANISATION"],[565,572,"LOCATION"],[574,587,"LOCATION"],[589,609,"DURATION"],[613,631,"ROLE"],[1121,1145,"INSTITUTION"],[1146,1153,"LOCATION"],[1156,1163,"LOCATION"],[1165,1178,"LOCATION"],[1188,1191,"EDUCATION"],[1193,1212,"INSTITUTION"],[1222,1229,"EDUCATION"],[1231,1249,"INSTITUTION"],[1250,1257,"LOCATION"],[1338,1341,"SKILLS"],[1343,1346,"SKILLS"],[1348,1352,"SKILLS"],[1354,1364,"SKILLS"],[1364,1372,"SKILLS"],[1374,1383,"SKILLS"],[1385,1390,"SKILLS"],[1392,1404,"SKILLS"],[1437,1441,"SKILLS"],[1463,1468,"SKILLS"]]}]]}