{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Pradeep U\r\nVijayawada, Andhra Pradesh\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Pradeep-U/bdaa252873a5cd2b\r\n\r\n• Having 2.0 years of experience as Python developer. \r\n• Experience in building REST APIs, API design and development using Django \r\nframework. \r\n• Experience in Front end development with HTML and CSS. \r\n• Experience in Database technologies like PostgreSQL, and MYSQL \r\n• Hands on experience on using python modules (Numpy, Scipy, Pandas and \r\nMatplotlib). \r\n• Committed, goal oriented, & learns new things & technologies. \r\n• Ability to handle multiple tasks and assignments concurrently in cross-functional teams \r\nand a flexible team player able to communicate with all levels of personnel.\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nPython Developer\r\nTech Mahindra - Bengaluru, Karnataka\r\nFebruary 2020 to Present\r\n\r\nTech Mahindra. Python Developer (Feb 2020 to till date)\r\nClient: Carzone\r\n\r\nDescription:\r\nThis application is developed for a Carzone company where company wants to lift the cars and website\r\nand allow the user to visit the site and browse through all of its latest cars and features. And\r\nuser  can  buy  or  sell  a  used  car,  at  this  point  user  can  specify  the  feature's  using  filters  and  get  the\r\ninformation about required car through email.\r\n\r\nRoles & Responsibilities:\r\n• Involved in developing carzone application for Carzone.\r\n• Installed &Configured MySQL database Connections.\r\n• Involved in creating models, views and templates for the assigned modules.\r\n• Written Rest-API's using Django-rest framework.\r\n• Actively involved in writing Unit Test cases.\r\n• Involved in code reviews and review meetings.\r\n• Developed and modified python code to make new enhancements or resolve problems,\r\nas per client requirement.\r\n\r\nEnvironment: Python, Django, Django-Rest, PostgreSQL, HTML, CSS, GIT, GITHUB.\r\n\r\nDeclaration:\r\n\r\nI hereby declare that the information furnished above is true and correct to the best of my\r\nKnowledge. I bear the responsibility for any liabilities with the provided information.\r\n\r\n\fBachelor of Technology in Mechanical Engineering in Mechanical Engineering\r\nJNT University Anantapur - Anantapur, Andhra Pradesh\r\n\r\nPRADEEP UPPULURI\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Languages\r\n\r\n• Python\r\n\r\n• Frameworks\r\n\r\n• Django, Visual studio\r\n\r\n• Web Technologies\r\n\r\n• HTML, CSS, JSON, XML.\r\n\r\n• SCM and Tools\r\n\r\n• Git, GitHub\r\n\r\n• Technical Tools\r\n\r\n• PyCharm, JIRA\r\n\r\n• Database\r\n\r\n• MySQL, PostgreSQL\r\n\r\n• Operating Systems\r\n\r\n• Windows\r\n\r\n• MySQL\r\n\r\n• Django\r\n\r\n• HTML5\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,21,"PERSON"],[23,37,"LOCATION"],[123,132,"DURATION"],[150,167,"ROLE"],[186,204,"SKILLS"],[206,216,"SKILLS"],[221,258,"SKILLS"],[277,286,"SKILLS"],[304,308,"SKILLS"],[313,317,"SKILLS"],[363,373,"SKILLS"],[379,384,"SKILLS"],[418,432,"SKILLS"],[434,439,"SKILLS"],[441,446,"SKILLS"],[448,454,"SKILLS"],[461,471,"SKILLS"],[733,749,"ROLE"],[751,764,"ORGANISATION"],[767,776,"LOCATION"],[778,787,"LOCATION"],[789,813,"DURATION"],[817,831,"ORGANISATION"],[832,848,"ROLE"],[850,871,"DURATION"],[882,889,"ORGANISATION"],[943,950,"ORGANISATION"],[1774,1780,"SKILLS"],[1782,1788,"SKILLS"],[1790,1801,"SKILLS"],[1803,1813,"SKILLS"],[1815,1819,"SKILLS"],[1821,1824,"SKILLS"],[1826,1829,"SKILLS"],[1831,1838,"SKILLS"],[2043,2091,"EDUCATION"],[2095,2117,"EDUCATION"],[2119,2143,"INSTITUTION"],[2146,2155,"LOCATION"],[2157,2171,"LOCATION"],[2175,2191,"PERSON"]]}]]}