{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Sagar Babu Gundala\r\nGuntur, Andhra Pradesh\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Sagar-Babu-Gundala/c25398cef50a97db\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nQlik Developer\r\nLTI - Larsen & Toubro Infotech - Pune, Maharashtra\r\nMay 2021 to January 2022\r\n\r\nQlik Developer with CM\r\nSeptember 2017 to May 2021\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nMaster's in MBA\r\nJNTU-K - Rajahmundry, Andhra Pradesh\r\nJune 2013 to January 2016\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Business Intelligence Tools: QlikView, Qlik Sense (4 years)\r\n\r\n• Data Base: Oracle 11g, Sql Server\r\n\r\n• Operating Systems: Windows XP, Windows 07,\r\n\r\n• Languages: C, C++, Core Java\r\n\r\n• Domains: Retail, Pharma, Pinance on the cloud\r\n\r\n• Qlikview Developer\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,18,"PERSON"],[20,26,"LOCATION"],[28,42,"LOCATION"],[147,161,"ROLE"],[163,193,"ORGANISATION"],[196,200,"LOCATION"],[202,213,"LOCATION"],[215,239,"DURATION"],[243,257,"ROLE"],[263,265,"ORGANISATION"],[267,293,"DURATION"],[310,325,"EDUCATION"],[327,333,"INSTITUTION"],[336,347,"LOCATION"],[349,363,"LOCATION"],[365,390,"DURATION"],[403,412,"SKILLS"],[447,455,"SKILLS"],[457,461,"SKILLS"],[494,504,"SKILLS"],[506,516,"SKILLS"],[581,582,"SKILLS"],[582,587,"SKILLS"],[589,598,"SKILLS"]]}]]}