{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["NOORJAHAN K.V.\r\nEdappal - Kerala\r\nMOB NO: +919526010304, +919656014518\r\nEmail : noorjahankv26523@gmail.com\r\n\r\n \r\n\r\nCourse /\r\nGraduation\r\n\r\nBTECH\r\n\r\n+2\r\n\r\n10th\r\n\r\nUniversity or College\r\n\r\nYear\r\n\r\nStream\r\n\r\npercentage\r\n\r\nRoyal College of \r\nEngineering and \r\nTechnology, Akkikavu.\r\nCalicut University\r\n\r\nISS Higher Secondary\r\nSchool -Ponnani\r\n\r\n2013-2017\r\n\r\nElectronics and\r\nCommunication\r\nEngineering\r\n\r\n2011-2013\r\n\r\nscience\r\n\r\nISS Higher Secondary\r\nSchool -Ponnani\r\n\r\n2010-2011\r\n\r\n70%\r\n\r\n86%\r\n\r\n99%\r\n\r\nCareer Objective\r\n\r\nTo associate with an innovative and vibrant organization, this allows me to put my competencies to the\r\nbest use, to add value to the organization and contributes to my overall growth as an individual. Looking\r\nforward for an opportunity to utilize my skills and abilities that offer sensitivity and professional growth\r\nwhile being resourceful, innovative and flexible and there by uplift my carrier.\r\n\r\nProfessional  Qualification\r\n\r\nComputer Proficiency\r\n\r\n    MS OFFICE & WINDOWS.\r\n\r\n    Internet & E-Mail Operations\r\n\r\n\fPersonal Skills & Strengths:\r\n\r\n Belief in continuous learning.\r\n\r\n Innovative outlook.\r\n\r\n High energy levels and self-motivated\r\n\r\n Open to new ideas and environment \r\n\r\n Team Spirit \r\n\r\nLanguages Known:\r\n\r\nEnglish\r\n\r\n       Malayalam\r\n\r\n       Hindi\r\n\r\n       \r\n\r\n       \r\n\r\nPersonal Details:\r\n\r\nInterest and Hobbies:\r\n\r\n Designing \r\n Browsing.\r\n Keeping Fit. \r\n Travelling\r\n\r\nDeclaration\r\n\r\n  NOORJAHAN K.V.\r\n\r\n  Date: 25-07-2017\r\n\r\n Date of Birth\r\n Marital Status\r\n Nationality\r\n Current Location\r\n\r\n: 29/08/1995\r\n: Married\r\n: Indian\r\n: Malappuram(D) -Kerala.\r\n\r\nI hereby declare that the above furnished details are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.\r\n\r\n  Place: Edappal                                                                                                      \r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,23,"PERSON"],[42,55,"CONTACT"],[57,70,"CONTACT"],[80,106,"EMAIL"],[139,144,"EDUCATION"],[148,158,"EDUCATION"],[219,266,"INSTITUTION"],[268,277,"LOCATION"],[279,286,"LOCATION"],[301,329,"INSTITUTION"],[330,338,"LOCATION"],[342,351,"DURATION"],[355,398,"EDUCATION"],[402,411,"DURATION"],[426,454,"INSTITUTION"],[455,463,"LOCATION"],[467,476,"DURATION"],[1603,1613,"PERSON"],[1617,1625,"LOCATION"],[1740,1747,"LOCATION"]]}]]}