{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Pradeep Bhilare\r\nMumbai, Maharashtra\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Pradeep-Bhilare/d7178201bcb942b8\r\n\r\nPersonal Details\r\n\r\nDate of Birth: 1991-03-13\r\nHighest Career Level: 5+ years experience\r\nIndustry: Banking & Finance, Software Development, Technology\r\nTotal years of experience: 5\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nSoftware Developer\r\nNCR Corporation India Pvt Ltd - Mumbai, Maharashtra\r\nSeptember 2018 to July 2021\r\n\r\nBanking domain\r\n\r\nSoftware Developer\r\nPibm\r\nNovember 2015 to August 2018\r\n\r\nWork on 7 website with managing database and new client requirements.\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nMaster's in Master Computer Application\r\nBvimit - Mumbai, Maharashtra\r\nJune 2013 to April 2015\r\n\r\nHigher Secondary(12th Pass) in Science\r\nN. G. Acharya & D. K. Marathe College - Mumbai, Maharashtra\r\nJune 2009 to April 2012\r\n\r\nBachelor's in B.sc(IT)\r\nOes - Sanpada, Navi Mumbai, Maharashtra\r\nJune 2009 to April 2012\r\n\r\n• Hi, i have 5.6 year's of experience in asp.net, sql server 2012, crystal reports, Javascript, Jquery.\r\n\r\nBasics knowledge about mvc, angular 4, asp.net 4.5 above. I am looking for job in Mumbai expect\r\nCTC is 5.9 lac (5.6 years) (5 years)\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• .NET (6 years)\r\n\r\n• SQL (6 years)\r\n\r\n\f• Javascript (4 years)\r\n\r\n• Agile\r\n\r\nLanguages\r\n\r\n• Marathi - Fluent\r\n• English - Fluent\r\n• Hindi - Fluent\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,15,"PERSON"],[17,23,"LOCATION"],[25,36,"LOCATION"],[188,196,"DURATION"],[219,236,"ROLE"],[238,258,"ROLE"],[323,341,"ROLE"],[343,372,"ORGANISATION"],[375,381,"LOCATION"],[383,394,"LOCATION"],[396,423,"DURATION"],[445,463,"ROLE"],[471,499,"DURATION"],[601,628,"EDUCATION"],[630,636,"ORGANISATION"],[639,645,"LOCATION"],[647,658,"LOCATION"],[660,683,"DURATION"],[687,703,"EDUCATION"],[704,713,"EDUCATION"],[718,725,"EDUCATION"],[727,764,"INSTITUTION"],[767,773,"LOCATION"],[775,786,"LOCATION"],[788,811,"DURATION"],[815,833,"EDUCATION"],[834,836,"EDUCATION"],[845,852,"LOCATION"],[854,865,"LOCATION"],[867,878,"LOCATION"],[880,903,"DURATION"],[920,930,"DURATION"],[948,955,"SKILLS"],[957,972,"SKILLS"],[991,1001,"SKILLS"],[1003,1010,"SKILLS"],[1037,1040,"SKILLS"],[1042,1051,"SKILLS"],[1053,1064,"SKILLS"],[1096,1102,"LOCATION"],[1175,1179,"SKILLS"],[1195,1198,"SKILLS"],[1215,1225,"SKILLS"]]}]]}