{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["CURRICULUM VITAE\r\n\r\nVASIM ASIF.S\r\nEmail      :vasim.civil50@gmail.com\r\nMobile    : +91-9941065341 \r\nSkype id : Sadiqbasha360             \r\n\r\n                \r\n\r\nCAREER OBJECTIVE :\r\n\r\nTo make my knowledge pave a way for success to the work that is my \r\n\r\nresponsibility.\r\n\r\nWORK EXPERIENCE :\r\n\r\nTOTAL SITE EXPERIENCE  –  4  Years\r\n\r\nFeb 2015 - Till date\r\n\r\n     Organization\r\n     Designation\r\n     Project title\r\n                                                      (Residential 11 floors,128 apartments)\r\n     Location                \r\n\r\n        :  ETA  CONSTRUCTIONS (I) LTD\r\n        :  ASSISTANT  ENGINEER\r\n        :  ETA STAR Verde\r\n\r\n        :  Valasaravakkam,Chennai\r\n\r\n        \r\n      \r\n\r\n.                                                                   \r\n\r\n            Nov 2013 – Jan 2015\r\n\r\n     Organization                 \r\n     Designation\r\n     Project                       \r\n     Location                      \r\n                                       \r\n\r\n        :    SS  CONSTRUCTIONS\r\n        :   SITE ENGINEER  \r\n        :   residential building (G+2), villa\r\n        :   Medavakkam, kottivakkam,\r\n            Kovalam, Chennai.\r\n\r\nJOB RESPONSIBILITIES :\r\n\r\n Responsible for project execution and completion of project as per specification.    \r\n Responsibilities also include review of construction drawings, preparation of \r\n\r\nweekly    &    daily Progress reports.\r\n\r\n Prepararion of bar bending schedule,sub contractor’s bills, Review of quality \r\n\r\ncontrol plans.\r\n\r\n Attending weekly progress review meetings with client and Inspection and \r\n\r\nacceptance of materials supplied by contractors.\r\n Maintaining quality standards for all structural works.\r\n Setting out the works in accordance with the drawings and specifications.\r\n Checking materials and work in progress for compliance with the specified \r\n\r\nrequirements.\r\n\r\n\f Observance of safty requirements.\r\n Preparing record drawings, technical reports, site diary.\r\n Managing all the finishing works till handing over of flats to clients.\r\n Achieving construction activities like Shuttering ,Reinforcement , RCC ,Masonry \r\n\r\nfor Blockwork, Plastering ,Tile laying ,Door shutter fixing and Waterproofing upto \r\ncompletion.Independently following up with design engineers of Architectures and \r\nStructural updated drawing for minor changes, as per site requirement needed.\r\n\r\nCAREER INTEREST :\r\n\r\nSite Engineer\r\n\r\n QA/QC Engineer\r\n\r\nEDUCATION :\r\n\r\nCourse &\r\nYear\r\n\r\nInstitution\r\n\r\nUniversity/\r\nBoard\r\n\r\nYear Of\r\nCompletion\r\n\r\nPercentage\r\n\r\nB.E\r\n          (Civil)\r\n\r\nBalaji institute of Engg. &\r\ntechnology, Chennai.\r\n\r\nAnna University\r\n\r\n2013\r\n\r\n6.8\r\n(CGPA)\r\n\r\nHigher\r\nSecondary\r\n\r\nCorporation higher sec. school,\r\nthiruvanmiyur ,\r\nChennai.\r\n\r\nState board \r\n\r\n2009\r\n\r\n71.2 \r\n\r\nSSLC\r\n\r\nState board\r\n\r\n2007\r\n\r\nGovt. higher Secondary\r\nSchool, Palavakkam,\r\nChennai.\r\n\r\n         \r\n          75.5\r\n\r\nTECHNICAL SKILLS :\r\n\r\n Residential construction supervision and inspection\r\n\r\n Preparation of sub contractor and sub agencies work schedule on weekly basis. \r\n\r\nImplementation of QA/QC programs.\r\n\r\nSOFTWARE SKILLS :\r\n\r\n AutoCAD\r\n Ms office \r\n\r\n\fPROFESSIONAL STRENGTH: \r\n\r\n Team Lead\r\n Self confidence\r\n\r\nPERSONAL DETAILS :\r\n\r\n Date of Birth                     \r\n Gender                                \r\n Marital Status                    \r\n Nationality                          \r\n Religion                               \r\n Languages known              \r\n Passport no                          \r\n Place of Issue                       \r\n Date of Issue                        \r\n Date of Expiry                     \r\n Permanent Address\r\n\r\n                     \r\n\r\n                                                      \r\n                                                      \r\n\r\nDECLARATION:\r\n\r\n06-august-1991\r\nMale\r\nSingle\r\nIndian\r\nMuslim\r\nEnglish, Tamil, Hindi,Urdu\r\nM4105074\r\nCHENNAI\r\n03/12/2014\r\n02/12/2024\r\n2/476 ,plot no 110\r\n5th singaravelan street,\r\nChinna neelankarai,\r\nChennai-600 117\r\n\r\nI hereby declare that all the above details furnished are true and correct  to the best of my \r\nknowledge.\r\n\r\nPlace:   Chennai\r\nDate:\r\n\r\n                                                                                                          (VASIM ASIF)\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[20,32,"PERSON"],[46,69,"EMAIL"],[83,97,"CONTACT"],[551,569,"ORGANISATION"],[590,609,"ROLE"],[651,665,"LOCATION"],[666,673,"LOCATION"],[781,800,"DURATION"],[988,1005,"ORGANISATION"],[1019,1032,"ROLE"],[1095,1105,"LOCATION"],[1107,1118,"LOCATION"],[1133,1140,"LOCATION"],[1142,1150,"LOCATION"],[2389,2402,"ROLE"],[2534,2555,"EDUCATION"],[2560,2599,"INSTITUTION"],[2601,2609,"LOCATION"],[2613,2628,"INSTITUTION"],[2655,2706,"INSTITUTION"],[2709,2722,"LOCATION"],[2726,2734,"LOCATION"],[3980,3995,"LOCATION"],[4118,4125,"LOCATION"],[4243,4253,"PERSON"]]}]]}