{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["rohit verma\r\nAgra, Uttar Pradesh\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/rohit-verma/26ff4c5495e07091\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nMarketing\r\nHavells India Limited - Agra, Uttar Pradesh\r\nMarch 2016 to Present\r\n\r\nResponsibilities\r\nsearch job for any side\r\n\r\nAccomplishments\r\ni want to job\r\n\r\nSkills Used\r\nmarketing\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nb.b.a in marketing\r\nuttam institute - Agra, OK\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[13,17,"LOCATION"],[19,32,"LOCATION"],[130,139,"ROLE"],[141,162,"ORGANISATION"],[165,169,"LOCATION"],[171,184,"LOCATION"],[186,207,"DURATION"],[329,347,"EDUCATION"],[349,364,"INSTITUTION"],[367,371,"LOCATION"]]}]]}