{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Sandip Palave\r\nDigital Marketing and Business Development\r\nNashik, Maharashtra\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Sandip-Palave/943c717ad0370d55\r\n\r\nHighest Career Level: Fresher\r\nIndustry: Advertising, PR, MR, Event Management, Internet, Ecommerce, Management, Marketing,\r\nMedia & Communications, Sales\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\r\n\r\nPersonal Details\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nDigital Marketing\r\nSelf-practice\r\nSeptember 2021 to Present\r\n\r\nAs a student..\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nBachelor's in Physics\r\nFergusson College, Pune - Pune, Maharashtra\r\nJuly 2017 to February 2020\r\n\r\nHigher Secondary(12th Pass) in Science\r\nVainateya Jr. College of Science, Niphad - Niphad, Maharashtra\r\nMay 2016 to June 2017\r\n\r\nSecondary(10th Pass)\r\nVainateya Vidyalaya, Niphad - Niphad, Maharashtra\r\nMay 2014 to June 2015\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Digital Marketing (1 year)\r\n\r\n• Marketing Management (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• Social Media Marketing (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• Business Development (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• Business Management (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• Marketing\r\n\r\n\f• Google AdWords\r\n\r\n• SEO\r\n\r\n• SEM\r\n\r\n• Google Analytics\r\n\r\n• Email marketing\r\n\r\nOnline Profile\r\n\r\nhttps://www.linkedin.com/in/sandip-palave\r\n\r\nCertifications and Licenses\r\n\r\nDigital Marketing\r\nDecember 2021 to Present\r\n\r\nData Science with Python\r\nApril 2021 to Present\r\n\r\nDigital Marketing\r\nOctober 2019 to Present\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[15,32,"ROLE"],[37,57,"ROLE"],[59,65,"LOCATION"],[67,78,"LOCATION"],[200,211,"LOCATION"],[213,215,"LOCATION"],[217,219,"LOCATION"],[221,237,"LOCATION"],[272,281,"LOCATION"],[284,306,"LOCATION"],[308,313,"LOCATION"],[389,406,"ROLE"],[423,448,"DURATION"],[483,504,"EDUCATION"],[506,523,"INSTITUTION"],[525,529,"LOCATION"],[532,536,"LOCATION"],[538,549,"LOCATION"],[551,577,"DURATION"],[581,597,"EDUCATION"],[598,619,"EDUCATION"],[621,653,"INSTITUTION"],[655,661,"LOCATION"],[664,670,"LOCATION"],[672,683,"LOCATION"],[685,706,"DURATION"],[710,729,"EDUCATION"],[732,751,"INSTITUTION"],[753,759,"LOCATION"],[762,768,"LOCATION"],[770,781,"LOCATION"],[787,804,"DURATION"],[817,826,"SKILLS"],[832,849,"SKILLS"],[864,884,"SKILLS"],[909,931,"SKILLS"],[956,976,"SKILLS"],[1001,1020,"SKILLS"],[1045,1054,"SKILLS"],[1099,1115,"SKILLS"],[1234,1251,"CERTIFICATE"],[1253,1277,"DURATION"],[1281,1305,"CERTIFICATE"],[1307,1328,"DURATION"],[1332,1349,"CERTIFICATE"],[1351,1374,"DURATION"]]}]]}