{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Rafiq Ahmed\r\nHyderabad, Telangana\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Rafiq-Ahmed/990e2e8f335bf550\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\r\n\r\nPersonal Details\r\n\r\nDate of Birth: 1972-01-01\r\nEligible to work in: India\r\nHighest Career Level: 5+ years experience\r\nIndustry: Architecture, Interior Design, Arts & Entertainment, Marketing, Retail, Sales\r\nTotal years of experience: 10\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nSales & Marketing\r\nDezign India Interiors - Hyderabad, Telangana\r\nJanuary 2008 to Present\r\n\r\nI have worked as a Marketing Executive previously for Zuari Furniture\r\nat  \"Saidutta  Enterprises\"  Hyderabad  for  4  Years  from  2003  to  2007  in  Twin  Cities  Hyderabad  and\r\nSecunderabad dealing with 170 dealers regularly.\r\n\r\nI am doing my own Business \"Dezign India\" in Interiors Field taking up small and Big Interior projects\r\nfrom 2008 and stiil on.\r\n\r\nBut due to Corona effect I have gone through hard times and Now I am in need of my Eligible job and I\r\nassure that I will fully serve and give my Best for the development of the Company whichever I join.\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nBachelor's in Biology\r\nSilver Jubilee College - Kurnool, Andhra Pradesh\r\nJune 1990 to April 1993\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Computer skills\r\n\r\n• Marketing\r\n\r\n• Sales\r\n\r\n• Communication skills\r\n\r\n• Adobe Photoshop\r\n\r\n\f• Salesforce\r\n\r\n• Business Development\r\n\r\n• Digital Marketing\r\n\r\nLanguages\r\n\r\n• English, Telugu, Hindi, Urdu - Fluent\r\n\r\nAdditional Information\r\n\r\nBeyond sales and Marketing I am a Story and Screenplay Writer, \r\nSinger, Composer, and Film Maker. \r\nAnd also I am a Graphic Designer ( Photoshop ) and \r\nVideo Editor ( Premiere Pro ).\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,22,"PERSON"],[24,33,"LOCATION"],[273,350,"ROLE"],[412,445,"ORGANISATION"],[448,468,"LOCATION"],[470,493,"DURATION"],[516,535,"ROLE"],[572,595,"ORGANISATION"],[597,606,"LOCATION"],[629,643,"DURATION"],[663,691,"LOCATION"],[758,772,"ORGANISATION"],[840,858,"DURATION"],[1069,1103,"EDUCATION"],[1105,1127,"INSTITUTION"],[1128,1153,"LOCATION"],[1155,1178,"DURATION"],[1206,1360,"SKILLS"],[1563,1612,"ROLE"]]}]]}