{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Rahul Kumar\r\nReact developer\r\nPatna, Bihar\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Rahul-Kumar/6e385bce84dca632\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\r\n\r\nPersonal Details\r\n\r\nDate of Birth: 1997-02-19\r\nEligible to work in: India\r\nHighest Career Level: Fresher\r\nIndustry: Software Development\r\nTotal years of experience: 0\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nReactJS Developer\r\nReact js developer\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nBachelor's in Bca\r\nM.P.S science College muzaffarpur bihar - Muzaffarpur, Bihar\r\nAugust 2016 to January 2020\r\n\r\nHigher Secondary(12th Pass) in Isc\r\nSanjay Singh 10+2 College Bihar - Bihar\r\nAugust 2014 to March 2016\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• JavaScript (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• HTML5 (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• React js (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• Bootstrap 4 (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• Material Ui (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• Java\r\n\r\nLanguages\r\n\r\n• Hindi, English, Bhojpuri - Intermediate\r\n\r\n\fCertifications and Licenses\r\n\r\nFront end development course\r\nMarch 2021 to June 2021\r\n\r\nBesant technologies btm layout Bangalore Karnataka\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[13,28,"ROLE"],[30,42,"LOCATION"],[270,290,"ROLE"],[343,380,"ROLE"],[397,414,"EDUCATION"],[416,437,"INSTITUTION"],[438,476,"LOCATION"],[478,505,"DURATION"],[509,536,"EDUCATION"],[540,570,"INSTITUTION"],[571,584,"LOCATION"],[586,611,"DURATION"],[637,813,"SKILLS"],[859,935,"EDUCATION"],[937,960,"DURATION"],[964,983,"ORGANISATION"],[995,1014,"LOCATION"]]}]]}