{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Priya Mane\r\nAurangabad, Maharashtra\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Priya-Mane/fc65ec69458383b9\r\n\r\nmanepriya222019@gmail.com\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nSoftware Developer\r\nIdentity Card Generation Software\r\nJuly 2019 to Present\r\n\r\nEnvironment: Java\r\nDatabase: MySQL\r\nIDE: Eclipse\r\nDescription: The objective of project is to develop identity card which is having a uniquebarcode\r\nnumber that can be for identification.\r\n\r\nResponsibilities: • Responsible for coding and developing using Core Java.\r\n• Writing hibernate mapping files and maintain database.\r\n• Designing Controller, Service and DAO specific Java Classes.\r\n\r\nMINI PROJECTS DETAILS\r\nProject Title: Building an Online College Library Website\r\nFront-end: HTML, CSS\r\nBack-end: JavaScript\r\nDiscription: The objective of project is t o first Create a Student Account and after Loging in. the Student\r\nselects number of books of his\r\nchoice and then collects the information of the selected books\r\n\r\nPERSONAL DETAIL\r\n\r\nDate of Birth 22 july 1997\r\n\r\nGender Female\r\nMarital Status Married\r\nNationality Indian\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nBachelor of Engineering in Information Technology\r\nGovernment College Of Engineering Aurangabad - Aurangabad, Maharashtra\r\n2019\r\n\r\nDIPLOMA in Technology\r\nInformation Government Polytechnic - Mumbai, Maharashtra\r\n\r\n\f2016\r\n\r\nS.S.C in Latur Board\r\nState Board\r\n2013\r\n\r\nBE in Technology\r\nGovernment College - Aurangabad, Maharashtra\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Technical Skills: C, Java, Javascript \r\n\r\n \r\nIDE: Turbo C, Eclipse, VS Code \r\n \r\nWeb Technology: HTML, CSS\r\n\r\n• C\r\n\r\n• Java\r\n\r\n• SQL\r\n\r\n• JavaScript\r\n\r\n• Java\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,10,"PERSON"],[12,22,"LOCATION"],[24,35,"LOCATION"],[113,138,"EMAIL"],[161,179,"ROLE"],[181,214,"PROJECTS"],[216,236,"DURATION"],[253,257,"SKILLS"],[269,274,"SKILLS"],[681,711,"PROJECTS"],[724,728,"SKILLS"],[730,733,"SKILLS"],[745,755,"SKILLS"],[1075,1111,"EDUCATION"],[1115,1137,"EDUCATION"],[1139,1172,"INSTITUTION"],[1173,1183,"LOCATION"],[1186,1196,"LOCATION"],[1198,1209,"LOCATION"],[1219,1226,"EDUCATION"],[1254,1276,"INSTITUTION"],[1279,1285,"LOCATION"],[1287,1298,"LOCATION"],[1320,1344,"INSTITUTION"],[1372,1403,"INSTITUTION"],[1556,1557,"SKILLS"],[1563,1567,"SKILLS"],[1573,1576,"SKILLS"],[1582,1592,"SKILLS"],[1598,1602,"SKILLS"]]}]]}