{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Rajeesh K\r\nKunnamangalam, Kerala\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Rajeesh-K/c77b40c67a775b5b\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nMarketing Executive\r\nKAG INDIA PVT. LTD. - Calicut, Kerala\r\nDecember 2019 to Present\r\n\r\nBusiness Development Executive\r\nSR Trading corporation - Calicut, Kerala\r\nJanuary 2016 to August 2019\r\n\r\n•\r\n\r\nMarketing Executive\r\nAhladham dhothies - Calicut, Kerala\r\nOctober 2011 to December 2015\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nBachelor's in B.com\r\nCalicut university\r\nPresent\r\n\r\nHSE\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Marketing\r\n\r\n• Sales\r\n\r\n• Business Development\r\n\r\n• Communication skills\r\n\r\n• Customer service\r\n\r\n• Negotiation\r\n\r\n• Computer skills\r\n\r\n• Microsoft Excel\r\n\r\n• Microsoft office\r\n\r\n\fLanguages\r\n\r\n• Malayalam - Native\r\n• English - Beginner\r\n• Tamil - Beginner\r\n\r\nAdditional Information\r\n\r\nCOMPUTER KNOWLEDGE \r\nMSOffice \r\n \r\nSKILLS \r\n \r\n• Active Listening \r\n• Analytical \r\n• Identifying risk \r\n• Communication \r\n \r\n• Observation \r\n• Planning \r\n• Problem solving \r\n• Record keeping \r\n• Scheduling appointments \r\n• Time management\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,24,"PERSON"],[26,32,"LOCATION"],[161,180,"ROLE"],[182,201,"ORGANISATION"],[204,211,"LOCATION"],[213,219,"LOCATION"],[221,245,"DURATION"],[249,279,"ROLE"],[281,303,"ORGANISATION"],[306,313,"LOCATION"],[315,321,"LOCATION"],[323,350,"DURATION"],[359,378,"ROLE"],[380,397,"ORGANISATION"],[400,407,"LOCATION"],[409,415,"LOCATION"],[417,446,"DURATION"],[463,473,"EDUCATION"],[477,482,"EDUCATION"],[484,502,"INSTITUTION"],[546,555,"SKILLS"],[561,566,"SKILLS"],[572,592,"SKILLS"],[598,618,"SKILLS"],[624,640,"SKILLS"],[646,657,"SKILLS"],[663,671,"SKILLS"],[684,699,"SKILLS"],[705,721,"SKILLS"],[852,872,"SKILLS"]]}]]}