{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Rutuja Katale\r\nPune, Maharashtra\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Rutuja-Katale/d4e3ae98b12c02cd\r\n\r\nTo obtain a challenging growth oriented position in a \r\nProgressive company, where my skills are effectively \r\nUtilized in new development and in organization Success.\r\n\r\n• 6 month of Experience in PHP as well as ERP software development\r\n• I have successfully completed online website development course (Html, CSS, JAVA Script language)\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nPHP Developer\r\nsk developer - Pune, Maharashtra\r\nJanuary 2021 to June 2021\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nUniversity of pune\r\n2019 to 2020\r\n\r\nH.S.C\r\nMaharashtra state - Pune, Maharashtra\r\n2018 to 2019\r\n\r\nS.S.C\r\nMaharashtra state - Pune, Maharashtra\r\n2016 to 2017\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• MINI PROJECT:\r\n\r\n• RAILWAR RESERVATION SYSTEM\r\n\r\n• JavaScript\r\n\r\n• MySQL\r\n\r\n• PHP\r\n\r\n• HTML5\r\n\r\n• Operating systems MS Windows 7/8/XP, Linux Database Language SqL, PL-SQL, My-sql Languages C,\r\n\r\nC++ Web technologies HTML, CSS, java script\r\n\r\n• The software \"RAILWAY RESERVATION SYSTEM\" will be an application that will be used for\r\n\r\nautomating the railway reservation system. This application will manage information about\r\npassengers details regarding the reservation of seat in different class for different trains, cancellation\r\nof seats, waiting lists of passengers, train schedule. The system also provides the facility to the\r\npassenger to check the time- table of train, reservation level of the seat, waiting seat level. This\r\napplication will greatly improve the current manual system and will be much more efficient.\r\n\r\n\f• Css\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[15,19,"LOCATION"],[21,32,"LOCATION"],[286,293,"DURATION"],[311,314,"SKILLS"],[326,350,"SKILLS"],[474,487,"ROLE"],[489,501,"ROLE"],[504,508,"LOCATION"],[510,521,"LOCATION"],[523,548,"DURATION"],[552,583,"EDUCATION"],[585,597,"DURATION"],[601,606,"EDUCATION"],[608,619,"LOCATION"],[628,632,"LOCATION"],[634,645,"LOCATION"],[647,659,"DURATION"],[663,668,"EDUCATION"],[670,681,"LOCATION"],[690,694,"LOCATION"],[696,707,"LOCATION"],[709,721,"DURATION"],[734,743,"SKILLS"],[768,794,"PROJECTS"],[965,969,"SKILLS"],[971,974,"SKILLS"],[976,987,"SKILLS"],[1007,1033,"PROJECTS"]]}]]}