{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Ramya. S\r\nDigital Marketing Strategist - Sl. No\r\nBengaluru, Karnataka\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Ramya-S/80235f4b8d8f2c37\r\n\r\n• Experience of 8 months in Digital Marketing till date. \r\n• Currently working as consultant at METRO Cash & Carry Ind Pvt Ltd \r\n• Experience in Email Marketing, Web Analytics, SMS Marketing & Web designing domains. Currently\r\nworking in Digital domain. \r\n• Ability to prioritize tasks effectively to balance customer needs. \r\n• Good knowledge about the Microsoft Office, MS Excel, InDesign & Photoshop. \r\n• Good knowledge of Software Testing, SQL, Linux, Java, C, CSS & HTML.\r\n\r\nOrganization Designation Joining Date Relieving Date\r\n1 METRO Cash & Carry India Pvt Ltd Digital Marketing Strategist 08-Nov 17 Till Date\r\n\r\nTechnical Expertise\r\nElements Particulars\r\nPrimary Skill Digital & Email Marketing\r\nOperating Systems Windows 7, Windows XP\r\nDomain  Knowledge  Digital,  Email  &  SMS  Marketing,  SEO,  Web  Analytics,  Software  Testing  &  Web\r\nDesigning\r\nDatabase Connectivity MySQL\r\nCoding\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nDigital Marketing Strategist\r\nSl. No\r\nNovember 2017 to Present\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nBachelor of Science\r\nDegree College - Bengaluru, Karnataka\r\n2017\r\n\r\nMES\r\nPU College\r\n2014\r\n\r\nSSLC\r\nStella Maris School\r\n2012\r\n\r\n\f• Java,HTML,CSS,INDESIGN,Photoshop (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• MySQL\r\n\r\n• Marketing\r\n\r\n• Communication skills\r\n\r\n• Social media management\r\n\r\nCertifications and Licenses\r\n\r\nSmart pro.java\r\nMarch 2014 to Present\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,8,"PERSON"],[10,38,"ROLE"],[49,58,"PERSON"],[60,69,"PERSON"],[160,168,"DURATION"],[172,189,"ROLE"],[226,236,"ROLE"],[240,270,"ORGANISATION"],[289,304,"SKILLS"],[306,319,"SKILLS"],[321,334,"SKILLS"],[337,359,"SKILLS"],[498,514,"SKILLS"],[516,524,"SKILLS"],[526,534,"SKILLS"],[537,547,"SKILLS"],[570,586,"SKILLS"],[588,591,"SKILLS"],[593,598,"SKILLS"],[600,604,"SKILLS"],[606,607,"SKILLS"],[609,612,"SKILLS"],[615,620,"SKILLS"],[680,712,"ORGANISATION"],[713,741,"ROLE"],[742,761,"DURATION"],[822,847,"SKILLS"],[849,866,"SKILLS"],[867,877,"SKILLS"],[878,888,"SKILLS"],[909,916,"SKILLS"],[919,924,"SKILLS"],[929,943,"SKILLS"],[946,949,"SKILLS"],[952,966,"SKILLS"],[969,986,"SKILLS"],[991,1005,"SKILLS"],[1007,1028,"SKILLS"],[1029,1034,"SKILLS"],[1036,1042,"SKILLS"],[1098,1126,"ROLE"],[1136,1160,"DURATION"],[1177,1204,"EDUCATION"],[1215,1224,"LOCATION"],[1226,1235,"LOCATION"],[1245,1260,"INSTITUTION"],[1270,1295,"INSTITUTION"],[1308,1312,"SKILLS"],[1313,1317,"SKILLS"],[1318,1321,"SKILLS"],[1322,1330,"SKILLS"],[1331,1340,"SKILLS"],[1387,1392,"SKILLS"],[1398,1407,"SKILLS"],[1497,1511,"CERTIFICATE"]]}]]}