{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Rajat Shrotriya\r\nMarketing manager\r\nBhopal, Madhya Pradesh\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Rajat-Shrotriya/afa9f63d387739de\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\r\n\r\nPersonal Details\r\n\r\nDate of Birth: 1991-11-18\r\nEligible to work in: India\r\nHighest Career Level: 5+ years experience\r\nIndustry: Marketing\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nMarketing Manager\r\nTARGET ALL IN MARKETING - Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh\r\nApril 2013 to Present\r\n\r\nDone many Projects for MNC's.\r\n\r\nMARKETING MANAGER\r\nTARGET ALL IN MARKETING - Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh\r\nPresent\r\n\r\nManaging OPERATION, MARKETING,SALES & PRODUCTION.\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nMaster's in M.B.A - MARKETING & OPERATION\r\nDEVI AHILYA VISHWAVIDYALAY, INDORE. - Indore, Madhya Pradesh\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• OPERATIONS,MARKETING,SALES & PRODUCTION.\r\n\r\nLanguages\r\n\r\n• English,Hindi,Marathi. - Fluent\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,15,"PERSON"],[17,34,"ROLE"],[36,58,"LOCATION"],[271,279,"DURATION"],[334,351,"ROLE"],[353,376,"ORGANISATION"],[379,401,"LOCATION"],[403,424,"DURATION"],[438,457,"PROJECTS"],[461,478,"ROLE"],[480,503,"ORGANISATION"],[506,528,"LOCATION"],[607,648,"EDUCATION"],[650,676,"INSTITUTION"],[678,710,"LOCATION"],[749,778,"SKILLS"]]}]]}