{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Parvez Hussain\r\nGurgaon, Haryana\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Parvez-Hussain/c83a278d0af3dbc3\r\n\r\nPROFESSIONAL PROFILE SUMMARY \r\n \r\nI am a dynamic and self-motivated professional with 4.5 Years of diverse experience in tool\r\nconfiguration, creation of scripts, \r\nrunning scripts, tool testing, Web Testing and Project management .I have experience in Tool\r\nconfiguring, Requirement analysis, \r\nDatabase management, project management, project planning, executing, Monitoring and closing of\r\nmajor and minor projects. \r\nAlso have a vast experience in identification, analysis & resolution of both pro-active & reactive\r\nbottlenecks of process flow. I \r\npossess good organizational skills with proven abilities in team management, client relationship\r\nmanagement & effective crisis \r\nmanagement. \r\n \r\nCAREER HIGHLIGHTS \r\n \r\nSetup Configuration Specialist - AON Hewitt \r\n \r\n➢ Implementation and Configuration work as developer, Prepairing scripts, Running Scripts on DBMS\r\nenvironments, bug \r\nfixing, worked on AM360 tool. \r\n➢ Created and executed test plans, cases and scripts to uncover, identify and document software\r\nproblems and their \r\ncauses. \r\n➢ Analysis of client requirement. \r\n➢ Good understanding of SDLC & STLC, Agile (Scrum) process. \r\n➢ Documented software defects using bug tracking system and reported defects involving program\r\nfunctionality, \r\noutput, online screen and content to software developers. \r\n➢ Hands on Experience in JIRA, SQL, Eclipse Tool, Black Box Testing. \r\n➢ Cohesive team worker, having strong analytical, problem solving and interpersonal skills. \r\n➢ Working on daily deliverable work to the client. \r\n➢ Enhanced the performance of the team by implementing Best Practices and maintaining pace with\r\nthe current \r\ntechnological change and development. Awarded with Unmatched Team Award(Gold Award) for the\r\nsame. \r\n \r\nClient Implementation Associate - Guardian India \r\n \r\n➢ Management of Management Software. \r\n➢ Successfully accomplished rollout of Absence Management Software -''360ASP'' in Guardian India\r\nfor \r\n\r\n\fmaintaining tracking of employee benefits. \r\no Served as a lead for 360ASP as Issue Resolution team. \r\no benefit analysis of 360ASP and examined estimated no. of users in Delhivery for actually using it\r\nand \r\nresolved different issue on an organization level. \r\no Got to work on SQL for fetching out employees of clients.\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\ndeveloper\r\nFMC\r\nMarch 2015 to October 2018\r\n\r\nTracking changes and enhancements of similar products and services.\r\n➢ Performed Unit and Integration testing.\r\n➢ Prepared weekly reports and bug Report.\r\n\r\nClient Name: - Johnson & Johnson (United States & Puerto Rico)\r\n\r\nRole & Responsibility:\r\n➢ Dev work and bug fixing, Prepaire scripts, identify and document software problems and their causes.\r\n➢ Analysis of client requirement.\r\n➢ Bug fixing and unit testing.\r\n\r\nClient Name: - NISSAN\r\nRole & Responsibility:\r\n➢ Configured Correspondence (Using HTML, Java - Eclipse, SSH secure Shell).\r\n➢ Performed Unit Testing, Acceptance Testing, Integration Testing)\r\n➢ Also worked on Plans Configuration (provided by the respective Clients and their testing)\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nCBSE in Board\r\nRawal Convent School Ballabgarh\r\n2011\r\n\r\nCBSE in Board\r\nHigh school standard - Palwal, Haryana\r\n2009\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• SQL-Advance Query Tool\r\n\r\n• HTML and XML scripts\r\n\r\n• Ecllipse and Jira\r\n\r\n• General Software- MS-Office (MS-Project Planning, MS-Word, MS-Excel, MS-Power Point).\r\n\r\n\f• White box testing, Unit Testing, Black box testing, Functional Testing etc.\r\n\r\n• Software Development Methodologies\r\n\r\n• Software Testing\r\n\r\n• Defect/Bug Tracking(JIRA)/tfs\r\n\r\n• Functional Requirements\r\n\r\n• Scripting & Documentation\r\n\r\n• HTML5\r\n\r\n• SQL\r\n\r\n• Agile\r\n\r\nLanguages\r\n\r\n• Hindi - Native\r\n• English - Expert\r\n• Urdu - Intermediate\r\n• Arabic - Beginner\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[16,23,"LOCATION"],[25,32,"LOCATION"],[200,209,"DURATION"],[235,254,"SKILLS"],[256,275,"SKILLS"],[279,294,"SKILLS"],[296,308,"SKILLS"],[310,321,"SKILLS"],[326,344,"SKILLS"],[386,406,"SKILLS"],[410,429,"SKILLS"],[431,449,"SKILLS"],[451,467,"SKILLS"],[469,478,"SKILLS"],[480,490,"SKILLS"],[838,868,"ROLE"],[871,881,"ORGANISATION"],[930,939,"ROLE"],[1226,1230,"SKILLS"],[1233,1237,"SKILLS"],[1239,1244,"SKILLS"],[1462,1466,"SKILLS"],[1468,1471,"SKILLS"],[1473,1485,"SKILLS"],[1487,1505,"SKILLS"],[1877,1901,"ROLE"],[1904,1918,"ORGANISATION"],[2045,2059,"ORGANISATION"],[2431,2457,"DURATION"],[2633,2650,"ORGANISATION"],[2652,2665,"LOCATION"],[2668,2679,"LOCATION"],[2896,2902,"ORGANISATION"],[3181,3185,"EDUCATION"],[3196,3216,"INSTITUTION"],[3217,3227,"LOCATION"],[3237,3241,"EDUCATION"],[3275,3281,"LOCATION"],[3283,3290,"LOCATION"],[3324,3335,"SKILLS"],[3352,3356,"SKILLS"],[3361,3364,"SKILLS"],[3378,3386,"SKILLS"],[3391,3395,"SKILLS"],[3430,3440,"SKILLS"],[3451,3458,"SKILLS"],[3460,3468,"SKILLS"],[3470,3484,"SKILLS"],[3742,3745,"SKILLS"]]}]]}