{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Onkar Lokhande\r\nPhaltan, Maharashtra\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Onkar-Lokhande/32be028381f36e13\r\n\r\nI am Bsc Horticulture graduate. In Shreemant Shivajiraje college of horticulture Phaltan so I need job I\r\nam fresher\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nMarketing Executive\r\nIFFCO KISAN SANCHAR LTD - Pune, Maharashtra\r\nJanuary 2017 to January 2021\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nSecondary(10th Pass)\r\nShivaji University - Satara, Maharashtra\r\nJanuary 2015 to July 2016\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Completed Ms cit course\r\n\r\n• Marketing\r\n\r\n• Communication skills\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[16,23,"LOCATION"],[25,36,"LOCATION"],[123,126,"EDUCATION"],[127,139,"EDUCATION"],[140,149,"EDUCATION"],[153,198,"INSTITUTION"],[199,206,"LOCATION"],[257,276,"ROLE"],[278,301,"ORGANISATION"],[304,308,"LOCATION"],[310,321,"LOCATION"],[323,351,"DURATION"],[368,377,"EDUCATION"],[378,387,"EDUCATION"],[390,408,"INSTITUTION"],[411,417,"LOCATION"],[419,430,"LOCATION"],[432,457,"DURATION"],[470,472,"SKILLS"],[495,508,"CERTIFICATE"],[514,523,"SKILLS"],[529,542,"SKILLS"]]}]]}