{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Ruchit Sanghvi\r\nMumbai, Maharashtra\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Ruchit-Sanghvi/008ffc45e2a785fc\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nSales and Marketing\r\nIndex Assistive Technologies\r\nJune 2018 to November 2019\r\n\r\nKey Responsibilities:\r\n• Marketing (Online and Offline)\r\n• Product Development\r\n• Handling B2B portals for the company\r\n• Order Execution and Client Servicing\r\n• various other marketing and sales related activities\r\n\r\nRatnamani Jewellers\r\nApril 2014 to May 2018\r\n\r\nKey Responsibilities:\r\n• Store management\r\n• Marketing\r\n• Overall monitoring of business\r\n\r\nOnline Marketing Executive\r\nWebSmith Technologies Private Limited\r\nAugust 2013 to March 2014\r\n\r\nKey Responsibilities:\r\n• Link Building - getting links from fellow bloggers.\r\n• Guest Posting - approach bloggers to guest post on their website asking for a back link in return.\r\n• Email outreach - get articles published and getting featured as a guest blogger.\r\n• Bylines - a short bio about the author.\r\n• Resource Boxes - description for ad words.\r\n• Citations - descriptors that instigate call to action.\r\n\r\nSenior Sales and Marketing Executive (International and Domestic Sales)\r\nAdvanced Fittings Private Limited - Mumbai, Maharashtra\r\nNovember 2011 to August 2013\r\n\r\nNov 2011 - Aug 2013 - (1 Year 9 Months)\r\nDesignation: Senior Sales and Marketing Executive (International and Domestic Sales)\r\nKey Responsibilities:\r\n• Generating new business\r\n• Acquisition of new clients\r\n• Planning for execution of orders\r\n• Marketing of products\r\n• Follow-ups with the client for feedback and repeat orders\r\n\r\n\f• Client Servicing\r\n\r\nAchievements:\r\n• Successfully acquired and catered to GMM Pfaudler (Mumbai) by co-operating for their projects in which\r\nwe supplied our Fittings. (Revenue generated - 8 Lakh Rupees)\r\n• Acquired the complete project of Arya Group (Mumbai), a conglomerate for supply of Fittings in their\r\nIron Ore Pelletization Plant (Revenue generated - 39 Lakh Rupees)\r\n• Relationship building and acquiring a project from Gaffney Kroese Supply Corp (USA), largest Oil and\r\nGas trader in the USA with offices and operations globally including India (Revenue generated - 15 Lakh\r\nRupees)\r\n• Executing a project for United Phosphorous Limited (Gujarat) for the expansion of their CS2 Plant, in\r\nwhich we supplied entire Fittings and Piping package\r\n• Successfully acquired and executed projects worth 78 Lakh Rupees for the year 2012-13\r\n\r\nPost Graduate Diploma in Business Administration in Business Administration\r\nWelingkar's Institute of Management and Research\r\n2012 to 2014\r\n\r\nAdministrator\r\nNovoGene Lifesciences Private Limited\r\nSeptember 2010 to November 2011\r\n\r\nKey Responsibilities:\r\n• Research on Pharmaceutical products\r\n• Work closely with the department head on new projects\r\n• Setting up a new clinical trial research project\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nBachelor of Arts in English\r\nKishinchand Chellaram College\r\n2008 to 2009\r\n\r\nHSC\r\nKishinchand Chellaram College\r\n2005 to 2006\r\n\r\nSSC\r\nSt. Ignatius High School\r\n2003 to 2004\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Excellent communication skills\r\n\r\n• Proficiency in English, Hindi and Marathi (R, W, S)\r\n\r\n• Microsoft Word and Excel\r\n\r\n• Internet and basic hardware usage\r\n\r\n• Qualified in Google Online Marketing Fundamentals\r\n\r\n\f• Certified in Google AdWords (2018-19)\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[16,22,"LOCATION"],[24,35,"LOCATION"],[136,155,"ROLE"],[157,185,"ORGANISATION"],[187,213,"DURATION"],[242,271,"ROLE"],[276,295,"ROLE"],[299,335,"ROLE"],[339,375,"ROLE"],[435,454,"ORGANISATION"],[456,478,"DURATION"],[507,523,"ROLE"],[527,536,"ROLE"],[540,570,"ROLE"],[602,639,"ORGANISATION"],[641,666,"DURATION"],[695,708,"ROLE"],[750,763,"ROLE"],[852,866,"ROLE"],[936,943,"ROLE"],[979,993,"ROLE"],[1025,1034,"ROLE"],[1083,1119,"ROLE"],[1156,1189,"ORGANISATION"],[1192,1198,"LOCATION"],[1200,1211,"LOCATION"],[1213,1241,"DURATION"],[1245,1264,"DURATION"],[1268,1283,"DURATION"],[1299,1335,"ROLE"],[1397,1420,"ROLE"],[1424,1450,"ROLE"],[1454,1486,"ROLE"],[1490,1511,"ROLE"],[1515,1572,"ROLE"],[1579,1611,"ROLE"],[1653,1665,"ORGANISATION"],[1667,1673,"LOCATION"],[1818,1828,"ORGANISATION"],[1830,1836,"LOCATION"],[1956,2001,"ROLE"],[2007,2033,"ORGANISATION"],[2035,2038,"LOCATION"],[2076,2079,"LOCATION"],[2127,2132,"LOCATION"],[2198,2224,"ORGANISATION"],[2226,2233,"LOCATION"],[2411,2418,"DURATION"],[2422,2497,"EDUCATION"],[2499,2547,"ORGANISATION"],[2549,2561,"DURATION"],[2580,2617,"ORGANISATION"],[2619,2650,"DURATION"],[2679,2714,"ROLE"],[2718,2771,"ROLE"],[2775,2823,"ROLE"],[2840,2867,"EDUCATION"],[2869,2898,"INSTITUTION"],[2900,2912,"DURATION"],[2916,2919,"EDUCATION"],[2921,2950,"INSTITUTION"],[2952,2964,"DURATION"],[2968,2971,"EDUCATION"],[2973,2997,"INSTITUTION"],[2999,3011,"DURATION"],[3024,3033,"SKILLS"],[3132,3156,"SKILLS"],[3257,3284,"CERTIFICATE"],[3286,3293,"DURATION"]]}]]}