{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["KIRAN SHIVAPOOJI\r\nAddress: At: Bachanal\r\nPost: Rajanal\r\nTQ: Kamalapur\r\nDIST: GULBARGA-585313\r\nCell:8277456219\r\nkiranshivapooji@gmail.com\r\n\r\nCAREER OBJECTIVE\r\nTo obtain a challenging position in a high quality engineering environment where my resourceful \r\nexperience and academic skills will add value to organizational operations\r\n\r\nACADEMICDETAILS\r\n\r\n•Diploma in electrical and electronics engineering [2015] with aggregate of 78 from    \r\nN.R.A.M.polytechnic,nitte\r\n\r\n•ITI [2011] with aggregate of 82 fromH.K.E.S polytechnic\r\n\r\nWORKEXPERIENCE\r\n• Worked as Electrical foreman  in SOUDI ELECTRICITY COMPANY(AL-MASHARIQ) \r\n\r\nfrom May 2016 to 2nd July 2017\r\nRole :Over all supervising the cable laying up to 132KV\r\nSECO certified splicing card up to 33kv.\r\nResponsible for up to 33kv terminations, joints& glandings.\r\nInstallations of500KVA, 1MVA, 1.5MVA, 5MVA distribution transformer substations, \r\nEnergisation transformers.\r\n Over all coordinating manpower and material co-ordination. \r\nDistribution network faults locating and clearing.\r\nTroubleshooting of RMU's, Replacements of CT’s, PT’s and \r\nRelays. Installations of CT, Single box, double boxand four \r\nbox meters. 13.8kv substation (RMU &Transformer unit) \r\nmaintenance.\r\nReplacement of Schneider and Saudi LucyRMU’s, Replacements of relays \r\nand CT's Installations of ACDB &DCDB panel boards.\r\n\r\n• Worked asFM Engineer in ERICSSON INDIA PVT LTDfrom May 2015 to May 2016\r\n\r\nRole: Installations of microwave and GSM Antennas through sub-contractors and \r\ncommissioning. Overallmaintenance of 2G, 3G, &4G BTS's.\r\nResponsible for DG sets, SMPS, UPS & Battery banks over all preventive and \r\nbreakdown maintenance.\r\nSupervising utility supply 24*7 through vendors.\r\n\r\n• Worked asTrainee technician in TOYOTA KIRLOSKAR MOTORS PVT LTD from Apr \r\n\r\nRole: planned and breakdown maintenance of conveyors and \r\novens. Installations of new lighting loads & small equipment.\r\nInspection and periodic maintainable of all motors in \r\nplant. Implementing kaizen activities to reduce \r\naccidents.\r\n\r\nPROJECTDETAILS\r\n\r\nDescription:\r\n\r\n•Modon132/33/13.8kvsubstation (Al-Qassim)\r\n\r\noverall supervising the cable laying and \r\nterminations. High pot testing and over sheath \r\ntesting of cables. Installations of ACDB &DCDB \r\npanel boards. Installationand periodic \r\ninspections of battery banks.\r\n\r\n\f6 Months\r\nElectrical foreman\r\n\r\n:\r\nDuration\r\nRole\r\n:\r\nTeam Size :\r\n\r\n Description:\r\n\r\n23 Members\r\n•Almaraipre-Treatmentplant-2\r\n\r\nDuration:\r\nRole:\r\n   Team Size:\r\n\r\n8 Months\r\nElectrical foreman\r\n20 Members.\r\n\r\ninstallations of 3 Medium voltage ringsof 50 Mva capacity with 9 4way RMU's \r\nand 18 transformers\r\nOverall cable laying and glanding,termination supervising\r\n\r\nFIELDOFINTERESTS\r\n\r\n•Power, energy\r\n•Oil &gas\r\n\r\n•Manufacturing\r\n\r\n•Telecommunication\r\n\r\nSKILLS\r\nTeamworking\r\n•\r\n•\r\nPositivity\r\n• Creativity\r\n• Hard working\r\n\r\nSTRENGTH&HOBBIES\r\n\r\n•Communication \r\n•Flexibility\r\n•Analytic\r\n\r\n•Swimming\r\n\r\n•Watching movies \r\n•Web surfing\r\n•Trekking\r\n\r\nDECLARATION\r\n\r\nbelief.\r\n\r\nPlace: Bangalore\r\n\r\nI hereby declare that the above written particulars are true to the best of my knowledge and \r\n\r\n(Kiran shivapoji)\r\n\r\n\f\f",{"entities":[[0,16,"PERSON"],[31,39,"LOCATION"],[60,69,"LOCATION"],[77,92,"LOCATION"],[94,109,"CONTACT"],[111,136,"EMAIL"],[353,361,"EDUCATION"],[365,403,"EDUCATION"],[462,467,"INSTITUTION"],[516,527,"EDUCATION"],[582,607,"ORGANISATION"],[630,655,"DURATION"],[1367,1380,"ORGANISATION"],[1384,1410,"ORGANISATION"],[1411,1431,"DURATION"],[1758,1789,"ORGANISATION"],[3026,3035,"LOCATION"],[3137,3152,"PERSON"]]}]]}