{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Raghav Mahajan\r\nPathankot, Punjab\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Raghav-Mahajan/a343c35390debb23\r\n\r\nTo be a part of company that indulges professional growth which provides challenging career while\r\nallowing me to utilize my knowledge and skills.\r\n\r\nI currently working in Smartwebrowse India Pvt. Ltd. As a Front-End web developer in Wordpress (CMS)\r\nand i have a knowldege of java Script and PHP\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nWeb Developer\r\nSmartwebrowse India Pvt. Ltd. - Kharar, Punjab\r\nJanuary 2021 to Present\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nMaster's in Information Technology\r\nSri sai group of institute - Pathankot, Punjab\r\nJuly 2018 to October 2020\r\n\r\nB.sc in P, C, M\r\nMonad University\r\n2016\r\n\r\nP.S.E.B\r\n2011\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Web Designing: HTML, CSS, WORDPRESS, JAVA SCRIPT\r\n\r\n• Basic knowledge of JQUERY, PHP\r\n\r\n• Computer skills in, such as Microsoft word, Microsoft Power Point\r\n\r\n• I had done typing course (6 month) QUALITIES AND STRENTH\r\n\r\n• Focused and punctual\r\n\r\n• Flexible to work conditions\r\n\r\n• Keen observant and good learner\r\n\r\n• Positive and strong aptitude\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[16,33,"LOCATION"],[288,317,"ORGANISATION"],[323,364,"ROLE"],[393,412,"SKILLS"],[421,448,"ROLE"],[450,479,"ORGANISATION"],[480,496,"LOCATION"],[498,521,"DURATION"],[538,572,"EDUCATION"],[574,600,"INSTITUTION"],[603,620,"LOCATION"],[622,647,"DURATION"],[651,666,"EDUCATION"],[668,684,"INSTITUTION"],[686,690,"DURATION"],[694,701,"INSTITUTION"],[703,707,"DURATION"],[735,890,"SKILLS"]]}]]}