{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Pranshul Junghare\r\nIndore, Madhya Pradesh\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Pranshul-Junghare/41878e3fbdc62b5b\r\n\r\nBACKGROUND \r\nVedantu \r\n \r\nMarketing & HR Initiating phone conversations with parents. \r\n2019 - 2021 Follow up with the prospects and close the sales. \r\nAchieving the weekly targets in a high-pressure. \r\nRani Durgawati Vishwa Vidyalaya, Diligently communicating and priming the lead. \r\nJabalpur M.P. \r\nBachelor of Science in Biology \r\nAditya Birla Capital Chhindwara \r\n2015 - 2018 \r\nBusiness Development Executive \r\nVidya Bhumi Public School, \r\nApr. 2017 - Jun 2019 \r\nChhindwara, M.P. Discover and understand the needs of the \r\nBiology customers. \r\n12th | 2014-15 | CBSE Co-creates the perfect solution protecting their \r\ngoals. \r\nVidya Bhumi Public School, Contribute and add value to their lives. \r\nChhindwara, M.P. Closing the sale with good customer relation. \r\n10th | 2012-13 | CBSE\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nMarketing Manager & Marketing Strategist\r\nRaheja Solar Food Processing Pvt. Ltd - Indore, Madhya Pradesh\r\nOctober 2021 to Present\r\n\r\ndeveloping and implementing Nov 2021 - working\r\nsuccessful strategies, driving profits, Work with top management.\r\nincreasing market shares, and Supervise and coordinate business activities.\r\nstrengthening customer dominance. Identify Potential Market.\r\nSelect the Channels of Distribution.\r\nEvaluate the Product.\r\n\r\nBusiness Development Executive\r\nAditya Birla Group - Chhindwara, Madhya Pradesh\r\nFebruary 2017 to August 2019\r\n\r\n\fEducation\r\n\r\nMaster's in Marketing\r\nMedicaps University - Indore, Madhya Pradesh\r\nAugust 2019 to July 2021\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Storytelling.\r\n\r\n• Strategic Marketing.\r\n\r\n• Digital marketing.\r\n\r\n• Performing and managing many Events like Open\r\n\r\n• Mic, Moonstone2020 \"Melange\" in university as\r\n\r\n• an organizer and did anchoring in front of 2000+\r\n\r\n• audience successfully.\r\n\r\n• Leadership.\r\n\r\n• Performed in many street shows with the\r\n\r\n• Active listener.\r\n\r\n• Multitasking.\r\n\r\n• awareness.\r\n\r\n• organization \"Natyaganga, \" which spreads social\r\n\r\n• Published an International Anthology named\r\n\r\n• \"Stories beyond those three words\" as a compiler\r\n\r\n• and an Author in the Year 2020, February, which\r\n\r\n• is available on more than ten channels.\r\n\r\n• Articles got selected in two International\r\n\r\n• Anthologies named: \"Confession of Love, \" It all\r\n\r\n• started with you\" as a Co-Author.\r\n\r\n• ms office\r\n\r\n• Google AdWords\r\n\r\n• SEM\r\n\r\n• Digital marketing\r\n\r\n• Marketing\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,17,"PERSON"],[19,25,"LOCATION"],[27,41,"LOCATION"],[139,146,"ORGANISATION"],[152,161,"ROLE"],[164,166,"ROLE"],[214,225,"DURATION"],[329,360,"INSTITUTION"],[411,419,"LOCATION"],[420,424,"LOCATION"],[427,457,"EDUCATION"],[460,480,"INSTITUTION"],[481,491,"LOCATION"],[494,505,"DURATION"],[508,538,"ROLE"],[541,566,"INSTITUTION"],[570,590,"DURATION"],[593,603,"LOCATION"],[605,609,"LOCATION"],[674,678,"EDUCATION"],[681,688,"DURATION"],[691,695,"EDUCATION"],[756,781,"INSTITUTION"],[826,836,"LOCATION"],[838,842,"LOCATION"],[891,895,"EDUCATION"],[898,905,"DURATION"],[908,912,"EDUCATION"],[968,985,"ROLE"],[988,1008,"ROLE"],[1010,1047,"ORGANISATION"],[1050,1056,"LOCATION"],[1058,1072,"LOCATION"],[1074,1097,"DURATION"],[1418,1448,"ROLE"],[1450,1468,"ORGANISATION"],[1471,1481,"LOCATION"],[1483,1497,"LOCATION"],[1499,1527,"DURATION"],[1557,1566,"ROLE"],[1568,1587,"INSTITUTION"],[1590,1596,"LOCATION"],[1598,1612,"LOCATION"],[1614,1638,"DURATION"],[1695,1705,"SKILLS"],[1711,1729,"SKILLS"],[2051,2062,"ORGANISATION"],[2477,2494,"SKILLS"],[2500,2509,"SKILLS"]]}]]}