{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["S Guruganesh\r\nsalesman\r\nChennai, Tamil Nadu\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/S-Guruganesh/e98b3a8f44b48f15\r\n\r\nTo give my whole contribution to develop the organization and co-ordinate with my team mates by \r\nhigh level of involvement.\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nMarketing\r\nVinayak Industries ( bigart)\r\nFebruary 2019 to September 2020\r\n\r\n• Furniture & interior Sales Marketing (Jan 2019 to sep 2020)\r\n• Distribute in all over tamil Nadu\r\n\r\nsalesman\r\nPothys textiles pvt ltd - Madurai, Tamil Nadu\r\nJuly 2014 to May 2015\r\n\r\nWorked in The Chennai silks, Chennai for 3.4 years (July 2015 to November 2018)\r\n\r\n• 4 months in sales department\r\n• 2.5 years in purchase department\r\n• 7 months in section maintenance\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nSSLC\r\nState - Madurai, Tamil Nadu\r\n2014\r\n\r\nPKN Boys Higher Secondary School\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• BUYING/PROCUREMENT (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• CONFIDENT (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• MARKETING (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• MERCHANDISING (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• MS OFFICE (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• car driving (2 years)\r\n\r\n\fLanguages\r\n\r\n• Hindi - Beginner\r\n• English - Fluent\r\n\r\nAdditional Information\r\n\r\nPersonal skills \r\n• Good communication \r\n• Self-confident \r\n• Quick learner \r\n• Adaptive nature \r\n• Persuasive skill \r\n \r\nComputer skills \r\n• MS Office \r\n \r\nArea of interest \r\n• Merchandising \r\n• Tele marketing \r\n• Purchasing field\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[24,38,"LOCATION"],[270,279,"ROLE"],[281,308,"ORGANISATION"],[311,342,"DURATION"],[348,384,"ROLE"],[386,406,"DURATION"],[434,444,"LOCATION"],[448,456,"ROLE"],[458,481,"ORGANISATION"],[484,491,"LOCATION"],[493,503,"LOCATION"],[505,526,"DURATION"],[544,551,"LOCATION"],[559,566,"LOCATION"],[571,580,"DURATION"],[582,608,"DURATION"],[627,632,"ROLE"],[647,656,"DURATION"],[683,691,"DURATION"],[695,714,"ROLE"],[745,752,"LOCATION"],[754,764,"LOCATION"],[774,806,"INSTITUTION"],[819,828,"SKILLS"],[834,852,"SKILLS"],[911,920,"SKILLS"],[983,992,"SKILLS"]]}]]}