{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Reshma Parhar\r\nPassionate Backend Developer\r\nKarjat, Maharashtra\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Reshma-Parhar/0830cba394dc1ed1\r\n\r\nI have started my journey as backend developer at Jio Platforms Limited.Currently I am working on\r\nproject Jiogate .I am responsible for developing microservice based API'S for both mobile apps and\r\nwebsite. \r\n \r\nI have always been a quick learner . I consistently love to learn new technologies and explore new\r\nthings.I am very much curious about to know how things happen in background for every code\r\nexecution. \r\n \r\nI am working on technologies like Node.js,Express.js.I have experience of working with databases like\r\nMongodb,Redis,Mysql and Elastic Search.I have basic exposure to CICD tools like docker,jenkins and\r\nkubernetes.\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\r\n\r\nPersonal Details\r\n\r\nDate of Birth: 1999-03-23\r\nEligible to work in: India\r\nHighest Career Level: 1-2 years experience\r\nIndustry: Information Design & Documentation\r\nTotal years of experience: 1\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nBackend Developer\r\nJiogate Platforms Limited\r\nJune 2021 to Present\r\n\r\n• Experience in RESTful API design and development\r\n• Implemented npm module for common functions used in Jio Gate Project\r\n• Actively Participate in defining the product as part\r\n• of regular meetings with the product team\r\n• Developed scripts for synchronization of db\r\n• Modified existing restful web service\r\n• Delivered quality code in an optimized way by applying the best development practices\r\n• During API development created API documentation using\r\n• Swagger and tested API’s using chai,mocha and sinon.\r\n• I am having experience working within agile methodologies\r\n•  Hands  on  experience  with  Continuous  Delivery  build  pipeline  tools  like:  Git,  Jenkins  ,Docker  and\r\nKubernetes\r\n\r\n\fEducation\r\n\r\nHigher Secondary(12th Pass)\r\nMahatma Gandhi Vidyalaya,Karjat - Karjat, Maharashtra\r\nJune 2016 to June 2017\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Javascript\r\n\r\n• Java\r\n\r\n• C\r\n\r\n• Html5\r\n\r\n• Css\r\n\r\n• Python\r\n\r\n• Node.js (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• Express Js (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• Mongodb (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• Mysql (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• Redis (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• Elastic Search (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• RabbitMQ (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• Software Development (1 year)\r\n\r\n• Gitlab (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\nLanguages\r\n\r\n• Hindi - Fluent\r\n• Marathi - Fluent\r\n• English - Fluent\r\n\r\nOnline Profile\r\n\r\nhttps://github.com/reshmapar\r\n\r\nhttps://www.linkedin.com/in/reshmaparhar23/\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[26,43,"ROLE"],[45,51,"LOCATION"],[53,64,"LOCATION"],[174,191,"ROLE"],[195,226,"ORGANISATION"],[244,259,"PROJECTS"],[600,607,"SKILLS"],[608,620,"SKILLS"],[669,676,"SKILLS"],[677,682,"SKILLS"],[683,688,"SKILLS"],[693,709,"SKILLS"],[749,755,"SKILLS"],[756,763,"SKILLS"],[769,780,"SKILLS"],[1033,1050,"ROLE"],[1052,1077,"ORGANISATION"],[1079,1099,"DURATION"],[1119,1130,"SKILLS"],[1131,1137,"SKILLS"],[1142,1153,"SKILLS"],[1169,1179,"SKILLS"],[1659,1678,"SKILLS"],[1765,1769,"SKILLS"],[1771,1778,"SKILLS"],[1781,1787,"SKILLS"],[1794,1804,"SKILLS"],[1822,1838,"EDUCATION"],[1839,1848,"EDUCATION"],[1851,1875,"INSTITUTION"],[1876,1882,"LOCATION"],[1885,1891,"LOCATION"],[1893,1904,"LOCATION"],[1906,1928,"DURATION"],[1956,1966,"SKILLS"],[1972,1976,"SKILLS"],[1982,1983,"SKILLS"],[1989,1994,"SKILLS"],[2000,2003,"SKILLS"],[2009,2015,"SKILLS"],[2021,2028,"SKILLS"],[2053,2063,"SKILLS"],[2088,2095,"SKILLS"],[2120,2125,"SKILLS"],[2150,2155,"SKILLS"],[2180,2194,"SKILLS"],[2219,2227,"SKILLS"],[2252,2272,"SKILLS"],[2287,2293,"SKILLS"]]}]]}