{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Sachin Rathor\r\nFaridabad, Haryana\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Sachin-Rathor/164383913de61cfa\r\n\r\nPersonal Details\r\n\r\nDate of Birth: 1988-03-30\r\nEligible to work in: India\r\nHighest Career Level: 5+ years experience\r\nIndustry: Sales\r\nTotal years of experience: 10\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nMarketing Manager\r\nSuper Store - Faridabad, Haryana\r\nSeptember 2016 to January 2021\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Sales Manager\r\n\r\nDriven & Motivated to achieve organization tasks. Highly motivated to lounch professional sales careers.\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[15,24,"LOCATION"],[26,33,"LOCATION"],[182,187,"LOCATION"],[211,219,"DURATION"],[242,247,"ROLE"],[301,318,"ROLE"],[320,331,"ORGANISATION"],[334,343,"LOCATION"],[345,352,"LOCATION"],[354,384,"DURATION"],[397,406,"SKILLS"]]}]]}