{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["RESUME\r\nChinmaya Kumar Kund\r\n\r\nEmail: kundchinmaya@gmail.com\r\n M0BILE NO: +91 9902760235\r\n         \r\n          \r\n \r\n            \r\n \r\n            \r\n \r\n            \r\n \r\n \r\nObjective:\r\nTo   secure   a   promising   position   that   provides   me   a   good   opportunity   to\r\nefficiently utilize my skills and for my professional growth.\r\n\r\n \r\n            \r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n            \r\n\r\n \r\n            \r\n\r\n \r\n            \r\n\r\n \r\n            \r\n\r\n \r\n            \r\n\r\n \r\n            \r\n\r\n \r\n            \r\n\r\nSummary of Qualifications:\r\n\r\nAcademic Qualifications:\r\n\r\nEDUCATION\r\n\r\nBOARD/UNIVERSITY\r\n\r\nSUBJECT\r\n\r\nDegree\r\n\r\nUtkal University  Odisha\r\n\r\nIntermediate\r\n\r\nMatriculation\r\ns\r\n\r\nCouncil of Higher \r\nSecondary Education \r\nOdisha\r\nBoard of Secondary \r\nEducation Odisha\r\n\r\nBachelor of\r\nCommerce\r\n\r\nBachelor of\r\nCommerce\r\n\r\nYEAR OF\r\nPASSING\r\n\r\nApr-2004\r\n\r\nMar-2001\r\n\r\nAll subjects\r\n\r\nMar-1999\r\n\r\nProfessional Qualifications:\r\n\r\n I have completed DCA (Diploma in Computer Application) \r\n\r\nFrom A To Z Professional Technical Institute. \r\n Also complete   Accounting Package TALLY ERP.\r\n\r\n Computer Skills:\r\n\r\n Microsoft Office, Word, Excel & Power point.\r\n Tally 7.2, Tally 9.0, \r\n Internal mail system.\r\n\r\nWork Experience:\r\n\r\n Presently Working Fawaz Refrigeration Air conditioning Co.W.L.L as Secretary \r\n\r\ncum Accounts from Kuwait 13 April 2014 to till date. \r\n\r\n Worked in with M/s Holm KK Extrusions PVT.LTD as an Accountant from 01st \r\n\r\nMarch 2013 to 7th April 2014. \r\n\r\n Worked in M/s Rathi Adshive Tape (P) LTD as an Accountant from 10th \r\n\r\nFebruary 2008 to 20 December 2012.\r\n\r\n Worked in OASIS INDUSTRIES (P) LTD as an Accounts asst. from 18th February \r\n\r\n2006 to 20 August 2008. \r\n\r\n\fJob Responsibilities:\r\n\r\n Preparing   site   status   report   on   monthly   basis   to   Ministry   of   Health.\r\n\r\n(Farwaniya Hospital Site). \r\n\r\n Preparing various work schedules on monthly basis for HVAC, Plumbing, and\r\nElectrical & Civil works to be carried out by related technical departments.\r\n\r\n Preparing memos & letters to Ministry & Head Office.\r\n Send and receive the faxes & e-mails & replying in co-ordination with Site\r\n\r\nManager.\r\n\r\ndepartment.\r\n\r\nemployees. \r\n\r\n Making timesheet using ERP system (FOCUS) for 150 staff working at site\r\n\r\n(Farwaniya Hospital Site)\r\n\r\n Prepare the annual leave schedule for all employees & co-ordinate with HR\r\n\r\n Arrangements   for   Medical   and   Fingerprint   to   the   newly   appointed\r\n\r\n Co-ordinate with HR & Management for employee queries & complaints.\r\n Updating & maintain the holiday, absence & training records of staffs.\r\n Updating, processing & filing of all documents related to the site.\r\n Prepare the material request for some consumable items & follow up with\r\n\r\npurchase orders & tracking the materials.\r\n\r\n Maintaining the site petty cash & forwarding to finance department for re-\r\n\r\nimbursement cash payment.\r\n\r\n Quantity surveying for received materials at site office.\r\n Having   a   good   communication   skill   and   soft   spoken   approach   with\r\n\r\neveryone.\r\n\r\nCurrent Job Responsibilities (Accounts)\r\n\r\n Prepare all type of Vouchers and posting on computer.\r\n\r\n Reconcile the Bank & Analysis the Creditors & Cheque Preparing. \r\n\r\n Reconciliation of Party’s A/c, \r\n\r\n Preparing & Checking the Debit Note, Credit Note & Traveling Bill.\r\n\r\n Prepare the details of Sales Tax requisition (‘C’ form, Form-38, Form).\r\n\r\n Maintaining Day Book.\r\n\r\n Prepare Sale Tax Return file.\r\n\r\n Prepare Excise Return file on line.\r\n\r\n Preparing Excise Bill.\r\n\r\n Voucher Entry, Cash Book, and Bank work.\r\n\r\n\fPersonal Skills & Managements:\r\n\r\n Self-Motivated, Team working & Interpersonal Skills\r\n Organizing Skills\r\n Positive thinking and Hardworking\r\n Effective Communications skills\r\n\r\nPersonal Details:\r\n\r\n Date of Birth                 :    04.07.1984\r\n Father’s Name              :    Akshay Kumar Kund\r\n Marital status               :    Married \r\n Languages Known      :   English, Hindi, Odia\r\n Nationality                   :    Indian\r\n Sex                                 :     Male\r\n Passport No.\r\n:    M5450842\r\n Passport Issue\r\n Passport Expire\r\n\r\n:    05/02/2015\r\n\r\n:    04/02/2025\r\n\r\nDECLARATION:   -   I   hereby   declare   that   the   above   information   is   correct,   true   &\r\ncomplete from best knowledge. If given a chance, I assure that I will assume my all\r\nabilities for the satisfaction of my senior & management.\r\n\r\nYours truly,\r\n                                                                        \r\nChinmaya Kund\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[8,22,"PERSON"],[38,60,"EMAIL"],[74,88,"CONTACT"],[607,623,"EDUCATION"],[625,631,"LOCATION"],[651,664,"EDUCATION"],[671,710,"INSTITUTION"],[713,719,"LOCATION"],[721,751,"EDUCATION"],[752,758,"LOCATION"],[762,783,"EDUCATION"],[787,808,"EDUCATION"],[832,852,"DURATION"],[935,971,"EDUCATION"],[982,1022,"INSTITUTION"],[1043,1072,"CERTIFICATE"],[1100,1116,"SKILLS"],[1118,1122,"SKILLS"],[1124,1144,"SKILLS"],[1148,1164,"SKILLS"],[1174,1195,"SKILLS"],[1239,1284,"ORGANISATION"],[1288,1314,"ROLE"],[1320,1326,"LOCATION"],[1327,1354,"DURATION"],[1376,1384,"PERSON"],[1385,1406,"ORGANISATION"],[1413,1423,"ROLE"],[1429,1467,"DURATION"],[1484,1493,"PERSON"],[1494,1514,"ORGANISATION"],[1521,1531,"ROLE"],[1537,1580,"DURATION"],[1596,1620,"ORGANISATION"],[1627,1641,"ROLE"],[1647,1688,"DURATION"],[1733,1809,"ROLE"],[1846,1997,"ROLE"],[2003,2055,"ROLE"],[2059,2095,"ROLE"],[2181,2281,"ROLE"],[2287,2360,"ROLE"],[2366,2445,"ROLE"],[2451,2518,"ROLE"],[2522,2663,"ROLE"],[2667,2757,"ROLE"],[2898,2955,"ROLE"],[3161,3224,"ROLE"],[3444,3473,"ROLE"],[3479,3514,"ROLE"],[3548,3622,"ROLE"],[3835,3845,"DURATION"],[3881,3898,"PERSON"],[4165,4194,"DURATION"],[4535,4548,"PERSON"]]}]]}