{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Paghadal Chandresh\r\nSr. iOS Developer - Drunken Ducks\r\nMississauga\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Paghadal-Chandresh/e49d6fcf9d7b6676\r\n\r\nSURAT, GJ\r\n● Worked closely with product managers and designers to define a rich iOS experience for the user\r\n\r\n● Involved in implementing the application from requirements specified\r\n\r\n● Responsible for technical documentation on how to use the plugin to develop applications.\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nSr. iOS Developer\r\nDrunken Ducks - SURAT, GUJARAT, IN\r\nSeptember 2017 to Present\r\n\r\nㅡ\r\n\r\nJr. iOS Developer\r\nNarola Infotech - SURAT, GUJARAT, IN\r\nJune 2017 to September 2017\r\n\r\nSURAT, GJ\r\n\r\n●  Supported  and  streamlined  company  policies,  procedures,  mission,  and  standards  of  ethics  and\r\nintegrity\r\n● Learnt the integration of rich frameworks on iOS app\r\n\r\n● Explored new technologies and shared findings with the team.\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nMCA in Systems Management\r\nVEER NARMAD SOUTH GUJARAT UNIVERSITY - SURAT, GUJARAT, IN\r\nJuly 2014 to April 2017\r\n\r\nBCA in Computer Programming\r\nVEER NARMAD SOUTH GUJARAT UNIVERSITY - SURAT, GUJARAT, IN\r\nJuly 2011 to March 2014\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• BUDGET (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• C# (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n\f• DATABASE (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• DEBUG (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• DEPLOYMENT (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• Git (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• JAVASCRIPT (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• MAC (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• MAC OS (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• MODEL VIEW CONTROLLER (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• MODEL-VIEW-CONTROLLER (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• MODEL-VIEW-VIEWMODEL (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• MVC (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• MVVM (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• OBJECTIVE C (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• PROVISIONING (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\n• XCODE (Less than 1 year)\r\n\r\nLanguages\r\n\r\n• English - Intermediate\r\n\r\nAdditional Information\r\n\r\n● Skilled and efficient iOS Developer with 3 years of experience creating unique and modern\r\napplications available in the App Store. \r\n \r\n● Results-oriented software developer and research professional with 3 years experience in both\r\ndevelopment and research positions. \r\n \r\n● Understand the importance of creating highly readable and easily maintainable source code. \r\n \r\n● Experienced of working on iOS platform and frameworks and customizing it as per requirements.\r\nGood hand at MVVM and MVC. \r\n \r\n● Constantly striving to learn new technologies and look to ways to better myself in this rapidly\r\nchanging industry. \r\n \r\nㅡ \r\n \r\nSkills \r\n \r\n● Environment: Mac OS X, Xcode, Git, Bitbucket \r\n● Languages: Objective C, Swift, C#, JavaScript \r\n● Framework: MVC, MVVM, \r\n● Database: Realm, Core Data, SQLite, Firestore \r\n\r\n\f● Advanced knowledge of how to profile, debug and optimise apps with Instruments, able to diagnose\r\napplication crashes with crash report symbolication \r\n● Able to learn quickly and willing to share knowledge \r\n● Demonstrable ability to deliver projects on time, with high quality, and within budget \r\n● Ability to produce high quality software with an emphasis on performance, reliability and\r\nextensibility \r\n● Knowledge of iTunes Connect, provisioning, Code-signing and IPA/Build creation, knowledge of\r\nEnterprise deployment is a bonus\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,18,"PERSON"],[20,37,"ROLE"],[40,53,"ORGANISATION"],[55,66,"LOCATION"],[152,157,"LOCATION"],[159,161,"LOCATION"],[193,201,"ROLE"],[206,215,"ROLE"],[452,469,"ROLE"],[471,484,"ORGANISATION"],[487,492,"LOCATION"],[494,501,"LOCATION"],[507,532,"DURATION"],[541,558,"ROLE"],[560,575,"ORGANISATION"],[578,583,"LOCATION"],[585,592,"LOCATION"],[598,625,"DURATION"],[629,634,"LOCATION"],[636,638,"LOCATION"],[925,961,"INSTITUTION"],[964,969,"LOCATION"],[971,978,"LOCATION"],[984,1007,"DURATION"],[1011,1014,"EDUCATION"],[1018,1038,"SKILLS"],[1040,1076,"INSTITUTION"],[1079,1084,"LOCATION"],[1086,1093,"LOCATION"],[1099,1122,"DURATION"],[1181,1182,"SKILLS"],[1307,1310,"SKILLS"],[1335,1345,"SKILLS"],[1370,1373,"SKILLS"],[1398,1401,"SKILLS"],[1475,1496,"SKILLS"],[1521,1541,"SKILLS"],[1566,1569,"SKILLS"],[1594,1598,"SKILLS"],[1623,1632,"SKILLS"],[2276,2280,"SKILLS"],[2285,2289,"SKILLS"],[2462,2467,"SKILLS"],[2469,2472,"SKILLS"],[2474,2483,"SKILLS"],[2499,2508,"SKILLS"],[2509,2510,"SKILLS"],[2512,2517,"SKILLS"],[2520,2521,"SKILLS"],[2523,2533,"SKILLS"],[2549,2552,"SKILLS"],[2554,2558,"SKILLS"],[2592,2598,"SKILLS"],[2600,2609,"SKILLS"]]}]]}