{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Pranit Kamble\r\nMaster Of Business Administration Marketing Management and Finance management\r\nBaner, Pune\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Pranit-Kamble/52ddcdb7d253289d\r\n\r\nTo work in an organization where I can use my skills and knowledge to deliver \r\nvalue-added results that provide me job satisfaction and self-development which \r\nhelp me achieve personal as well as organizational goals.\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nSales and marketing\r\nIFORTIS Pvt.Ltd\r\nDecember 2021 to Present\r\n\r\n1 month)\r\nCourses-\r\nPresentation Skills\r\nPlatform: TCS ion\r\nCommunication skills\r\nPlatform: TCS ion\r\n\r\nInternship\r\nExcellent Communication and Collaboration\r\nCLARITY\r\nMarketing and Research (1 month)\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• University/ Board \r\n\r\nYear Of \r\nPassing \r\n2021 \r\nPercentage/ \r\nCGPA \r\nPursuing \r\n(FY CGPA - \r\n8.11) \r\nMaster of Business \r\nAdministration \r\nMaster of Business \r\nAdministration (MBA) \r\n\r\nMaster's in Master of Business Administration (Marketing and Finance)\r\nRajarambapu Institute of technology Rajaramnagar - Sangli, Maharashtra\r\n2021\r\n\r\n\fRajarambapu Institute of Technology, Islampur. \r\nShivaji University, \r\nKolhapur \r\nBachelors of science \r\n2020 \r\n55.8 \r\n(Microbiology) \r\nHSC (Science) \r\nKwc, Sangli \r\nMaharashtra State Board 2015 \r\nPDVP Collage Tasgaon \r\nMaharashtra State Board 2013 \r\nSRBV Tasgaon \r\n46.6 \r\n62 \r\nSSC \r\nWork interest- \r\nFinance, Marketing Management, Research Management, Sales Management\r\n\r\n• Business development\r\n\r\n• Leadership\r\n\r\n• English\r\n\r\n• Management\r\n\r\n• Marketing\r\n\r\n• Microsoft Excel\r\n\r\n• Negotiation\r\n\r\n• Sales\r\n\r\n• Finance\r\n\r\n• Financial Management\r\n\r\n• Financial Analysis\r\n\r\n• Market research\r\n\r\n• Hindi\r\n\r\nLanguages\r\n\r\n• Marathi Hindi English - Fluent\r\n\r\nOnline Profile\r\n\r\nhttps://www.linkedin.com/in/pranit-kamble-b47a941aa\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[15,48,"EDUCATION"],[49,69,"ROLE"],[74,92,"ROLE"],[94,99,"LOCATION"],[101,105,"LOCATION"],[482,497,"ORGANISATION"],[499,534,"DURATION"],[694,703,"SKILLS"],[708,716,"SKILLS"],[718,725,"DURATION"],[869,904,"EDUCATION"],[907,942,"EDUCATION"],[944,947,"EDUCATION"],[965,998,"EDUCATION"],[1000,1021,"EDUCATION"],[1024,1059,"INSTITUTION"],[1060,1072,"LOCATION"],[1075,1081,"LOCATION"],[1083,1094,"LOCATION"],[1105,1140,"INSTITUTION"],[1142,1151,"LOCATION"],[1154,1172,"LOCATION"],[1176,1184,"LOCATION"],[1225,1237,"EDUCATION"],[1241,1244,"EDUCATION"],[1246,1253,"EDUCATION"],[1262,1268,"LOCATION"],[1271,1282,"LOCATION"],[1283,1294,"LOCATION"],[1302,1314,"INSTITUTION"],[1315,1322,"LOCATION"],[1406,1413,"SKILLS"],[1415,1435,"SKILLS"],[1437,1456,"SKILLS"],[1458,1474,"SKILLS"],[1480,1500,"SKILLS"]]}]]}