{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Sagar Dixit\r\nMumbai, Maharashtra\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Sagar-Dixit/43f5775bb5845b7a\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nDigital Marketing Consultant\r\nFolks Marketing Solution - Victoria, BC\r\nMarch 2021 to Present\r\n\r\nDigital Marketing Manager\r\nNext Level Marketers - Thane, Maharashtra\r\nJune 2016 to January 2021\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\n• Manage SEO & PPC for the clients\r\n• Create campaign strategy, create ad copies, manage media, manage reports, manage ad performance\r\n• Keyword analysis, keywords research, competitors analysis, site audits, speed analysis\r\n• Website audit, website analysis\r\n• On page SEO, Off Page SEO Strategy building, Link building strategies\r\n• Collaboration with Graphic & Content team.\r\n\r\nManaging and Optimisation of Organic & Paid Digital Marketing Campaigns for Clients for Better Sales.\r\n\r\nBachelor of Business Administration in Business, Marketing, Management\r\nSikkim Manipal University Distance Education - Thane, Maharashtra\r\nJuly 2014 to July 2017\r\n\r\nAdvanced Diploma in Digital Marketing\r\nSoftPro Digital Marketing Training Institute - Dadar, Mumbai, Maharashtra\r\nJune 2014 to June 2015\r\n\r\nDiploma in Information Technology\r\nShreeram Polytechnic - Airoli, Navi Mumbai, Maharashtra\r\nJune 2007 to June 2011\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Social Media Marketing\r\n\r\n• Digital Marketing\r\n\r\n• Lead Generation\r\n\r\n• Google Analytics\r\n\r\n• Google Ads\r\n\r\n• Search Engine Optimization\r\n\r\n\f• Digital Marketing Strategy\r\n\r\n• Customer Service\r\n\r\n• Customer Handling\r\n\r\n• Business Development\r\n\r\n• Marketing Management\r\n\r\n• Search Engine Optimization (SEO)\r\n\r\n• Google AdWords\r\n\r\n• SEO\r\n\r\n• SEM\r\n\r\n• Facebook Advertising\r\n\r\n• WordPress\r\n\r\n• PPC Campaign Management\r\n\r\n• Keyword Research\r\n\r\n• Branding\r\n\r\n• E-Commerce\r\n\r\nOnline Profile\r\n\r\nhttps://www.facebook.com/sagardxt\r\n\r\nhttps://www.instagram.com/sagardxt/\r\n\r\nhttps://www.linkedin.com/in/sagar-dixit-55401b93/\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[13,19,"LOCATION"],[21,32,"LOCATION"],[130,158,"ROLE"],[160,184,"ORGANISATION"],[187,195,"LOCATION"],[197,222,"DURATION"],[226,251,"ORGANISATION"],[253,273,"ORGANISATION"],[276,281,"LOCATION"],[283,321,"DURATION"],[340,372,"ROLE"],[376,400,"ROLE"],[402,418,"ROLE"],[420,432,"ROLE"],[434,448,"ROLE"],[450,471,"ROLE"],[475,491,"ROLE"],[493,510,"ROLE"],[565,578,"ROLE"],[580,596,"ROLE"],[613,643,"ROLE"],[645,669,"ROLE"],[673,715,"ROLE"],[719,820,"ROLE"],[824,871,"EDUCATION"],[873,882,"EDUCATION"],[896,940,"INSTITUTION"],[943,948,"LOCATION"],[950,961,"LOCATION"],[963,985,"DURATION"],[989,1026,"EDUCATION"],[1028,1072,"INSTITUTION"],[1075,1080,"LOCATION"],[1082,1088,"LOCATION"],[1090,1101,"LOCATION"],[1103,1125,"DURATION"],[1129,1162,"EDUCATION"],[1164,1184,"INSTITUTION"],[1187,1193,"LOCATION"],[1195,1206,"LOCATION"],[1208,1219,"LOCATION"],[1221,1243,"DURATION"],[1256,1265,"SKILLS"],[1271,1293,"SKILLS"],[1299,1316,"SKILLS"],[1322,1337,"SKILLS"],[1343,1359,"SKILLS"],[1365,1375,"SKILLS"],[1414,1440,"SKILLS"],[1446,1462,"SKILLS"],[1491,1511,"SKILLS"],[1517,1537,"SKILLS"],[1543,1574,"SKILLS"],[1581,1595,"SKILLS"],[1601,1604,"SKILLS"],[1619,1639,"SKILLS"],[1645,1654,"SKILLS"],[1660,1683,"SKILLS"]]}]]}