{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Rinky Borah\r\nData Analyst job seeker\r\nJodhpur, Rajasthan\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Rinky-Borah/8efd4e8678bf85c0\r\n\r\nHigh energy professional with exposure in \r\ntarget demanding assignments \r\naspiring a role at a reputed IT organization to \r\nutilize my skills that can contribute to the \r\nassociation’s growth as well as enhance my \r\ncognition by exploring new things.\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nApplication Developer\r\nIBM India(P)Ltd - Bengaluru, Karnataka\r\nApril 2013 to July 2016\r\n\r\nWorked as an Associate System Engineer for one year and then Application Developer for more than two\r\nyears in an internal project named IBM Domestic Enterprise Application for IBM India Pvt\r\nLtd, Bangalore.\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nBachelor's in Information Technology\r\nRustam Ji Institute of Technology - Gwalior, Madhya Pradesh\r\n2008 to 2012\r\n\r\nHigher Secondary(12th Pass) in CBSE Board\r\nKV ONGC AGARATALA - Agartala, Tripura\r\n2008\r\n\r\nSecondary(10th Pass) in PCMB\r\nKV JALIPA CANTT,Barmer - Barmer, Rajasthan\r\n2006\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\nDB2,Python, R\r\n\r\nLanguages\r\n\r\n• Hindi - Fluent\r\n• English - Fluent\r\n\r\n• Apache Open Office, MS Excel, MS Powerpoint, MS Word, MySQL Workbench, MySQL 5.0, IBM\r\n\r\n\fNGO, Non-Profit / Student Organizations\r\n\r\nAFFWA-Indian Air Force\r\nMarch 2016 to Present\r\n\r\nThe Air Force Wives Welfare Association was formed with the main objective of providing assistance to\r\nfamilies of deceased, disabled, retired, as well as serving personnel of the Indian Air Force. \r\n \r\nWelfare of \r\n• Sanginis \r\n• Families of  Air Warriors \r\n• Veer Naris \r\n• Special Children in IAF \r\n• Under  Privileged \r\n• Civil Population  during disaster or natural calamities\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[13,25,"ROLE"],[38,45,"LOCATION"],[45,56,"LOCATION"],[409,430,"ROLE"],[432,447,"ORGANISATION"],[450,459,"LOCATION"],[461,470,"LOCATION"],[472,495,"DURATION"],[512,537,"ROLE"],[542,550,"DURATION"],[560,581,"ROLE"],[676,694,"ORGANISATION"],[696,706,"LOCATION"],[723,759,"EDUCATION"],[761,794,"INSTITUTION"],[797,804,"LOCATION"],[806,820,"LOCATION"],[822,834,"DURATION"],[838,854,"EDUCATION"],[855,864,"EDUCATION"],[869,879,"INSTITUTION"],[881,888,"INSTITUTION"],[889,898,"LOCATION"],[901,909,"LOCATION"],[911,918,"LOCATION"],[928,937,"EDUCATION"],[938,947,"EDUCATION"],[958,973,"INSTITUTION"],[974,980,"LOCATION"],[983,989,"LOCATION"],[991,1000,"LOCATION"],[1032,1035,"SKILLS"],[1036,1042,"SKILLS"],[1044,1058,"SKILLS"],[1104,1122,"SKILLS"],[1124,1132,"SKILLS"],[1134,1147,"SKILLS"],[1149,1156,"SKILLS"],[1158,1173,"SKILLS"],[1175,1184,"SKILLS"],[1186,1197,"SKILLS"]]}]]}