{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["A responsible and challenging position to utilize my professional skill to impact on the growth and\r\ndevelopment of a progressive organization.\r\n\r\nCURRICULUM - VITAE\r\n\r\nSHAHNAWAZ\r\nHouse No.1248 Street No.17,B\r\nRajiv Gandhi Nagar\r\nNew Mustafabad\r\nDelhi :- 110094\r\nCont.No:- 9717885303,9212867659\r\nEmail:- azims0975@gmail.com\r\n\r\nOBJECTIVE.\r\n\r\nEDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION.\r\n\r\n 10th Passed from C.B.S.E. Board.\r\n 12th Passed from C.B.S.E.Board.\r\n\r\nOTHER SKILLS.\r\n\r\n Basic Knowledge of Computer.\r\n Auto Cad from MSME.\r\n First Aid from Red Cross.\r\n\r\nWORK EXPERIENCE.\r\n\r\n One Year Experience in Amazone PSA work.\r\n One Year Experience in Auto Cad work.\r\n\r\nPERSONAL PROFILE.\r\n\r\nFather’s Name\r\nDate of Birth\r\nNationality\r\nMarital Status\r\nGender\r\nLanguage Known\r\n\r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\n\r\nMohd Nisar\r\n08th May 1995\r\nIndian\r\nUnmarried\r\nMale\r\nHindi & English\r\n\r\nDECLARATION.\r\n\r\nDate:\r\nPlace: Delhi\r\n\r\nI hereby declare that the all entry that is furnished in this resume is true in my knowledge and\r\nbelief.\r\n\r\nSHAHNAWAZ\r\n(Signature)\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[160,178,"PERSON"],[180,206,"LOCATION"],[210,228,"LOCATION"],[230,244,"LOCATION"],[246,261,"LOCATION"],[263,294,"CONTACT"],[304,323,"EMAIL"],[373,405,"EDUCATION"],[409,440,"EDUCATION"],[463,491,"SKILLS"],[509,514,"INSTITUTION"],[569,588,"DURATION"],[592,599,"ORGANISATION"],[613,632,"DURATION"],[636,644,"ORGANISATION"],[780,790,"PERSON"],[881,886,"LOCATION"],[999,1008,"PERSON"]]}]]}