{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["RESUME                 \r\n\r\nAshish Gujrati\r\nEmail Id: gujrati.ashish1@gmail.com                                                   \r\nMob no: 09760207737\r\n\r\nCareer Objective:\r\n\r\nTo join an organization that will recognize and utilize my skills fully and offer me a \r\nposition requiring innovative and creative ideas where continuous growth and learning\r\nare way of life.\r\n\r\nEducational Qualifications:\r\n\r\nYear\r\n\r\nDegree\r\n\r\nInstitution\r\n\r\nSubjects/Specialization\r\n\r\n%\r\n\r\n2012-\r\n2014\r\n\r\nPOST\r\nGRADUATION\r\n(MBA)\r\n\r\nGURUKUL\r\nKANGRI\r\nUNIVERSITY\r\n\r\n2008-\r\n2011\r\n\r\n  GRADUATION\r\n          (BBA)\r\n\r\nSGRRITS ,\r\nDEHRADUN\r\n\r\n2008\r\n\r\n2006\r\n\r\nINTERMEDIAT\r\nE\r\n\r\nA B V M I\r\nCOLLEGE\r\n\r\nHIGH \r\nSCHOOL\r\n\r\nB G R M I\r\nCOLLEGE\r\n\r\nBUSINESS FINANCE\r\n\r\n68.00%\r\n\r\nBUSINESS FINANCE\r\n\r\n67.00%\r\n\r\nENGLISH, HINDI,\r\nGEOGRAPHY\r\nENGLISH,\r\nHINDI,MATHEMATICS\r\n, SCIENCE, SOCIAL\r\nSCIENCE\r\n\r\n52.00%\r\n\r\n55.00%\r\n\r\n\fAdditional Qualifications:\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nI have done Computer application software from Prime computers Institute \r\n(Dehradun).\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nI have done Hindi Typing from Nice institute (Dehradun). \r\n\r\nSkills Sets:\r\n \r\nPersonal Skills:  Leadership, Team-Building, Professional, Public speaking.\r\n\r\nTechnical SKILLS: MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access, Internet use, etc.\r\n\r\nProject and Training Undertaken:\r\n\r\n Successfully completed Eight weeks summer training in “ING VYSYA \r\n\r\nBANK”   from Dehradun under BBA.\r\n\r\n Successfully completed Six weeks summer training in “LOHIA CORP \r\n\r\nLIMITED” From Kanpur under MBA.\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nI have completed “Skills University” Project under Dr. Pankaj Madan (Prof. in \r\nGurukul Kangri University).\r\n\r\nExtra & Co-Curricular Activities: \r\n\r\n Participated in the “5th FIESTA QUIZ-2013” held by GURUKUL \r\n\r\nKANGRI VISHWAVIDYALA, HARIDWAR.\r\n\r\n Participated in the “POSTER COMPITION” held by GURUKUL \r\n\r\nKANGRI VISHWAVIDYALA, HARIDWAR.\r\n\r\n Presently working in “Uttarakhand Sanskrit Academy” As a Account \r\n\r\nCurrent working:\r\n\r\nAssistant.\r\n\r\nPersonal Details:\r\n\r\n\fDate of Birth                       :                08-07-1991\r\n\r\nFather’s Name            \r\n\r\n:                Mr. Santosh Kumar Gujrati\r\n\r\nAddress                            :                Mo-Khatrana, Post-Bilgram,\r\n\r\n                                            Dist-Hardoi, Uttar Pradesh.\r\n\r\nMarital status                :               Unmarried\r\n\r\nNationality                      :                 Indian\r\n\r\nLanguage Known           :                 English, Hindi\r\n\r\nDATE \r\n                                                                                                    (ASHISH GUJRATI)\r\n\r\nNAME\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[27,41,"PERSON"],[53,78,"EMAIL"],[139,150,"CONTACT"],[467,478,"DURATION"],[482,498,"EDUCATION"],[501,504,"EDUCATION"],[509,536,"INSTITUTION"],[540,551,"DURATION"],[557,567,"EDUCATION"],[580,583,"EDUCATION"],[588,595,"INSTITUTION"],[599,607,"LOCATION"],[611,623,"DURATION"],[627,641,"EDUCATION"],[645,663,"INSTITUTION"],[667,693,"INSTITUTION"],[706,714,"EDUCATION"],[715,722,"EDUCATION"],[956,981,"INSTITUTION"],[985,993,"LOCATION"],[1034,1048,"INSTITUTION"],[1050,1058,"LOCATION"],[1141,1157,"SKILLS"],[1179,1186,"SKILLS"],[1188,1193,"SKILLS"],[1195,1205,"SKILLS"],[1207,1213,"SKILLS"],[1298,1309,"DURATION"],[1329,1349,"ORGANISATION"],[1357,1365,"LOCATION"],[1372,1376,"EDUCATION"],[1405,1414,"DURATION"],[1434,1458,"ORGANISATION"],[1464,1470,"LOCATION"],[1477,1481,"EDUCATION"],[1541,1557,"PERSON"],[1570,1595,"INSTITUTION"],[1692,1724,"INSTITUTION"],[1726,1735,"LOCATION"],[1788,1820,"INSTITUTION"],[1822,1831,"LOCATION"],[1858,1888,"INSTITUTION"],[1926,1936,"ROLE"],[2075,2100,"PERSON"],[2156,2167,"LOCATION"],[2169,2181,"LOCATION"],[2230,2241,"LOCATION"],[2243,2257,"LOCATION"],[2550,2564,"PERSON"]]}]]}