{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["                                              \r\n\r\n                                                                                 CURRICULUM--VITAE           \r\n            S. Naqui Abbas \r\n                    Qtr No.-54/C 3rd Floor\r\n                 Street-5 , J- Extension, Laxmi Nagar \r\n                 New Delhi --110092. (INDIA)\r\n                 Tel-9873538782, 9953492854, 09504742835, 061542-78014\r\n                 Email : Naqui_Abbas@rediffmail.com \r\n                               Syed_Abbas1982@yahoo.com\r\n                               SyedAbbas2554@gmail.com\r\n\r\n                 Carrier Objective    To make a career with a leading organization contribution towards exodus of\r\n                                                    the organisation and personal gain of knowledge to develop, mature creative\r\n                                                    myself as an able IT Professional in  today’s IT industry.\r\n\r\n                 Academic Qualification:               Graduation (Hons) in 1996  \r\n\r\n                 Professional Qualification:             Completed Master Degree in Computer Applications \r\n                                                                            from NIIT New Delhi –110001 (INDIA) \r\n                                                                           \r\n                                                                            Pursuing  M. B. A. (IT) from Pondicherry University.\r\n                 Technical Skills:   \r\n\r\n                 Languages:\r\n\r\n                 C++, Visual C++, Visual Basics(6.0) , HTML, Sybase\r\n\r\n                 Operating Systems:  \r\n\r\n                 Windows 95,Windows 98, Windows-NT, MS-Dos, Unix\r\n\r\n                 Front End Tools:\r\n                                                                                                                                                                                           \r\n                 Visual Basics, SQL \r\n \r\n                 Networking:\r\n\r\n                 Windows-NT, TCP/IP, LAN, INTERNET\r\n\r\n                 Packages:\r\n                 MS-Office\r\n\r\n\f My Job Role                JOB PROFILE AT CUSTOMER LOCATION\r\n Key Responsibilities    1.American Express\r\n\r\nThe job involved looking after their mainframe jobs, mainly submission and processing and other\r\nproduction related activities using IBM AS/400. I was looking after their daily upload and download\r\ns of files from the mainframe database and running query on mainframe application. I was also\r\nlooking different processes and smooth functioning of their different package, which are related to\r\nproduction such as Reward Trackers, Xcom, FTP, etc. \r\n\r\nAmerican Express (TRS): working with American Express Travel Related Service in Technologies\r\n(Production Control) as a representative of PSPL.\r\nJob Role: The organization has fully automated operation based on highly advanced information\r\ntechnology system IBM-AS/400, Mini system. My Job role is to manage the administrator of As/400\r\noperation as per the allocated schedule. This requires in depth knowledge of SQL and CL (Control\r\nlanguage As/400).\r\n\r\nResponsibilities   included:-  Ensure   connectivity   to   the   mainframe   System   in   Phoenix   USA.   The\r\nconnectivity of American Express System globally is through CISCO routers support the launch of\r\nnew product by analysing the system requirement .\r\n\r\nManaging   User   Profile   As/400:-  Looking   after   mainframe   data   administration   and   different\r\nproduction related activities using IBM As/400.IBM AS/400 is being used as interface between and\r\nthe local system. I also Monitors LAN and Lotus Notes.\r\n\r\n  Networking / Telecom Support  \r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nSupport of Standard Packages and all kind of Remote Access Packages like Database Related,\r\nImage Bases, Mailing etc.\r\n\r\nInstallation,   configuration,   troubleshooting,   Maintaining   and   Documentation   of   WIN   NT   /\r\nWIN95 / 98 Server and Workstation, Lotus Notes Server / Workstation, CITRIX Server. \r\n\r\n Workstation, NS Elite Workstation Mainframe Application and Banking Application etc.\r\n\r\nInstallation, Monitoring and maintaining of Network and communication equipment’s like –\r\nToken Ring, Ethernet, Router 7200/ 3600, series, IGX ,WAN ,Switch, Token Ring, Switch ,Hubs\r\n& four wires leased line.\r\n\r\n Monitoring and Maintaining of ATM’s for whole India.\r\n\r\n\f        Projects done:                    1.Sales Order & Processing System using Ms-- Access.\r\n\r\n                                                                      2.Video Library Application System  using Sybase & C++.\r\n          \r\n                                                                      3.Video Library Application System using Visual C++ &Access.\r\n\r\n                                                                      4.Video Library Application System  using Visual Basic & SQL.\r\n\r\n                         Experiences:                      1. Worked as a MIS Executive with Shilpi Modes Pvt Ltd, \r\n                                                                        East of Kailash, New Delhi from March 1997 to Sept 2000.\r\n\r\n                                                                     2. Worked as a Customer Support Engineer in American Express \r\n                                                                        Connaught Place New Delhi, from November 2000 to June 2004.\r\n\r\n                                                                     3. Worked as a Data Center Officer in Tata Aig Insurance Co. Ltd. from\r\n                                                                        August, 2004 to Oct 2005.  \r\n\r\n 4. Worked as a Technical Support Engineer in Al-Jeraisy Computers & \r\n    Comm. Services Ltd. Jeddah (KSA) From October 2005 to Nov 2006.\r\n\r\n5. Worked as Technical Support Engineer with Stracon Solutions\r\n    Ltd, New Delhi from December 2006 to January 2008.\r\n\r\n                                                        March 2008 to January 2014.\r\n  \r\n\r\n      6. Worked as IT Administrator with Oger AbuDhabi LLC, UAE, from                  \r\n\r\n      7.Working as a Admin.Manager  with Harveera Bharat Services New Delhi \r\n\r\n    from March 2014 to till date.\r\n\r\n                 Personal Details:\r\n\r\n                 Father’s Name:                          Mr. S. Nazim Hussain (APP Advocate)\r\n\r\n                 Date of Birth:                             5th December 1975\r\n\r\n                 Sex:                                              Male\r\n\r\n                 Nationality:                                Indian\r\n \r\n                 Marital Status:                          Married\r\n\r\n                 Languages Known:                   English , Hindi, Urdu & Bengali\r\n\r\n                 Date:\r\n                 Place:  New Delhi                                                                                                            \r\n                                                                                                                                                 Signature\r\n\r\n\f                                                          \r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[173,187,"PERSON"],[210,259,"LOCATION"],[262,274,"LOCATION"],[276,287,"LOCATION"],[307,334,"LOCATION"],[353,367,"CONTACT"],[369,379,"CONTACT"],[381,392,"CONTACT"],[394,406,"CONTACT"],[433,459,"CONTACT"],[493,517,"CONTACT"],[550,573,"CONTACT"],[990,1015,"EDUCATION"],[1088,1126,"EDUCATION"],[1210,1214,"INSTITUTION"],[1215,1224,"LOCATION"],[1406,1418,"EDUCATION"],[1425,1448,"INSTITUTION"],[2199,2217,"ORGANISATION"],[2708,2724,"ORGANISATION"],[4968,4981,"ROLE"],[4987,5007,"ORGANISATION"],[5083,5109,"LOCATION"],[5115,5139,"DURATION"],[5227,5252,"ROLE"],[5256,5272,"ORGANISATION"],[5347,5372,"LOCATION"],[5379,5406,"DURATION"],[5494,5513,"ROLE"],[5517,5544,"ORGANISATION"],[5623,5648,"DURATION"],[5670,5696,"ROLE"],[5700,5748,"ORGANISATION"],[5749,5761,"LOCATION"],[5767,5792,"DURATION"],[5809,5835,"ROLE"],[5841,5867,"ORGANISATION"],[5869,5878,"LOCATION"],[5884,5914,"DURATION"],[5974,6001,"DURATION"],[6028,6044,"ROLE"],[6050,6054,"ORGANISATION"],[6055,6072,"LOCATION"],[6121,6134,"ROLE"],[6141,6165,"ORGANISATION"],[6166,6175,"LOCATION"],[6189,6213,"DURATION"],[6312,6332,"PERSON"],[6411,6428,"DURATION"],[6784,6793,"LOCATION"]]}]]}