{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["                                        \r\n\r\nCURRICULUM-VITAE                           \r\n\r\n   \r\n\r\n      \r\nMD TOUSHEEF KHAN                               D-85, 3rd Floor\r\n                                                                                                New Ashok nagar,\r\n\r\n            New Delhi-110096\r\n\r\nEmail Id: khantsf@gmail.com\r\nMobile No: +91 9654184091\r\n\r\nOBJECTIVE:\r\n\r\n               Seeking a career with progressive organization where I can verify my skills knowledge  &          \r\n\r\nexperience for progressive growth of firm.\r\n\r\nWORK EXPERIENCE:\r\nHaving   3   Years   experience   on   Maintenance   Field.   I   am   currently   working   as   a   Technical\r\nSupervisor. My role involves supervision of all maintenance work and completes all paper\r\nwork on time to time. \r\n\r\nJOB DESCRIPTION:\r\n\r\n Maintaining Engineering Compliance\r\n Designing & Maintaining Log Books, Equipment History card of ISO standard.\r\n Making Weekly/Monthly Management Report.\r\n Making & Maintaining of PM Schedule.\r\n Procurement of technical items required for day to day operation & maintenance.\r\n Overhauling of L&T, Schneider make LT switchgear.\r\n Execute the minor project.\r\n\r\n OPERATION & MAINTENANCE\r\n\r\n Operation & Maintenance of HT and LT Panel and DG Panel properly.                \r\n\r\n Operation & Maintenance of ACB, OCB, VCB .\r\n Maintenance of Lighting System and all type of New Lighting Wiring & Cable \r\n\r\nWiring.\r\n\r\n Preventive and Breakdown Maintenance of DOL, Star Delta Starter.        \r\n Operation of Split Ac, Packages Ac, Ductable Ac, Tower Ac, cassette ac &  PAC.\r\n Operation and Maintenance of Fire Fighting System.\r\n Operation and Maintenance of Transformer and DG.\r\n Operation and Maintenance of UPS System.\r\n Operation and Maintenance of RO Plant.\r\n Operation and Maintenance of STP.\r\n Operation and Maintenance of HVAC (chiller plant, AHU, VAV)\r\n\r\n\f                                        \r\n\r\nEXPERIENCE SUMMARY:\r\n\r\nCompany\r\n\r\nSites\r\n\r\nDesignation\r\n\r\nPeriod\r\n\r\nRoto Power \r\nProjects \r\nPVt.Ltd.\r\n\r\nEricsson Global \r\nIndia Pvt. Ltd.\r\n\r\nSite Engineer\r\n\r\nJan 2015 to Till date\r\n\r\nIcon Facilitors\r\n\r\nTechnical Supervisor\r\n\r\nJan 2014 to Dec 2014\r\n\r\nAccenture Noida,\r\nsec-135\r\n\r\n Icon Facilitors\r\n\r\nAccenture Noida,\r\nsec-135\r\n\r\nMST\r\n\r\nAug 2013 to Dec 2013 \r\n\r\nINDUSTRIAL TRAINING\r\n\r\nSummer Industrial Training:-\r\n\r\nName of the Organization:    Kanti Thermal power plant. (Bihar)\r\n                                              (Electrical Maintenance Department)               \r\nDuration\r\n\r\n            : \r\n\r\n6 Weeks\r\n\r\nTraining Synopsis\r\n\r\nTo understand the  switchgear , switchyard\r\n\r\n\r\n Maintenance of electrical power system\r\n\r\nName of the Organization:  Guru   Teg   Bahadur   Khalsa   Institute   of   Engineering   and\r\nTechnology\r\nDuration\r\nProject Title                   :         Basic Engg Tools, Household Wiring, Winding of Electrical\r\nMachine                        \r\n\r\n6 weeks\r\n\r\n :   \r\n\r\nSix Months Industrial Training:-\r\n\r\nName of the Organization   : Panjab state power corp. Ltd.        \r\nDuration                           :   6 Months from (Jan-2013 to May-2013)\r\n  \r\nTRAINING SYNOPSIS:-\r\n\r\nStudy of 132/220 KV substation, switchgear.\r\n\r\n\r\n Maintenance of electrical machines\r\n\r\n Design of electrical machines\r\n\r\nTraining on PLC\r\n\r\n\f                                        \r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nProtection of power system\r\n\r\n \r\n\r\nTECHNICAL QUALIFICATION:\r\n\r\nDuration\r\n\r\n2009-2013\r\n\r\nSpecialization\r\n\r\nCourse/Institute\r\n\r\nElectrical\r\n\r\nB.Tech from PTU, with marks 69%\r\n\r\n                                                       \r\n\r\n \r\nEDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS:\r\n\r\nDuration\r\n\r\n2007-2009\r\n\r\n2005-2006\r\n\r\nCourse/Institute\r\n\r\nClass XII from WB Board, with marks 63%\r\n\r\nClass X from UP Board, with marks 67%\r\n\r\nCOMPUTER SKILL:\r\n Ms office\r\n C++\r\n\r\nPERSONAL INFORMATION:\r\n\r\n:\r\n       :\r\n\r\nName\r\nFather’s Name\r\n:  \r\nDate of Birth           \r\nLanguages Known            :  \r\nMarital Status\r\nPassport No                         :               L3966784\r\n\r\nMd Tousheef khan\r\nMr. Md Israr khan\r\nJan 27, 1993 \r\nEnglish, Hindi and Urdu\r\nUnmarried\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\nDECLARATION:\r\nI hereby declare that all the details furnished above are true to the best of my knowledge \r\nand I am solely responsible for any discrepancy.\r\n\r\nDATE:\r\n\r\nPLACE: \r\n\r\n\f                                        \r\n\r\n                                               \r\n\r\n                                                                                                                         Md \r\nTousheef Khan\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[109,122,"PERSON"],[153,157,"LOCATION"],[159,314,"LOCATION"],[328,345,"EMAIL"],[358,372,"CONTACT"],[580,589,"DURATION"],[610,630,"ROLE"],[673,695,"ROLE"],[713,778,"SKILLS"],[822,856,"ROLE"],[860,893,"ROLE"],[989,1018,"ROLE"],[1105,1134,"SKILLS"],[1219,1261,"SKILLS"],[1306,1336,"SKILLS"],[1352,1382,"SKILLS"],[1444,1487,"SKILLS"],[1520,1598,"SKILLS"],[1602,1652,"SKILLS"],[1656,1704,"SKILLS"],[1708,1748,"SKILLS"],[1752,1790,"SKILLS"],[1794,1827,"SKILLS"],[1831,1864,"SKILLS"],[2012,2039,"ORGANISATION"],[2043,2076,"ORGANISATION"],[2097,2118,"DURATION"],[2122,2161,"ORGANISATION"],[2169,2185,"DURATION"],[2189,2214,"LOCATION"],[2238,2263,"LOCATION"],[2274,2294,"DURATION"],[2322,2348,"EDUCATION"],[2383,2402,"ORGANISATION"],[2547,2554,"DURATION"],[2699,2777,"INSTITUTION"],[2831,2897,"PROJECTS"],[2925,2932,"DURATION"],[2945,2955,"DURATION"],[3010,3039,"ORGANISATION"],[3088,3096,"DURATION"],[3103,3123,"DURATION"],[3423,3432,"DURATION"],[3436,3494,"EDUCATION"],[3500,3503,"INSTITUTION"],[3628,3637,"DURATION"],[3641,3650,"DURATION"],[3674,3683,"EDUCATION"],[3689,3697,"INSTITUTION"],[3717,3724,"EDUCATION"],[3730,3738,"INSTITUTION"],[3777,3817,"EDUCATION"],[4001,4017,"PERSON"],[4019,4036,"PERSON"],[4038,4050,"DURATION"],[4492,4510,"PERSON"]]}]]}