{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Md. Shahzad Hasan\r\nH-44/16A, Batla House,\r\nJamia nagar, Okhla\r\nNew Delhi-110025\r\nMobile: 8800689905\r\nE-mail:shahzad_h09@yahoo.com\r\n\r\nCareer Objective\r\n\r\n                                                     \r\n\r\nMy aim in life is to be successful in my field of work & motto is to preserve to the \r\n\r\nhighest point and secure a position where I can effectively contribute my skills and abilities in the \r\nI.T & ITES industry as a Technical engineer possessing Competent Technical skills.\r\n\r\nProfessional Summary\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\n Store Keeper \r\nSYAL SCALE CO., Delhi\r\n\r\nRoles and Responsibility:\r\n\r\n Around 3 Years of experience in Microsoft Windows Technologies\r\n Hands on experience in Systems troubleshooting.\r\n A keen communicator and team member with excellent relation management, \r\n\r\nleadership, analytical and problem solving skills.\r\n\r\nAug’ 2015 to till date\r\n\r\n Store keeping to monitor stock levels and carry out regular manual checks of \r\n\r\nrecorded stock level against actual.\r\n\r\n    Manage labors with unloading and storage of goods received.\r\n\r\n    Identification and loading of goods for dispatch.\r\n\r\n    Assist with checking the condition and quantity / quality of goods received.\r\n\r\n    To update records manually for all transactions of assigned materials.\r\n\r\n    Generate invoice and other necessary paperwork for goods dispatched.\r\n\r\n\fNet Connect Pvt. Ltd.                                                                             Feb’ \r\n2014 to July' 2015\r\nDesktop Engineer\r\nClient:  IBM Netsol Daksh\r\n\r\nRoles and Responsibility:\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nInstallation, configuration, Software and troubleshooting Hardware \r\nperipherals on Windows platforms.\r\nInstallation, configuration Citrix client ends\r\nInstallation, configuration and troubleshooting Lotus notes\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n Responsible for VPN connection\r\n Network printer installation & configuration\r\n\r\n\r\nIdentify and troubleshoot network related physical problems on a regular \r\nbasis.\r\n\r\n Encryption of Laptop with Standard Check list\r\n Attending problems reported by customer through mails and through Elixir, \r\n\r\nMaximo & Codesk ticketing tool.\r\n\r\nSP Solutions Point Pvt. Ltd.                                                                   \r\nMarch’ 2012 to Feb’ 2014\r\nDesktop Engineer\r\nClient: Northern railway Headquarter\r\n\r\nRole & responsibilities:\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nInstallation, configuration and troubleshooting of operating systems- \r\nWindows XP, Win 7,Win Vista, Windows 2003 Server- drivers, Software \r\npatches & other PC peripherals\r\n\r\n Configuration & troubleshooting of MS Outlook at client end.\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nLooking after maintenance of hardware and software\r\nInstallation of Anti-Virus software’s on clients.\r\nInstallation and configuration LAN on Microsoft Windows Operating \r\nSystem based machine.\r\n\r\nNetwork Incorporation                                                                          July’ \r\n2009 to Dec’ 2011\r\nHardware Engineer\r\n\r\n\fRole & responsibilities:\r\n\r\n Assembling Of Desktop system.\r\n\r\n\r\nInstallation, configuration and troubleshooting of operating systems- \r\nWindows XP, Win 7,Win Vista, Windows 2003 Server- drivers, Software \r\npatches & other PC peripherals\r\n\r\n Configuration & troubleshooting of MS Outlook at client end.\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nLooking after maintenance of hardware and software\r\nInstallation of Anti-Virus software’s on clients.\r\nInstallation and configuration LAN on Microsoft Windows Operating \r\nSystem based machine.\r\n\r\nTechnical Qualification\r\n\r\n Passed Microsoft Certified IT Professional (MCITP), Windows 7 in July-2011.\r\n Certification course in A+ (Hardware) and N+ (NETWORKING) from IIHT.\r\n Certification course in Windows Server2003 Engineer (MCSE-2003) from IIHT.\r\n Certification course in Cisco Certified Engineer (CCNA) from IIHT.\r\n\r\nAcademic Qualification\r\n\r\n B.A from Magadh University, Bihar\r\n 12th passed from – Patna Council of Intermediate Science Education\r\n 10th passed from –Bihar Board (Patna) of Secondary Education\r\n\r\nPersonal Profile\r\n\r\nFather’s Name\r\nDate of Birth\r\nMarital Status\r\nPermanent Address\r\n\r\nDeclaration:\r\n\r\n: Md. Sadrul Hasan Azad\r\n: 15th December, 1985\r\n: Single\r\n: Vill- Hargawan\r\n P.O-Barbigha\r\n \r\n\r\n                                                                                Dist- Nalanda (Bihar)\r\n\r\n I hereby declare that all the details provided are true to my knowledge and I \r\npromise that if I am placed at your concern I will do my jobs to the best satisfaction \r\nof my superiors.\r\n\r\n______________________________________________________________________\r\n\r\n\fDate:\r\nPlace:\r\n\r\n(MD SHAHZAD HASAN)\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,17,"PERSON"],[19,27,"LOCATION"],[29,79,"LOCATION"],[89,99,"CONTACT"],[108,129,"CONTACT"],[534,546,"ROLE"],[549,563,"ORGANISATION"],[565,570,"LOCATION"],[612,619,"DURATION"],[852,874,"DURATION"],[1369,1390,"ORGANISATION"],[1467,1492,"DURATION"],[1494,1518,"ROLE"],[1521,1531,"ORGANISATION"],[2132,2160,"ORGANISATION"],[2229,2253,"DURATION"],[2255,2279,"ROLE"],[2888,2913,"DURATION"],[3486,3529,"CERTIFICATE"],[3544,3554,"DURATION"],[3582,3595,"CERTIFICATE"],[3600,3615,"CERTIFICATE"],[3621,3626,"INSTITUTION"],[3654,3693,"CERTIFICATE"],[3699,3704,"INSTITUTION"],[3732,3763,"CERTIFICATE"],[3769,3774,"INSTITUTION"],[3806,3832,"EDUCATION"],[3834,3839,"LOCATION"],[3843,3854,"EDUCATION"],[3862,3867,"LOCATION"],[3913,3924,"EDUCATION"],[3930,3936,"LOCATION"],[3944,3949,"LOCATION"],[4082,4103,"PERSON"],[4107,4126,"DURATION"],[4140,4277,"LOCATION"]]}]]}