{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["MAHIPAL SINGH                                      \r\nMobile No.     :   +91-9417153885; +91-8126352316\r\nE-mail             :  mahipalsinghmehta@gmail.com                                                                               \r\n__________________________________________________________                          \r\nCurriculum Vitae\r\n\r\nOBJECTIVE :\r\n\r\nLooking for challenging career, where there is scope for demonstration, always on a look out for a \r\npositive & bigger outlook, and to achieve organization goals with devotion & concentration for the \r\ngrowth and betterment of the organization\r\n\r\n \r\n  COMMUNICATION:\r\n \r\nADDRESS FOR\r\n \r\n\r\nCorrespondence Address\r\n\r\nPermanent Address\r\n\r\nMAHIPAL SINGH                                                    \r\nROOM NO-207\r\nHOSTEL NO.-04\r\nSLIET, LONGOWAL\r\nDIST-SANGRUR,PUNJAB  \r\nPIN-148106\r\n\r\nMAHIPAL SINGH                                                    \r\nS/O-  Mr. PRATAP SINGH    \r\nVill-RATIR KETI,KOTYURA,  P.O.-RATIR KETI\r\nBAGESHWAR (UTTARAKHAND)\r\nPIN-263633\r\n\r\nEDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS:\r\n\r\nCourse\r\n\r\nInstitution\r\n\r\nBoard/University Marks (%)\r\n\r\n& CGPA\r\n\r\nBachelor of Engg.\r\nChemical Engineering \r\n(polymer)\r\n\r\nSant Longowal Institute of \r\nEngg. & Tech. Longowal,\r\nPunjab(deemed university).\r\n\r\n S.L.I.E.T.\r\n\r\n 6.0 CGPA\r\n\r\nDiploma in Chemical Tech. \r\n(rubber & plastic).\r\n\r\nGovt. Polytechnic \r\nShaktifarm\r\n\r\nU.B.T.E, ROORKEE\r\n\r\n72.41 %\r\n\r\nMatriculation    \r\n(10th)\r\n\r\nH.K.H.S. School \r\n(Uttarakhand)\r\n\r\nUTTARAKHAND \r\nBOARD\r\n\r\n66.4 %\r\n\r\n \r\n  PROJECT\r\n \r\nACADEMIC\r\n \r\n\r\n TRAINING UNDERTAKEN :\r\n\r\n Design Plant of ethanol production and design of distillation column, & condenser. \r\n Plant layout of urea industry.\r\n\r\n\f● 1 month training in POLYESTER PVT. LTD. KHATIMA\r\n● 15 days training in GUJRAT AMBUJA PVT. LTD.SITARGANJ\r\n● 45 days training in S.R.F. LTD KASHIPUR\r\n\r\nCO-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES  & EXPERIENCE:\r\n\r\n● Participation & won in various sports like. Cricket, chess etc.\r\n● Participation in national label committee membership in health & medical.\r\n● Membership with IICHE\r\n● Knowledge about word, power point, excel, etc.\r\n\r\n● Design, production, research & development.\r\n● Working field ( pharmaceutical, fertilizer, polymer, other chemicals production \r\n\r\nFIELD OF INTERESTS :\r\n\r\nindustry.) \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\nPERSONAL PROFILE :\r\n\r\nGender\r\n\r\n      \r\n\r\nDate of Birth\r\n\r\nLanguage known\r\n\r\nNationality \r\n\r\nFather’s name\r\n\r\nMother’s name\r\n\r\nMarital status\r\n\r\nMale\r\n\r\n08-07-1994\r\n\r\nHindi, English\r\n\r\nIndian \r\n\r\nMr Pratap singh\r\n\r\nMrs Parwati devi\r\n\r\nunmarried\r\n\r\nI hereby affirm that the above information is true to the best of my knowledge.                      \r\n\r\n                                                                                                                 Mahipal singh\r\n                                                                         \r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[72,102,"CONTACT"],[126,153,"EMAIL"],[691,704,"PERSON"],[758,769,"LOCATION"],[771,784,"LOCATION"],[786,791,"LOCATION"],[793,801,"LOCATION"],[803,815,"LOCATION"],[816,822,"LOCATION"],[826,836,"LOCATION"],[840,853,"PERSON"],[913,929,"PERSON"],[935,950,"LOCATION"],[951,958,"LOCATION"],[961,976,"LOCATION"],[978,987,"LOCATION"],[989,1000,"LOCATION"],[1003,1013,"LOCATION"],[1113,1152,"EDUCATION"],[1168,1210,"INSTITUTION"],[1211,1219,"LOCATION"],[1222,1228,"LOCATION"],[1253,1263,"LOCATION"],[1280,1305,"EDUCATION"],[1331,1372,"INSTITUTION"],[1374,1381,"LOCATION"],[1396,1409,"EDUCATION"],[1416,1420,"EDUCATION"],[1425,1440,"INSTITUTION"],[1444,1455,"LOCATION"],[1460,1479,"INSTITUTION"],[1677,1684,"DURATION"],[1697,1716,"ORGANISATION"],[1728,1735,"DURATION"],[1748,1780,"ORGANISATION"],[1784,1791,"DURATION"],[1804,1823,"ORGANISATION"],[2032,2037,"ORGANISATION"],[2093,2099,"SKILLS"],[2101,2111,"SKILLS"],[2113,2121,"SKILLS"],[2124,2136,"SKILLS"],[2464,2479,"PERSON"],[2483,2499,"PERSON"],[2734,2747,"PERSON"]]}]]}