{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["RAHUL\r\nEmail: rahulsuneja0001@gmail.com\r\n552-2/32-A, Shivaji Colony, Rohtak, Haryana.\r\nMobile: 07206650504\r\n\r\nObjective:\r\n \r\n\r\nHave depth knowledge of civil engineering principles and theories. Seeking for profile as a \r\nCivil Engineer, where i can use my planning, designing and overseeing skills in \r\nconstruction and help grow the company to achieve its goal.\r\n\r\nEducational Qualifications:\r\n\r\nBachelor’s degree in Civil Engineering from SatPriya Group of Institution\r\n(M.D.U, Rohtak).\r\n\r\nDiploma in Civil Engineering from BITS College of Polytechnic, BHIWANI with 1st \r\nDivision. \r\n\r\n Internship during B.Tech: - Worked 4 months as Site Engineer with IL&FS \r\n\r\nEngineering & Construction Company ltd.\r\n\r\nPROJECT DETAILS\r\n\r\nNAME OF PROJECT:  DLF SECTOR ROAD PROJECT (UNDER PASS), GURGAON\r\nCLIENTS:                      HUDA & DLF\r\nCONSULTANT:            PARSONS BRINKERHOFF\r\nCONTRACTOR:           IL & FS ENGINEERING & CONSTRUCTIO COMPANY LTD.\r\n\r\n“Project work during Internship’’\r\n\r\n Oversee construction and maintenance of facilities.\r\n Handling reports and maps, engineering blueprints and photography etc.\r\n Conducted site survey with seniors and analyzing data to execute civil engineering \r\n\r\nprojects.\r\n\r\n Ensured safety by monitoring the site.\r\n Assisting seniors forecasting the cost, quantity and budgets of equipment, man \r\n\r\npower and labour.\r\nStudying and implementing different construction methods.\r\nStudying structural analysis.\r\nStudying BBS & structure drawing.\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n Execution of BBS with accurate dimensions & adjustment. \r\n Handling labour.\r\n Right use of tools & equipments. \r\n Oversee Shuttering & Casting process.\r\n Curing process & methods adopted.  \r\n\r\n Internship during Diploma: - Worked as a Jr. Engineer Trainee with C&C \r\n\r\nConstruction Pvt. Ltd.\r\n\r\n“Project work during Internship’’\r\n\r\n\f Oversee construction and maintenance of facilities.\r\n Handling reports and maps, engineering blueprints and photography etc.\r\n Conducted site survey with seniors and analyzing data to execute civil engineering \r\n\r\nprojects.\r\n\r\n Ensured safety by monitoring the site.\r\n Assisting seniors forecasting the cost, quantity and budgets of equipment, man \r\n\r\npower and labour.\r\nStudying and implementing different construction methods.\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n Technical Skills:\r\n\r\n MS-Office.\r\n Operating System: WINDOWS 2000/XP/NT/95/98/8/VISTAS\r\n\r\n Excellent Engineering/infrastructure background with excellent computer skills.\r\n\r\nInternet Fundamentals.\r\n\r\n Personal Qualities:\r\n\r\n Natural leadership and team work skills.\r\n Quick learner.\r\n Confident & Active listener.\r\n Excellent Mathematical skills.\r\n Good communication skill.\r\n\r\n Extra Curricular activities:-\r\n\r\n Got 3rd rank in One Act Play in YOUTH FESTIVAL.\r\n Got prize in drawing competitions.\r\n\r\n Personal Details:\r\n\r\nFather’s Name: Om Parkash\r\n\r\n\r\n D.O.B: 1st OCT 1992\r\n\r\nDATE:\r\nSignature: \r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,5,"PERSON"],[14,39,"EMAIL"],[53,67,"LOCATION"],[69,75,"LOCATION"],[77,85,"LOCATION"],[95,106,"CONTACT"],[221,235,"ROLE"],[397,435,"EDUCATION"],[441,470,"INSTITUTION"],[480,486,"LOCATION"],[492,520,"EDUCATION"],[526,553,"INSTITUTION"],[555,562,"LOCATION"],[608,614,"EDUCATION"],[637,650,"ROLE"],[656,705,"ORGANISATION"],[746,769,"PROJECTS"],[823,845,"ORGANISATION"],[858,877,"ORGANISATION"],[901,947,"ORGANISATION"],[1464,1467,"EDUCATION"],[1516,1519,"EDUCATION"],[1743,1763,"ROLE"],[1769,1799,"ORGANISATION"],[2391,2417,"EDUCATION"],[2838,2848,"PERSON"],[2872,2876,"DURATION"]]}]]}