{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["    RESUME\r\n\r\n   Contact no : +91 9978029626\r\nEmail:shakthiraj46@gmail.com\r\n\r\nSATHIYASUNDHARAM. S\r\n#38A,Shanmuga Nagar,\r\nLalpuram&(po),Manalur,\r\nChidambaram(tk),\r\nCuddalore -001\r\n\r\nCareer objective\r\n\r\nAcademic qualification\r\n\r\nSeeking a challenging career in an organization that provides me an opportunity to demonstrate my skills and \r\nimprove my knowledge and be a part of a team that works dynamically towards goal of the Organization.\r\n\r\nQualification\r\n\r\n                  Institution\r\n\r\n Board of Examination\r\n\r\n  Year of\r\n    Study\r\n\r\nPercentage \r\nOf Marks\r\n\r\nDiploma in Electrical & \r\nElectronics Engineering\r\n\r\nAyyappa polytechnic college\r\nAivadhugudi.\r\n\r\nDirectorate of Technical \r\nEducation\r\n\r\n2011-2013\r\n\r\n91.30%\r\n\r\nHSC\r\n\r\nS.S.L.C\r\n\r\nPachaiyppa’s higher secondary \r\nSchool, Chidambaram.\r\n\r\nState board of\r\nExamination. Tamilnadu\r\n\r\n2009-2011\r\n\r\n53%\r\n\r\nRamasamychettiar higher \r\nsecondary school, Chidambaram.\r\n\r\nState board of\r\nExamination. Tamilnadu\r\n\r\n2008-2009\r\n\r\n65 %\r\n\r\nCurrent Organisation \r\n\r\nOrganization: CHENNAI RADHA ENGINEERING WORKS (P) LTD.\r\n\r\n                      Currently working as operation & maintenance of  (Electrical & Electronics)Engineer Adani Port \r\nspecial Economic zone limited Under CREW PVT LTD.\r\n\r\nDesignation: Assistant Engineer.\r\n\r\nDepartment: Engineering.\r\n\r\nExperience: 2014 Till Now \r\n\r\nWork experience\r\n\r\nOrganization: RANE TRW STEERING SYSTEM LTD. \r\n\r\n                          Joint Venture of Rane Group and TRW of United Kingdom. One of the Leading Power Steering \r\ngear & Pump Manufacturer for global passenger car manufacturers like Hyundai, Ford, Tata, Renault, M&M and \r\nDICV.\r\n\r\nDepartment: R & D Product Development.\r\n\r\nExperience: 2013 to 2014\r\n\r\n\fCORE COMPETENCIES:-\r\n\r\napplication of troubleshooting tools\r\n\r\nmalfunctions and corrective actions\r\n\r\nRoles & responsibilities.\r\n\r\nTransformers (6.6KV / 415V)  \r\n\r\nBreaker (800AMPS to 3200AMPS)\r\n\r\n Planning   and   effecting   predictive   &   preventive   maintenance   schedules   for   various   machinery   and\r\n\r\nequipment to increase machine up time & equipment reliability\r\n\r\n Proactively identifying areas of obstruction/ breakdowns and taking steps to rectify the equipments through\r\n\r\n Ensuring   prompt   and   accurate   recording   and   reporting   of   preventive   maintenance   activities,   plant\r\n\r\n Responsible   for   operation   and   maintenance   of   Power   Transformers   (   66KV/11KV),   Distribution\r\n\r\n Responsible for operation and maintenance of Vacuum Circuit Breaker (6.6KV to 11KV) and Air Circuit\r\n\r\n Responsible for operation and maintenance of BATTERY BANK(Lead acid  and Nickel cadmium)\r\n\r\n Responsible for operation and maintenance of EOT(15Ton) and Electric Hoist(2Ton to 10Ton)\r\n\r\n Responsible for operation and maintenance of HT and LT control panel( Transformer feeder, Incomer, Bus\r\n\r\nCoupler and Motor feeder)\r\n\r\n Hands on experience with the conveyor safety devices work such as Pull cord, Sway switch, Zero speed\r\n\r\nswitch and having knowledge with Flap gate design.\r\n\r\n Meticulously kept maintenance records of machines and utilizing them as valuable reference for resolving \r\n\r\nbreakdown issues\r\n\r\n I have sufficient knowledge of Trouble Shooting of  all Electrical Equipment\r\n\r\n Ensuring 100% Preventive Maintenance (PM) & Condition Base Monitoring (CBM)\r\n\r\n Executing Cost Control Management in terms of Manpower\r\n\r\n Planned / Unplanned job execution & Check list, Log books and related records maintaining\r\n\r\n Ensuring Healthy, Safety & Environment.\r\n\r\n Deep understanding of PLC ( ABB AC 800M) programming ladder logic and all aspects of inputs and\r\n\r\noutputs of the system \r\n\r\n Data entry in SAP \r\n\r\n Capable to read and understanding electrical / instrumentation drawings.\r\n\r\n Capable to learning new techniques and technologies as they are discovered.\r\n\r\nNVH Testing\r\n\r\n Vehicle level, System level & Part level Noise measurement.\r\n\r\n Air borne noise and Structure borne measurement in pump.\r\n\r\n\f Pressure pulse& vibration measurement in power steering pump.\r\n\r\n Knowledge on Noise Instruments (Like PROSIG, NOISE METER) \r\n\r\n Knowledge on noise software (Like Dats)\r\n\r\n Skilled in setup of ACCELEROMETERS, MICROPHONE, SPEED SENSORS, PRESSURE \r\n\r\nTRANSDUCERS, THERMOCOUPLES & Other Sensors.\r\n\r\n\fCommunication Address\r\n\r\n#38A,Shanmuga Nagar,\r\n\r\n      Lalpuram&(po),Manalur,\r\nChidambaram(tk),\r\nCuddalore -608001\r\n\r\nProjects\r\n\r\nSoftware proficiency\r\n\r\nDiploma Project: RFID Based voting machine for stop the forgery voting.\r\n\r\n Design packages: AutoCAD, E – CADD.\r\n\r\n Operating System: Windows, Linux.\r\n\r\n Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Power point)\r\n\r\nPersonal Profile\r\n\r\n SAP \r\n\r\nFather’s Name        :  K.Saravanan\r\n\r\nAsserts\r\n\r\nDate Of Birth          :  20/07/1994\r\n\r\n Have much experience to handle customers & vendors globally\r\n\r\nSex                          :  Male\r\n\r\n Good communication skills.\r\n\r\nMartial Status          :  Single\r\n\r\n Eager to learn more technically.\r\n\r\nReligion                  :  Hindu\r\n\r\n Have much experience in power steering product testing & \r\n\r\nNationality              :  Indian \r\n\r\nLanguages Known  : English, Tamil , \r\n                                   Hindi \r\n\r\nExtra Certification courses\r\n\r\ndeveloping \r\n\r\n Quick learner.\r\n\r\nPassport Number     : L7417403\r\n\r\n Diploma in Product Design at CADD centre. (Electrical CADD)\r\n\r\nDeclaration\r\n\r\n                    Hereby, I declare that the above information furnished by me is\r\n\r\ntrue to the best of my knowledge and belief. I assure you that I will execute\r\n\r\nmy work to the fullest satisfaction of my superiors.\r\n\r\n                                                                                 Regards,\r\n\r\nS.Sathiyasundhharam\r\n\r\nPlace: \r\nDate :\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[30,44,"CONTACT"],[52,74,"EMAIL"],[78,97,"PERSON"],[100,118,"LOCATION"],[121,129,"LOCATION"],[135,142,"LOCATION"],[145,156,"LOCATION"],[163,177,"LOCATION"],[567,616,"EDUCATION"],[620,647,"INSTITUTION"],[649,661,"LOCATION"],[665,701,"INSTITUTION"],[728,731,"EDUCATION"],[735,784,"INSTITUTION"],[786,798,"LOCATION"],[831,840,"LOCATION"],[844,853,"DURATION"],[864,906,"INSTITUTION"],[908,920,"LOCATION"],[953,962,"LOCATION"],[966,975,"DURATION"],[1026,1066,"ORGANISATION"],[1113,1122,"ROLE"],[1125,1136,"ROLE"],[1141,1175,"ROLE"],[1176,1186,"ORGANISATION"],[1225,1238,"ORGANISATION"],[1255,1274,"ROLE"],[1367,1398,"ORGANISATION"],[1446,1456,"ORGANISATION"],[1461,1464,"ORGANISATION"],[1589,1596,"ORGANISATION"],[1598,1602,"ORGANISATION"],[1604,1608,"ORGANISATION"],[1610,1617,"ORGANISATION"],[1620,1621,"ORGANISATION"],[1629,1634,"ORGANISATION"],[1650,1676,"ROLE"],[1692,1704,"DURATION"],[2107,2151,"ROLE"],[4182,4196,"SKILLS"],[4198,4208,"SKILLS"],[4210,4223,"SKILLS"],[4225,4249,"SKILLS"],[4251,4264,"SKILLS"],[4316,4330,"LOCATION"],[4341,4349,"LOCATION"],[4355,4362,"LOCATION"],[4365,4376,"LOCATION"],[4383,4400,"LOCATION"],[4457,4482,"PROJECTS"],[4698,4709,"PERSON"],[5301,5326,"EDUCATION"],[5696,5715,"PERSON"]]}]]}