{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["            \r\n\r\npratyushbits@gmail.com\r\n\r\n          \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n                              CURRICULUM VITAE\r\n                                                          \r\n\r\nPRATYUSH KUMAR\r\n\r\nContact Number:  \r\n7562887639, 7319320614\r\n\r\nObjective\r\n\r\nCareer Overview\r\n\r\nEPC projects\r\nManagement\r\n\r\nErection, Loop checking\r\n& Commissioning\r\n\r\nof Power plants\r\n\r\nQuality Assurance\r\n\r\nAreas of Expertise\r\n\r\nI am   seeking   a   challenging   position   in   a   well-established   firm,   where   I   can\r\nimprove myself, my     skills and utilize my well founded work ethics, so as to\r\nhave in the growth of my career.\r\n\r\n \r\n\r\n Total 6 years’ experience in “Maintenance, \r\n\r\nErection & Commissioning fields” in thermal \r\npower plants.\r\n\r\n 5 years worked as a “Instrumentation \r\n\r\nEngineer”.\r\n\r\n 1 Years worked as a “Site Engineer”.\r\n\r\n                                   DETAILS OF SITE ENGINEER EXPERIENCE\r\n\r\n Company  :M/S  Pooja  Electricals  under” ABB INDIA LTD”\r\n\r\n                             \r\n Projects   :- \r\n\r\n[1] India Power corporation limited, Haldia (West Bengal)\r\n\r\n Duration:- 04.10.2015  to  till date.\r\n\r\n        DETAILS OF INSTRUMENTATION ENGINEER EXPERIENCE\r\n\r\n Company: EPS INSTRUMENTATION PVT LTD.\r\n\r\n Projects   :- \r\n\r\n         [1] Talwandi Sabo Power Limited, Banawali, Mansa(Punjab)\r\n\r\n        Duration: - 05.08.2013 to 20.09.2015\r\n\r\n[2] RSTEPL, Dhursar, Pokhran (Rajasthan).\r\n\r\n                 Duration   :- 07.07.2012 to 30.07.2013,\r\n\r\n[3]  Torrent Power Limited, Ahmadabad.\r\n\r\n        Duration   :- 02.10.2011 to 30.06.2012\r\n\r\n Job Profile:- Hands on Experience in Erection & Commissioning of\r\n\r\n DCS System- ABB Symphony Plus, I/O Remote Panel.\r\n\r\n Marshaling   Panels-Interpanel  wiring,  cabling,  termination\r\n\r\nand loop check.\r\n\r\n\f\r\n\r\nField Instrumentation:  Field Instrument Enclosures (FIE),\r\n\r\nLocal   Instrument   Rack   (LIR)   Field   Instruments:   RTD,\r\n\r\nThermocouple,   Pressure   Switch,   ABB   and   ROSMOUNT\r\n\r\nmake -Smart transmitter for measuring – Level, pressure,\r\n\r\nFlow and differential pressure, belt sway switches and pull\r\n\r\nchord switches.\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nInstallation of hydratect 2462 level switches make mobrey\r\n\r\nfor detection of steam and water.\r\n\r\n Control\r\n\r\n  Valves:   Installation   &   Calibration   of\r\n\r\nKeltron, IL, Control valve actuators and Rotork actuators.\r\n\r\n Electrical Erection: Panel Erection, Interpanel wiring,Motor\r\n\r\nErection,DG   Set   Erection,LPBS   Erection,Earthing   work   of\r\n\r\nMotor,Panel\r\n\r\n  and   cable  \r\n\r\ntray,\r\n\r\n  Cable   Tray\r\n\r\nErection,Transformer   Erection,HT   and   LT   Panel\r\n\r\nErection,Control   Panel   Erection,HT   and   LT   Cable\r\n\r\nlaying,Cable   Termination,SPBD   and   NSPBD   Erection   and\r\n\r\nalso   all   type   of   electricals   equipments   work   related\r\n\r\nErection   and   Commissioning   fields   in   thermal   power\r\n\r\nplants.\r\n\r\nACADEMIC CREDENTIALS:\r\n\r\n    Bachelor   of   Engineering   in   “Instrumentation   and   control”   with\r\n\r\n67.50%, in 2011 from RGTU, Bhopal. (MP)\r\n\r\n    Knowledge of hardware, operating systems, application programming. \r\nWindows XP, 2000.Window-7, Microsoft word and Microsoft office Excel.\r\n\r\nPERSONEL SYNOPSIS:\r\n\r\n:    Mr. kishor Upadhyay\r\n:    20/08/1987\r\n:    Indian\r\n:    Single\r\n:    English and Hindi.\r\n\r\nFather’s Name\r\nDate of Birth\r\nNationality\r\nMarital Status\r\nLanguages Known\r\nPermanent Address                   :    Vill.+Post- Khajuria, Via-Barauli,                  \r\n                                                    Dist- Gopalgang(Bihar)\r\n                                                                                                                    \r\nDECLARATION:\r\n \r\nI here by declare that above mentioned information is correct up to my\r\nknowledge   and   I   bear   the   responsibility   for   the   correctness   above   mentioned\r\nparticulars.\r\n\r\nDATE :\r\n\r\nPLACE:                                                                           PRATYUSH KUMAR\r\n\r\n                                                                                    \r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[16,38,"EMAIL"],[171,185,"PERSON"],[208,218,"CONTACT"],[220,230,"CONTACT"],[629,637,"DURATION"],[792,799,"DURATION"],[812,828,"ROLE"],[923,941,"ORGANISATION"],[950,964,"ORGANISATION"],[1023,1054,"ORGANISATION"],[1056,1075,"LOCATION"],[1090,1118,"DURATION"],[1191,1219,"ORGANISATION"],[1253,1283,"PROJECTS"],[1285,1294,"LOCATION"],[1295,1307,"LOCATION"],[1332,1356,"DURATION"],[1364,1370,"ORGANISATION"],[1372,1399,"LOCATION"],[1436,1460,"DURATION"],[1470,1491,"ORGANISATION"],[1493,1503,"LOCATION"],[1529,1553,"DURATION"],[2892,2960,"EDUCATION"],[2992,3009,"LOCATION"],[3188,3207,"PERSON"],[3214,3224,"DURATION"],[3396,3524,"LOCATION"],[3937,3951,"PERSON"]]}]]}