{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["CURRICULUM VITAE\r\n\r\nNAME: RAKESH KUMAR CHAUDHARY\r\nE- MAIL: rakeshkumar.gkp@gmail.com\r\nMOBILE: +91 9616191206\r\n\r\nObjective\r\n\r\nTo   work   an   organization   where   is   exclusive   environment,   health   competition   and   ample\r\nprospects of professional growth. Where I am exposed to all types of work fields, can enhance\r\nmy knowledge and broaden my experience to maximum. In short I just want to be the active part\r\nof development.\r\n\r\nACADEMIC QUALIFICATION\r\n\r\n Graduate\r\n\r\n Computer Diploma in Capital Computer Education (Hardwar, Networking & MS Office)\r\n\r\n ACS Academy For Computer Studies (ADCA One Year MS Office & OA)\r\n\r\nEXPERIENCE SUMMARY\r\n\r\n Company Name     \r\nJob Designation     \r\nJob Duration     \r\n  Company Name     \r\nJob Designation     \r\nJob Duration     \r\n Company Name     \r\nJob Designation     \r\nJob Duration     \r\n\r\n: ANGEL BROKING LTD\r\n: Back office Executive\r\n: July 2007 – April 2008\r\n: GLOBE CAPITAL MARKET LTD\r\n: Back office Executive cum Relation Ship Manager\r\n: 12 July 2008 – 31 May 2010\r\n: KAYNET CAPITAL LTD\r\n: Back office Executive (Clerk)\r\n: 15 October 2010 – Till Date\r\n\r\nEXPERIANCE AND RESPONSIBILITY\r\n\r\n Collect, count, disburse money, do basic bookkeeping and complete banking transactions.\r\n Communicate   with   customers,   employees,   and   other   individuals   to   answer   questions,\r\n\r\ndisseminate or explain information, take order and address complaints.\r\n\r\n Answer telephone, direct calls and take messages.\r\n Compile, copy, sort, and file records of office activities business transaction, and other\r\n\r\nactivities. \r\n\r\n Complete and mail bills, contract policies, invoices, or checks.\r\n Operate office machines, such as photocopiers and scanners, facsimile machines, voice\r\n\r\nmail system and personal computers.\r\n\r\n Compute, record, and proofread data and other information, such as records or reports.\r\n\r\n\f Maintain and update filing, inventory, mailing, and database systems, either manually or\r\n\r\nusing a computer.\r\n\r\n Open, sort and route incoming mail, answer correspondence, and prepare outgoing mail.\r\n Review files, records, and other documents to obtain information to respond to requests.\r\n Deliver message and run errands.\r\n Inventory and order materials, supplies, and services.\r\n Complete work schedules, manage calendars and arrange appointments.\r\n Process   and   prepare   documents,   such   as   business   or   government   forms   and   expense\r\n\r\nreport.\r\n\r\n Monitor and direct the work of lower-level clerks.\r\n Type, format, proofread and edit correspondence and other documents, from notes or\r\n\r\ndictating machines, using computer and typewriters.\r\n\r\n Count, weigh, measure, and/or organize materials.\r\n Train other staff member to perform work activities, such as using computer applications.\r\n Prepare meeting agendas, attend meeting, and record and transcribe minutes.\r\n Troubleshoot   problems   involving   office   equipment,   such   as   computer   hardware   and\r\n\r\nsoftware.\r\n\r\n Make travel arrangements for office personnel                     \r\n\r\nEnglish, Hindi\r\n\r\nLanguage known\r\n\r\nPersonal details\r\n\r\nName \r\nFather Name\r\nMother Name\r\nDate of Birth\r\nMarital Status \r\nSex            \r\nNationality \r\nAddress     \r\n\r\n:  Rakesh Kumar Chaudhary\r\n:  Ram Singhasan Chaudhary\r\n:  Usha Devi\r\n:  18/07/1989\r\n:  Married\r\n:  Male\r\n:  Indian\r\n: Home No.439E Chaksa Husain Pachperwa Gorakhnath Gorakhpur \r\n\r\nDeclaration\r\n\r\nI hereby assure that the above given information are true to the best of my knowledge and\r\nbrief.\r\n\r\n     Place: Gorakhpur       \r\n\r\nYours Faithfully\r\n\r\n     Date: \r\n\r\n                                                          (RAKESH KUMAR CHAUDHARY)\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[26,48,"PERSON"],[59,84,"EMAIL"],[94,108,"CONTACT"],[470,478,"EDUCATION"],[484,530,"EDUCATION"],[532,539,"LOCATION"],[570,602,"EDUCATION"],[850,867,"ORGANISATION"],[869,892,"ROLE"],[896,918,"DURATION"],[922,946,"ORGANISATION"],[950,997,"ROLE"],[1001,1027,"DURATION"],[1031,1049,"ORGANISATION"],[1058,1081,"ROLE"],[1086,1113,"DURATION"],[1152,1182,"SKILLS"],[1243,1286,"SKILLS"],[1422,1471,"SKILLS"],[1475,1533,"SKILLS"],[1587,1629,"SKILLS"],[1655,1678,"SKILLS"],[1785,1842,"SKILLS"],[1993,2050,"SKILLS"],[2082,2124,"SKILLS"],[2210,2264,"SKILLS"],[2268,2335,"SKILLS"],[2339,2451,"SKILLS"],[2457,2499,"SKILLS"],[2511,2648,"SKILLS"],[2654,2796,"SKILLS"],[2800,2875,"SKILLS"],[2879,2943,"SKILLS"],[3236,3258,"PERSON"],[3263,3286,"PERSON"],[3291,3300,"PERSON"],[3351,3408,"LOCATION"],[3655,3677,"PERSON"]]}]]}