{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION","SKILLS"],"annotations":[["COVER LETTER:\r\n\r\nEMAIL: el_supremo1524@outlook.com\r\nMOBILE: 0545207658\r\n\r\nDear Management,\r\n    I am sending this application for the job opening of HRD ADMIN\r\nCOORDINATOR in your organization and providing you all the documents for\r\nfurther consideration. I am aware that my background in administration would\r\nmake me the perfect candidate for your organization. Also, my skill of attention\r\nto detail will definitely prove to be an asset to your company.\r\nI have provided you resume along with this letter, but I would also like to give\r\na brief summary of my qualifications and skills. Worked as an administrative\r\ncapacity for more than two years and have directly worked for document\r\ndistribution and handled it for the maximum time Proficient computer skills\r\nand ability to use multiple emails, word processing and using software\r\npackages for database.\r\nExcellent ability in handling outgoing and incoming mails has always been my\r\nmain responsibility. I would bring this same skill to my current organization.\r\nI am a hardworking and dedicated worker and will never balk at any task,\r\nwhich has been handed over time. I have a good confidentiality, which is\r\nhighly appreciated by my past employers and which would be beneficial for\r\nyour organization as well.\r\nI would like to meet you in person and discuss this opportunity further at your\r\ntime and convenience. You\r\ncan contact me at 0545207658 or e-mail me at el_supremo1524@outlook.com.\r\n\r\nSincerely,\r\nARIES T. NAPIZA\r\n\r\n\f ARIES TANGONAN NAPIZA\r\n\r\nAl Murraqabbat, Dubai, UAE / el_supremo1524@outlook.com / \r\n0545207658 \r\n\r\nHR ADMIN COORDINATOR\r\n\r\nCAREER OBJECTIVE:\r\n\r\n  Under the direction of a Human Resources Manager provides \r\nsupport to the\r\noffice and/or individuals in assigned area of responsibility. Typical\r\nresponsibilities include: answering telephones; responding to \r\ninquiries via\r\nphone ,in-person, or via e-mail; routing calls to appropriate staff; \r\nperforming\r\nrecords maintenance; sorting and distributing mail; running reports;\r\nand,\r\nperforming other support functions as necessary.\r\n\r\nKEY SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE:\r\n\r\n Customer service principles;\r\n Modern office procedures, methods, and equipment;\r\n Basic filing and record keeping principles.\r\n Demonstrated Skill in:\r\n Providing customer service;\r\n Filing;\r\n Keyboarding;\r\n Using modern office equipment;\r\n Working with diverse academic, cultural and ethnic \r\n\r\nbackgrounds of\r\n\r\n community college students and staff;\r\n Utilizing computer technology used for communication, data \r\n\r\ngathering\r\n\r\n and reporting;\r\n\r\n\f Communicating effectively through oral and written mediums.\r\n\r\nEXPERIENCE:\r\n\r\n MAGIC MEMORIES:\r\n\r\n             GUEST ASSOCIATE PHOTOGRAPHER (CUSTOMER SERVICE \r\nREPRESENTATIVE)\r\n             DUBAI, UAE\r\n             SEPTEMBER 2016 – JUNE 2018\r\n\r\n DALMA MALL MANAGEMENT \r\n       HR ADMIN COORDINATOR\r\n\r\n              ABU DHABI, UAE\r\n              JANUARY 2015 – APRIL 2016\r\n\r\n NATIONAL CORPORATIONS FOR TORISM AND HOTELS\r\n\r\nHR ASSISTANT\r\n\r\n              ABU DHABI, UAE\r\n              DECEMBER 2012 – DECEMBER 2014\r\n\r\n RURAL BANK OF MABITAC \r\n\r\nPRODUCT MARKETING AND PHILIPPINES COLLECTIONS MANAGER\r\n\r\n              CALAMBA CITY, LAGUNA, \r\n              DECEMBER 2010 – MAY 2012\r\n\r\n WALTER MART DEPARTMENT STORE \r\n\r\n              ASSISTANT HR SUPERVISOR \r\n              CALAMBA CITY, LAGUNA, PHILIPPINES\r\n              MAY 2010 – NOVEMBER 2010\r\n\r\n LEADENCE CORPORATION PHILIPPINES\r\n\r\n               LINE TECHNICAL SUPERVISOR\r\n              CALAMBA CITY, LAGUNA, PHILIPPINES\r\n              JULY 2007 – MARCH 2010\r\n\r\n EDUCATIONAL ATTAINMENTS:\r\n\r\n              DUALTECH CENTER ELECTRO MECHANICS TECHNOLOGY\r\n              2004 – 2006\r\n\r\n UNIVERSITY OF PERPETUAL HELP\r\n BS BUSINESS MANAGEMENT\r\n\r\n              2001 - 2004\r\n\r\nPERSONAL INFORMATIONS:\r\n\r\n DATE OF BIRTH:             MARCH 25, 1985\r\n PLACE OF BIRTH:           CALAMBA, LAGUNA,PHILIPPINES\r\n\r\n\f NATIONALITY:                FILIPINO\r\n AGE:                                  33\r\n MARITAL STATUS:           SINGLE\r\n GENDER:                          MALE\r\n RELIGION:                       CATHOLIC\r\n VISA STATUS:                   RESIDENCE VISA\r\n VALID UNTIL:                  JUNE 2018\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[24,50,"EMAIL"],[60,70,"CONTACT"],[149,171,"ROLE"],[642,651,"DURATION"],[1399,1409,"CONTACT"],[1426,1453,"EMAIL"],[1531,1536,"LOCATION"],[1538,1541,"LOCATION"],[1544,1570,"EMAIL"],[1575,1585,"CONTACT"],[1590,1610,"ROLE"],[2105,2132,"SKILLS"],[2137,2161,"SKILLS"],[2263,2289,"SKILLS"],[2305,2316,"SKILLS"],[2650,2664,"ORGANISATION"],[2682,2710,"ROLE"],[2712,2745,"ROLE"],[2761,2766,"LOCATION"],[2768,2771,"LOCATION"],[2786,2812,"DURATION"],[2887,2896,"LOCATION"],[2898,2901,"LOCATION"],[2917,2942,"DURATION"],[2948,2991,"ORGANISATION"],[2995,3007,"ROLE"],[3025,3034,"LOCATION"],[3036,3039,"LOCATION"],[3055,3084,"DURATION"],[3090,3111,"ORGANISATION"],[3138,3169,"ORGANISATION"],[3187,3199,"LOCATION"],[3201,3207,"LOCATION"],[3225,3249,"DURATION"],[3255,3283,"ORGANISATION"],[3302,3325,"ROLE"],[3342,3354,"LOCATION"],[3356,3362,"LOCATION"],[3364,3375,"LOCATION"],[3391,3415,"DURATION"],[3421,3441,"ORGANISATION"],[3442,3453,"LOCATION"],[3472,3497,"ROLE"],[3513,3525,"LOCATION"],[3527,3533,"LOCATION"],[3535,3546,"LOCATION"],[3562,3584,"DURATION"],[3632,3676,"INSTITUTION"],[3692,3703,"DURATION"],[3709,3762,"INSTITUTION"],[3780,3791,"DURATION"],[3894,3901,"LOCATION"],[3903,3909,"LOCATION"],[3910,3921,"LOCATION"]]}]]}