{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["CURRICULUM VITAE\r\n\r\n                                                                                                           \r\n\r\nP.MANOJ\r\nS/O. S. Prabhakar,\r\nPlot No: 172,Venkateshwara Nagar,                p.manoj@ymail.com\r\n1ST Street, Pozichalur,\r\nChennai - 600 074.\r\n\r\n                      \r\n\r\nContacts:\r\n\r\nMob.no: +919566299790            \r\n\r\nCAREER OBJECTIVE:\r\n\r\nDesign Engineer (Switchgear Industry) in your illustrious organization.\r\n\r\nTo pursue a responsible and challenging career as Estimation or \r\n\r\nPROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:\r\n\r\nSUMMARY:\r\n                  Have around 7 years of experience in the field of Electrical Estimation or \r\nDesign Engineering (Switchgear Industry). A competent Electrical Estimation or \r\nDesign Engineer with a comprehensive knowledge of designing, developing and \r\nmaintaining electrical systems and components to required specifications. Have \r\nconsistent track record of successfully completing projects from the concept and detail of \r\nthe design through to implementation and handover. I am familiar with Eaton, Schneider \r\nElectric, L&T, ABB and Siemens make.\r\n\r\nPREVIOUS COMPANY  1 OF 6:\r\n\r\nExcel Metal Industries, Doha-Qatar.\r\n\r\nDESIGNATION:\r\n\r\nEstimation Engineer (Switchgear Industry)\r\n\r\nDURATION:\r\n\r\n 2016.\r\n\r\n1 of 6\r\n\r\n\fPREVIOUS COMPANY  2 OF 6:\r\n\r\nQatari German Switchgear Company W.L.L., Doha-Qatar.\r\n\r\nDESIGNATION:\r\n\r\nEstimation Engineer (Switchgear Industry)\r\n\r\nDURATION:\r\n\r\n 2015.\r\n\r\nPREVIOUS COMPANY  3 OF 6:\r\n\r\nBaliga Lighting Equipments Pvt. Ltd., Chennai-India.\r\n\r\nDESIGNATION:\r\n\r\nEngineer-Panel Design (Switchgear Industry)\r\n\r\nDURATION:\r\n\r\n 2014.\r\n\r\nPREVIOUS COMPANY  4 OF 6:\r\n\r\nDiplomat Switchgear, Doha-Qatar.\r\n\r\nDESIGNATION:\r\n\r\nDesign Engineer (Switchgear Industry) & \r\nISO Deputy Management Representative for Quality\r\nManagement System (ISO 9001:2008).\r\n\r\nDURATION:\r\n\r\n 2011 to 2013.\r\n\r\nPREVIOUS COMPANY  5 OF 6:\r\n\r\nHensel Electric India Pvt. Ltd., Chennai-India.\r\n\r\nDESIGNATION:\r\n\r\nDesign Engineer (Switchgear Industry)\r\n\r\nDURATION:\r\n\r\n 2009 to 2011.\r\n\r\n2 of 6\r\n\r\n\fPREVIOUS COMPANY  6 OF 6:\r\n\r\nAreva T&D India Ltd., Chennai-India.\r\n\r\nDESIGNATION:\r\n\r\nTrainee Design Engineer\r\n\r\nDURATION:\r\n\r\n2007 to 2008.\r\n\r\nWORK PROCEDURE:\r\n\r\n Studying the specification received along with the project.\r\n Preparation of General Arrangement (GA) drawing as per the \r\ncustomer requirement. Taking care of switchgear components \r\nto achieve spacious and aesthetic design for the customer. \r\n Preparation of Single line diagrams, Power/Instrument wiring \r\ndiagrams, Control circuit wiring diagram for various control \r\nschemes as per the customer specification/requirement.\r\n\r\n Preparing Estimation for the products designed.\r\n After receiving Order, checking PO and releasing to Sales \r\n\r\n Coordinating with Purchase, Production & Testing department.\r\n Coordinating with design team to produce more work for \r\n\r\n Maintaining a good human relationship with Sales Engineers.\r\n Preparation of As-Built drawings to confirm the locality of all \r\n\r\ndepartment.\r\n\r\nmanufacturing. \r\n\r\ndevices at site.\r\n\r\n Preparation of operation and maintenance manual while \r\n\r\nhandling over project.\r\n Maintained ISO document.\r\n\r\nPROJECTS HANDLED:\r\n\r\n PROPOSED RUBBER FACTORY.\r\n 6 VILLAS COMPOUND. \r\n LUCKY STAR ALUMINUM FACTORY.\r\n PROPOSED AL KHOR HOUSING PROJECT.\r\n\r\n3 of 6\r\n\r\n\f QREIC MIXED USE BUILDINGS AT MESAIED COMM. \r\n\r\nAND RES BUILDINGS (G+M+3).\r\n SHARA TOWER 2B+G+1ST+28.\r\n OFFICE TOWER (3B+G+14F) at OLD SALATA. \r\n MUSHREIB HEART OF DOHA-PHASE 1B.\r\n PROPOSED DEVELOPMENT OF BARZAN CAMP-PHASE \r\n\r\n2 E1-MOSQUE.\r\n\r\n DPS MODERN INDIAN SCHOOL AT AL WAKRA.\r\n HOTEL APARTMENT BUILDING (2B+G+5 FLOOR).\r\n 2B+G+PODIUM+25 HOTEL BUILDING.\r\n PROPOSED CBQ LANDSCAPING AND UNDERGROUND \r\n\r\nPARKING (3B+G).\r\n\r\n BIN SAMIKH HOTEL-3B + G + M + 40 FLOORS.\r\n\r\nEDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS:\r\n\r\nB.E.(Electrical & Electronics):\r\n\r\n College          : SRM Valliammai Engineering College.\r\n University      : Anna University\r\n Class              : I st Class\r\n Duration      : 2003 – 2007.\r\n\r\nH.S.C:\r\n\r\n School            : Sri Sankara Vidhyalaya Matric.hr sec School.\r\n Class              : I st Class\r\n Duration      : 2002 – 2003.\r\n\r\nCERTIFICATES RELATED TO MY WORK:\r\n\r\n I got Expertise of switchgear industry certificate given by \r\n\r\nGJ Switchgear Consultant.\r\n\r\n I got Autocad - Electrical certificate given by GJ Switchgear \r\n\r\nConsultant.\r\n\r\nAREAS OF INTEREST:\r\n\r\n Power system protection design.\r\n\r\n Design & Estimation of panels like MVP, MCC, SMDB, DB, \r\n\r\nLCP, Feeder Pillars, Capacitor Bank, etc. \r\n\r\n4 of 6\r\n\r\n\fPERSONAL SKILLS:\r\n\r\n Designing skill.\r\n Highly motivated to work as a team.\r\n Innovative and Result Oriented.\r\n Quick learner.\r\n\r\nSOFTWARE EXPOSURE:\r\n\r\n Programming Languages\r\n\r\n:  C,   C++ \r\n\r\nlanguages   &\r\n\r\nAutocad.\r\n\r\n Operating System\r\n\r\n:  MS   office,   Windows   XP,\r\n\r\n1998/2000, Windows 7, MS- DOS.          \r\n\r\nACEDEMIC PROJECT DETAILS:\r\n\r\nPROJECT DONE IN THE BACHELOR DEGREE:\r\n\r\nProject title : Submitted a study project on “COMPUTERISED TESTING OF STATIC \r\nCTMM MOTOR PROTECTION RELAY” at AREVA T&D INDIA Limited, Pallavaram, \r\nChennai.\r\n\r\nTeam size\r\n\r\n: 3\r\n\r\nObjectives\r\n\r\n: Protection of Motor using Static CTMM Relays.\r\n\r\nDescription : In Early days the manual testing takes lot of time and shows inaccurate \r\nresults under certain conditions and also with limited specifications and tolerance levels \r\nfor testing of relays, these drawbacks can be overcome by using computerized testing \r\nwith EPOCH equipment.              \r\n\r\n5 of 6\r\n\r\n\f                Now a days high rating motors can be protected by using newly introduced \r\nCTMM relay. Our main aim in this project is to protect different kinds of motor by using \r\nCTMM static relay with EPOCH.\r\n\r\nLanguages known\r\n\r\nEnglish, Tamil.\r\n\r\nPERSONEL PROFILE\r\n\r\nName\r\n\r\nDate of Birth\r\n\r\nGender\r\n\r\nMarital status\r\n\r\nNationality\r\n\r\nHobbies\r\n\r\nFather’s name\r\n\r\nMother’s name\r\n\r\nPermanent address\r\n\r\nDECLARATION\r\n\r\nP.MANOJ\r\n\r\n27/01/1986\r\n\r\nMale\r\n\r\nSingle\r\n\r\nINDIAN\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\n: \r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\nListening to music, Playing cricket.\r\n\r\nS.PRABHAKAR\r\n\r\nP.BANUMATHI\r\n\r\nPlot No: 172,Venkateshwara Nagar,\r\n1ST Street, Pozichalur,\r\nChennai - 600 074.\r\n\r\nI hereby declare that all the information furnished above is true, correct and complete to \r\nthe best of my knowledge.\r\n\r\nPlace:\r\n\r\n          Yours Sincerely,\r\n\r\nDate:                                                                                        \r\n                                                                                                Manoj.P    \r\n\r\n6 of 6\r\n\r\n\f7 of 6\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[131,138,"PERSON"],[145,157,"PERSON"],[173,192,"LOCATION"],[209,226,"EMAIL"],[253,260,"LOCATION"],[322,335,"CONTACT"],[372,387,"ROLE"],[1051,1056,"ORGANISATION"],[1058,1078,"ORGANISATION"],[1080,1083,"ORGANISATION"],[1085,1088,"ORGANISATION"],[1093,1100,"ORGANISATION"],[1139,1161,"ORGANISATION"],[1163,1174,"LOCATION"],[1194,1213,"ROLE"],[1253,1258,"DURATION"],[1302,1341,"ORGANISATION"],[1343,1354,"LOCATION"],[1374,1393,"ROLE"],[1433,1438,"DURATION"],[1471,1507,"ORGANISATION"],[1509,1523,"LOCATION"],[1543,1564,"ROLE"],[1604,1609,"DURATION"],[1642,1661,"ORGANISATION"],[1663,1674,"LOCATION"],[1694,1709,"ROLE"],[1736,1772,"ROLE"],[1838,1851,"DURATION"],[1884,1915,"ORGANISATION"],[1917,1931,"LOCATION"],[1951,1966,"ROLE"],[2006,2019,"DURATION"],[2063,2083,"ORGANISATION"],[2085,2099,"LOCATION"],[2127,2142,"ROLE"],[2159,2172,"DURATION"],[3193,3217,"PROJECTS"],[3223,3239,"PROJECTS"],[3244,3272,"PROJECTS"],[3285,3309,"PROJECTS"],[3403,3414,"PROJECTS"],[3431,3443,"PROJECTS"],[3474,3506,"PROJECTS"],[3534,3568,"PROJECTS"],[3693,3745,"PROJECTS"],[3834,3864,"EDUCATION"],[3890,3925,"INSTITUTION"],[3947,3962,"INSTITUTION"],[4017,4029,"DURATION"],[4065,4109,"INSTITUTION"],[4164,4176,"DURATION"],[4224,4256,"CERTIFICATE"],[4319,4351,"CERTIFICATE"],[4593,4609,"SKILLS"],[4757,4758,"SKILLS"],[4762,4765,"SKILLS"],[4787,4795,"SKILLS"],[4824,4835,"SKILLS"],[4839,4851,"SKILLS"],[4867,4876,"SKILLS"],[4878,4886,"SKILLS"],[5014,5076,"PROJECTS"],[5080,5103,"ORGANISATION"],[5105,5115,"LOCATION"],[5119,5127,"LOCATION"],[5956,5963,"PERSON"],[6100,6111,"PERSON"],[6115,6126,"PERSON"],[6190,6197,"LOCATION"]]}]]}