{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["CURRICULAM VITAE\r\n\r\nMOHD. WASEEM\r\nS/O Shri Saleem Ahmad\r\nMoh Chak-Swar\r\nPost-Swar\r\nTeh-Swar\r\nDistt-Rampur\r\nPin Code-244924\r\nMob- 07500129653, 8868075861\r\nE-Mail :-mohdwaseem96@gmail.com\r\n\r\nCAREER OBJECTIVE\r\n\r\n Looking   For   A   Challenging   Job   Where   I   Can   Reach   Infinite   Success   In\r\nProfessional Field With Full Effectiveness And Hard Work For The Growth Of\r\nAn Organization Along With Improvement In My Own Professional Skill.\r\n\r\nEDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION\r\n\r\n M.S.W. Passes From SHIATS DEEMED University in 2016.\r\n B.Com Passed From M.J.P Rohilkhand University Bareilly In 2011.\r\n Intermediate Passed From U.P. Board In 2008.\r\n High School Passed From U.P. Board In 2006.\r\n\r\nPROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION\r\n\r\n One   Year  Corporate   Accounts   Professional  Plus  Course   Form   “Institute   Of\r\nManagement And Professional Accounts Training” (Impact Education)  At\r\nKashipur.\r\n\r\nAREAS COVERED\r\n\r\n Basic Awareness Of Computer & Operating Software (M.S. Dos & Windows)\r\n M.S. Office-(M.s. Word, M.s. Excel, M.s. Power Point)\r\n Internet\r\n Fundamental Account\r\n Computerize Accounting Software (Tally 9.0 & 7.2)\r\n\r\nOTHER QUALIFICATION\r\n\r\n 1 Year Certificate In Computer Application (Basic Computer) From I.C.S.E.S \r\n\r\nRampur (U.P.)\r\n\r\nEXPERIENCE\r\n\r\n 3 Year Experience as a Accountant + Monitoring & Evaluation Officer in T.I \r\n\r\nProject under Uttar Pradesh State AIDS Control Society.\r\n \r\n\r\n\fEXTRA ACTIVITIES\r\n\r\n A workshop attends on Capacity Building of UPSACS TG. T.I. Project by \r\n\r\nVoluntary Health Service MSA DIVA.\r\n\r\n Awarded by Distt. Hospital Rampur for Supporting Blood Donor day Activities\r\n\r\nREFRENCES\r\n\r\n Mr. Mohammad Alam :Project Manager Targeted Intervention Project \r\n\r\n Navnit   Gulati   :Project   Officer   Chetna   Sewa   Sansthan   Rampur\r\n\r\nRampur.U.P.\r\nContact No.:- 9761747401 \r\n\r\nU.P.\r\nContact No.:-9557038902\r\n\r\nPERSONAL DETAILES\r\n \r\nFather’s Name \r\nDate of Birth\r\nPermanent Address\r\n\r\n :-   \r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\n\r\nNationality\r\nMarital Status\r\nLanguage Known\r\n\r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\n\r\nShri Saleem Ahmad\r\n08 July 1991\r\nMoh. Chak Swar\r\nPost- Swar\r\nTeh- Swar\r\nDistt- Rampur\r\nPin- 244924 (Uttar Pradesh)\r\nIndian\r\nUnmarried\r\nHindi, English, Urdu\r\n\r\nDECLARATION\r\nI Here By Declare That My All Above Information’s Are true and Correct in the Best of \r\nMy Knowledge and Belief.\r\n\r\nDate:-\r\n\r\nTime:-\r\n\r\n(MOHD. WASEEM)\r\n\r\n\f\f",{"entities":[[20,32,"PERSON"],[43,55,"PERSON"],[93,105,"LOCATION"],[129,140,"CONTACT"],[142,152,"CONTACT"],[162,185,"EMAIL"],[481,487,"EDUCATION"],[500,524,"INSTITUTION"],[537,542,"EDUCATION"],[555,582,"INSTITUTION"],[583,591,"LOCATION"],[595,600,"DURATION"],[604,616,"EDUCATION"],[629,639,"INSTITUTION"],[643,648,"DURATION"],[652,663,"EDUCATION"],[676,686,"INSTITUTION"],[690,695,"DURATION"],[802,865,"INSTITUTION"],[890,899,"LOCATION"],[972,980,"SKILLS"],[983,990,"SKILLS"],[995,1007,"SKILLS"],[1008,1017,"SKILLS"],[1019,1029,"SKILLS"],[1031,1047,"SKILLS"],[1064,1083,"SKILLS"],[1087,1118,"SKILLS"],[1120,1129,"SKILLS"],[1165,1207,"CERTIFICATE"],[1230,1239,"INSTITUTION"],[1244,1250,"LOCATION"],[1252,1256,"LOCATION"],[1277,1283,"DURATION"],[1300,1344,"ROLE"],[1348,1363,"PROJECTS"],[1370,1411,"ORGANISATION"],[1786,1792,"LOCATION"],[1796,1807,"LOCATION"],[1823,1833,"CONTACT"],[1838,1842,"LOCATION"],[1856,1867,"CONTACT"],[2022,2039,"PERSON"],[2101,2107,"LOCATION"],[2331,2343,"PERSON"]]}]]}