{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Resume\r\n\r\nC/O Transguard LLC Staff Accommodation\r\nAlquoz\r\n+97-0526510142\r\nrahulkumar.dun@gmail.com\r\n\r\nRAHUL KUMAR\r\n\r\nOBJECTIVE\r\n\r\n“To excel in my profession and contribute towards the growth of a multifunctional\r\norganization resulting increase in profits of the stakeholders both as an organization\r\nand an individual.”\r\n\r\nINDUSTRIAL TRAINING\r\n\r\nOrganization\r\n\r\nWebtel Electrosoft Pvt. Ltd.\r\n\r\nVikrant Tower,  Rajendar place,  New Delhi.\r\n\r\nDepartment                   \r\nDesignation                   \r\nDuration                        20th of july 2012 to 25th of September 2012.\r\nResponsibilities             \r\n\r\nMarketing (West Delhi).\r\nManagement Trainee.\r\n\r\nTo coordinate various other members in my team.\r\n\r\nTo coordinate with various direct marketing activities.\r\nTo coordinate with various sales promotion activities.\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nNov 2013-Dec 2014\r\n\r\nAPLHA ENGINEERS\r\n\r\nAlpha   Engineers   designs,   supplies,   install   and   provide\r\nservices   for   all   types   of   air   conditioning   and   ventilation\r\nsystems   in   the   domestic   and   commercial   market. The\r\ncompany’s   vision   is   to   become   a   leading   supplier   of   air\r\nconditioning   in   the   north   region   by   providing   honest,\r\ncompetent and personal customer service.\r\n\r\nDesignation\r\n\r\nExecutive Sales & Marketing\r\n\r\nJob Responsibilities\r\n\r\n- New Market Development for Air conditioning biz\r\n\r\n-Dealing with Architects, Consultant& Customers.\r\n-Enquiry Generation, Quotation submission on monthly sales \r\n\r\ntarget basis.\r\n\r\nFeb 2015-July 2015\r\n\r\nPERIL MANAGEMENT SERVICES\r\n\r\nEC ROAD, DEHRADUN UTTARAKHAND\r\n\r\n\fPeril management services is Risk control unit (RCU) Agency,\r\nwork for different banks.\r\n\r\nDesignation\r\n\r\nOffice Administration\r\n\r\nJob Responsibilities\r\nperiod.\r\nJuly 2015-Septmber 2015\r\n\r\nZhejiang, China.\r\n\r\nPreparing MIS report on daily basis and in given TAT \r\n\r\nZhejiang Homebase Industrial Co.,Ltd.\r\nQinggang Science-Technology Industrila Park, Yuhuan \r\n\r\nA Leading manufacturer and exporter of deep well \r\nsubmersible pumps, towel heater and valves.\r\n\r\nDesignation \r\n\r\nInternational Sales Executive (submersible pumps).\r\n\r\nJob Responsibilities\r\n\r\nTo find out the new customers in market.\r\nTo coordinate with various sales promotion activities.\r\nTo coordinate with various others members in my team and \r\nresearch and sales department.\r\nTo maintain different market research report.\r\n\r\nDecember 2015-Till Date\r\n\r\nTransguard group LLC.\r\n\r\nH.O. Emirates group security, Head Quarters, B Wing, 1 \r\n\r\nFloor\r\n\r\nDubai Airport Freezone, P.O. Box 22630, Dubai UAE.\r\n\r\nDesignation\r\n\r\nSecurity officer\r\n\r\nJob Responsibilities\r\n\r\nSafety and Security of the given premises.\r\n\r\nHandling the team of 3-5 persons.\r\nCustomer Care service.\r\n\r\nPROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATIONS\r\n\r\nMasters In Business Administration (MBA)\r\nDelhi.\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\nNBA   School   of   Business,   New\r\n\r\nAffiliated to Maharishi Dayanand University\r\n(MDU), Rohtak in 2013.\r\n:\r\n\r\nMarketing   (Major)&   International\r\n\r\nSpecialization\r\nBusiness (Minor).      \r\n\r\nBachelor of Commerce (B.Com.)\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\nH.N.B Gharwal University in 2011.\r\n\r\nACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS\r\n\r\nIntermediate (12th)\r\nDehradun, Uttarakhand.\r\n\r\nHigh School (10th)\r\nDehradun, Uttarakhand.\r\n\r\nCOMPUTER PROFICIENCY \r\n\r\nC.B.S.E.  from Children’s Academy school, \r\n\r\n           C.B.S.E.  from Children’s Academy school, \r\n\r\n Well versed in Operating System (Windows-98, XP, Vista, Windows-7, 8).\r\n\r\n\f Proficiency in entire MS-Office Suit. \r\n\r\n Sound understanding of Internet Tools.\r\n\r\n Knowledge of Tally (Diploma).\r\n\r\n Completed 1yr course of Computer Basic Knowledge.\r\n\r\nEXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES \r\n\r\n Participated as in Boxing Competition – Inter School\r\n\r\n Participated as in Cricket Tournament – Inter School\r\n\r\n NCC Certification\r\n\r\n Six Sigma Certification -Yellow Belt\r\n\r\nPERSONAL DETAILS\r\n\r\nDate of Birth\r\nFather’s Name\r\nNationality\r\n\r\n:\r\n:\r\nIndian\r\n\r\n:\r\n\r\n20th September 1986\r\nMr. PhoolSingh\r\n\r\nDate:\r\nPlace:\r\n\r\n(RAHUL KUMAR)\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[58,72,"CONTACT"],[74,98,"EMAIL"],[102,113,"PERSON"],[363,391,"ORGANISATION"],[428,438,"LOCATION"],[537,581,"DURATION"],[632,637,"LOCATION"],[641,660,"ROLE"],[849,866,"DURATION"],[870,885,"ORGANISATION"],[1300,1327,"ROLE"],[1538,1556,"DURATION"],[1560,1585,"ORGANISATION"],[1598,1606,"LOCATION"],[1607,1618,"LOCATION"],[1729,1750,"ROLE"],[1785,1808,"DURATION"],[1812,1820,"LOCATION"],[1822,1828,"LOCATION"],[1889,1926,"ORGANISATION"],[1973,1979,"LOCATION"],[2098,2127,"ROLE"],[2414,2437,"DURATION"],[2441,2462,"ORGANISATION"],[2574,2579,"LOCATION"],[2580,2584,"LOCATION"],[2603,2619,"ROLE"],[2785,2819,"EDUCATION"],[2821,2824,"EDUCATION"],[2842,2870,"INSTITUTION"],[2895,2924,"INSTITUTION"],[2933,2939,"LOCATION"],[2943,2948,"DURATION"],[3038,3058,"EDUCATION"],[3060,3066,"EDUCATION"],[3076,3100,"INSTITUTION"],[3104,3109,"DURATION"],[3140,3152,"EDUCATION"],[3154,3158,"EDUCATION"],[3171,3183,"LOCATION"],[3187,3198,"EDUCATION"],[3200,3204,"EDUCATION"],[3217,3229,"LOCATION"],[3258,3266,"INSTITUTION"],[3315,3323,"INSTITUTION"],[3396,3406,"SKILLS"],[3408,3410,"SKILLS"],[3412,3417,"SKILLS"],[3419,3428,"SKILLS"],[3462,3471,"SKILLS"],[3541,3546,"SKILLS"],[3936,3950,"PERSON"],[3972,3983,"PERSON"]]}]]}