{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Mohammad Burhan Sofi\r\nSrinagar, Jammu and Kashmir\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Mohammad-Burhan-Sofi/6d02911da47808c7\r\n\r\nTo attain the peak of success with my hard work and potential in shortest possible time. To \r\nyield better work prospective to the organization and a competitive working environment to \r\nmy subordinates with full encouragement and whole-hearted participation.\r\n\r\nPersonal Details\r\n\r\nDate of Birth: 2002-05-21\r\nEligible to work in: India, Switzerland, United Arab Emirates, United Kingdom, United States Minor\r\nOutlying Islands\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nMarketing Executive\r\nField Work\r\nDecember 2021 to Present\r\n\r\nField Boy\r\n\r\nSalesman\r\nGrocery - Srinagar, Jammu and Kashmir\r\nMarch 2020 to December 2021\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nHigher Secondary(12th Pass) in Commerce\r\nGovt. Boys Higher secondary School - Srinagar, Jammu and Kashmir\r\nMarch 2019 to February 2021\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Good Communication \r\n\r\nPassionate to learn and explore new things \r\nAbility to adapt any situation and learn from it \r\nCan effectively gel into a team as well as lead and motivate \r\nGood inter-personal and people management skills \r\nPositive attitude and work oriented \r\nExpertise in achieving customer satisfaction\r\n\r\n• Sales\r\n\r\n• Marketing\r\n\r\n• Communication skills\r\n\r\n• Business development\r\n\r\n\fLanguages\r\n\r\n• English - Intermediate\r\n• Urdu - Fluent\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,20,"PERSON"],[22,30,"LOCATION"],[32,49,"LOCATION"],[468,473,"LOCATION"],[475,486,"LOCATION"],[488,508,"LOCATION"],[510,524,"LOCATION"],[526,539,"LOCATION"],[586,605,"ROLE"],[619,643,"DURATION"],[660,677,"ROLE"],[680,688,"LOCATION"],[690,695,"LOCATION"],[700,707,"LOCATION"],[709,736,"DURATION"],[740,780,"EDUCATION"],[784,828,"INSTITUTION"],[831,839,"LOCATION"],[841,846,"LOCATION"],[851,858,"LOCATION"],[860,887,"DURATION"],[915,933,"SKILLS"],[1148,1165,"SKILLS"],[1236,1241,"SKILLS"],[1247,1256,"SKILLS"],[1262,1282,"SKILLS"],[1288,1322,"SKILLS"]]}]]}