{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Laxman Singh\r\nRampura, basti, IN\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Laxman-Singh/e7b71d5913cefff0\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nsales and marketing\r\nBikaji food pvt ltd - Rajasthan\r\n2007 to Present\r\n\r\nStore keeper work maal loding and 30\r\n\r\nSales and marketing telecom\r\nR k enterprises - Bikaner, Rajasthan\r\n2008 to December 2021\r\n\r\nLanguage\r\nCustomer relationship and field 1jun2020\r\nEnglish .Hindi.panjabe marketing\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nB.A\r\nMaha raja gagasingh university\r\n2007\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Sales and marketing\r\n\r\n• Sales\r\n\r\n• Marketing\r\n\r\n• Communication skills\r\n\r\n• Customer service\r\n\r\n• Business development\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,21,"PERSON"],[23,28,"LOCATION"],[207,216,"LOCATION"],[218,233,"DURATION"],[324,331,"LOCATION"],[333,342,"LOCATION"],[344,365,"DURATION"],[411,419,"DURATION"],[470,473,"EDUCATION"],[475,505,"INSTITUTION"],[507,511,"DURATION"],[539,558,"ROLE"],[564,569,"ROLE"],[575,584,"ROLE"],[590,610,"SKILLS"],[616,632,"SKILLS"],[638,658,"SKILLS"]]}]]}