{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Haridh TH\nTrichur, Kerala\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Haridh-TH/5c3f925fc2afff66\n\nI want to put to use my creative skills in marketing that I am familiar with innovative thoughts that will\nbenefit the organization in the long run.\n\nWork Experience\n\nMarketing Executive\nFisia Italimpianti S.p.A. - Abu Dhabi\nJune 1995 to July 2015\n\nEducation\n\nDiploma in Marketing\nIIM Kozhikod - Kerala\nMarch 2006 to August 2008\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• Business development\n\n• Communication skills\n\n• Computer skills\n\n• Customer service\n\n• Marketing\n\n• Microsoft Excel\n\n• Negotiation\n\n• Sales\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,9,"PERSON"],[19,25,"LOCATION"],[266,285,"ROLE"],[286,311,"ORGANISATION"],[314,323,"LOCATION"],[324,346,"DURATION"],[359,379,"EDUCATION"],[380,392,"INSTITUTION"],[395,401,"LOCATION"],[402,427,"DURATION"],[451,471,"SKILLS"],[475,495,"SKILLS"],[499,514,"SKILLS"],[518,534,"SKILLS"],[538,547,"SKILLS"],[551,566,"SKILLS"],[570,581,"SKILLS"],[585,590,"SKILLS"]]}]]}