{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Himanshu Singh\nMumbai, Maharashtra\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Himanshu-Singh/13cff53b0612a4de\n\nPersonal Details\n\nDate of Birth: 1998-12-10\nEligible to work in: India\nHighest Career Level: 1-2 years experience\nIndustry: NGO, Social Services, Regulators, Industry Associations\nTotal years of experience: 2\n\nWork Experience\n\nMarketing Executive\nLight of Life Trust\nOctober 2019 to December 2021\n\nEducation\n\nBachelor's in Finance & Marketing\nMumbai University - Mumbai, Maharashtra\nAugust 2016 to July 2019\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• Marketing\n\n• Communication skills\n\n• Computer skills\n\n• Microsoft Excel\n\n• Sales\n\n• Business development\n\n• Customer service\n\n• English\n\nLanguages\n\n• English,Hindi,marathi - Expert\n\n• Microsoft office , MS-word,Ms-Excel Ms-Presentation,Mass mailing, (2 years)\n\n\fOnline Profile\n\nhttps://www.linkedin.com/in/himanshu-singh-1859221b0/\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[15,21,"LOCATION"],[23,34,"LOCATION"],[178,183,"LOCATION"],[206,215,"DURATION"],[340,359,"ROLE"],[360,379,"ORGANISATION"],[380,409,"DURATION"],[422,455,"EDUCATION"],[456,473,"INSTITUTION"],[476,482,"LOCATION"],[484,495,"LOCATION"],[496,520,"DURATION"],[544,553,"SKILLS"],[557,577,"SKILLS"],[581,596,"SKILLS"],[600,615,"SKILLS"],[619,624,"SKILLS"],[628,648,"SKILLS"],[652,668,"SKILLS"],[728,744,"SKILLS"],[747,754,"SKILLS"],[755,763,"SKILLS"],[764,779,"SKILLS"],[780,792,"SKILLS"],[795,802,"DURATION"]]}]]}