{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Jaspreet Singh\nChennai, Tamil Nadu\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Jaspreet-Singh/009412d4a4382460\n\nExperienced UI developer having hands-on experience in designing, implementing and developing\nhigh-quality software designs & architecture. Proficient in writing efficient clean code and comfortable\nin interacting with the clients to successfully execute projects ensuring 100% client satisfaction.\n\nWork Experience\n\nDeveloper\nTata Consultancy Services - Chennai, Tamil Nadu\n2019 to September 2021\n\n1. Converted designs & wireframes to high-quality UI code.\n2. Optimized code to deliver high performance and fast loading times using best practices and latest\nfeatures.\n3. Involved in maintenance of legacy application UI code.\n4. Created highly responsive user interfaces ensuring best experience on various screen sizes.\n\nEducation\n\nPG Diploma in Software Development in Computer Science\nIIIT - Bengaluru, Karnataka\n2021 to Present\n\nBSc. in Computer Science\nOsmania University\n2016 to 2019\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• Software Development\n\n• Interface Designing\n\n• Responsive Web Design\n\n• Unit Testing\n\n• Rational & Critical Thinking\n\nLanguages\n\n• English - Fluent\n\n• Programming Languages: Java, JavaScript\n\n• Technologies: HTML, CSS, SASS, ReactJS, ReduxJS, NextJS, GIT\n\n\f• Hindi - Fluent\n• Punjabi - Fluent\n\nOnline Profile\n\nhttp://github.com/jaspreet22g\n\nhttp://linkedin.com/in/jaspreet22g\n\nhttps://jaspreetportfolio.netlify.app/\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[15,22,"LOCATION"],[24,34,"LOCATION"],[430,439,"ROLE"],[440,465,"ORGANISATION"],[468,475,"LOCATION"],[477,487,"LOCATION"],[488,510,"DURATION"],[850,901,"EDUCATION"],[902,918,"INSTITUTION"],[920,929,"LOCATION"],[930,945,"DURATION"],[947,971,"EDUCATION"],[972,990,"INSTITUTION"],[991,1003,"DURATION"],[1027,1047,"SKILLS"],[1051,1070,"SKILLS"],[1074,1095,"SKILLS"],[1099,1111,"SKILLS"],[1115,1143,"SKILLS"],[1201,1205,"SKILLS"],[1207,1217,"SKILLS"],[1235,1239,"SKILLS"],[1241,1244,"SKILLS"],[1246,1250,"SKILLS"],[1252,1259,"SKILLS"],[1261,1268,"SKILLS"],[1270,1276,"SKILLS"],[1278,1281,"SKILLS"]]}]]}