{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Jayesh Pansheriya\nAhmedabad, Gujarat\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Jayesh-Pansheriya/96f44520324faa8a\n\nhttps://github.com/jayeshpansheriya \nLinkedIn: \nProfile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jayeshpansheriya \nMedium: \nProfile: https://medium.com/@pansheriyajayesh \n \nㅡ\n\nWork Experience\n\nFlutter Developer\nIndianic Limited - Ahmedabad, Gujarat\nMarch 2020 to Present\n\nSoftware Engineer for Mobile applications with key focus on\nFlutter.\n\n● Responsible for improving the technical capability of self and\nhelping others to grow by sharing my knowledge. Believe in the project idea, architecture, time and team,\nunderstand the domain, and the technical challenges.\n\n● As a team player among all the other players, my role includes\ndeveloping Cross-platform app development, Apart from app\ndevelopment, communication, project understanding & feasibility checking, managing projects & team\nare also taken\ncare.\n\nAndroid Developer\nVnurture Technology - Ahmedabad, Gujarat\nSeptember 2017 to January 2020\n\nSoftware Engineer for Mobile applications with key focus on\nAndroid with hands-on experience on Flutter.\n\n● Developed new features for proprietary Android applications\nused on phones and tablets, worked with developers to develop\ntop-tier solutions.\n\n● Collaborated with cross functional teams to define, design, and ship new features.\n\n● Worked with outside data sources and API's.\n\n● Continuously discovered, evaluated, and implemented new\n\n\ftechnologies to maximize development efficiency.\n\n● Develop Cross platform Application using Flutter Framework.\nㅡ\n\nEducation\n\nComputer Engineering\nArun Muchhala Engineering College - Amreli, Gujarat\nJuly 2013 to July 2017\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• Profiles GitHub:\n\nOnline Profile\n\nhttps://jayeshpansheriya.github.io\n\nhttps://www.linkedin.com/in/jayeshpansheriya\n\n• Flutter, Dart, Android SDK, Web Service, Json, Gson, Kotlin. Designing Tools: Sketch, Zeplin, Adobe\nPhotoshop Database: SQLite. Analytics: Google Analytics, Sentry. Third party Libraries: Google Map\nand Direction APIs, Youtube APIs, GSON, Volley, PICASSO, FireBase, Parse push Notification. Flutter:\nWidgets, Material Design, Navigation, StateManagement, Extensions, Plugins. Development Tools:\nAndroid Studio, VS Code, XCode. Others: Git, Github, Bitbucket.\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,17,"PERSON"],[18,27,"LOCATION"],[29,36,"LOCATION"],[299,316,"ROLE"],[317,333,"ORGANISATION"],[336,345,"LOCATION"],[347,354,"LOCATION"],[355,376,"DURATION"],[378,395,"ROLE"],[917,934,"ROLE"],[935,954,"ORGANISATION"],[957,966,"LOCATION"],[968,975,"LOCATION"],[976,1006,"DURATION"],[1578,1598,"EDUCATION"],[1599,1632,"INSTITUTION"],[1643,1650,"LOCATION"],[1651,1673,"DURATION"],[1815,1822,"SKILLS"],[1822,1828,"SKILLS"],[1830,1841,"SKILLS"],[1843,1854,"SKILLS"],[1856,1860,"SKILLS"],[1862,1866,"SKILLS"],[1868,1875,"SKILLS"],[1893,1899,"SKILLS"],[1901,1907,"SKILLS"],[1909,1924,"SKILLS"],[1935,1942,"SKILLS"],[1954,1970,"SKILLS"],[1972,1979,"SKILLS"],[2003,2032,"SKILLS"],[2034,2046,"SKILLS"],[2048,2052,"SKILLS"],[2054,2060,"SKILLS"],[2062,2069,"SKILLS"],[2071,2079,"SKILLS"],[2081,2105,"SKILLS"],[2115,2122,"SKILLS"],[2124,2139,"SKILLS"],[2141,2151,"SKILLS"],[2153,2168,"SKILLS"],[2170,2180,"SKILLS"],[2182,2190,"SKILLS"],[2210,2224,"SKILLS"],[2226,2233,"SKILLS"],[2235,2241,"SKILLS"],[2250,2253,"SKILLS"],[2255,2261,"SKILLS"],[2263,2272,"SKILLS"]]}]]}