{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Jobin Joy\nJabalpur, Madhya Pradesh\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Jobin-Joy/9ac93eec19d5cf72",{"entities":[[0,9,"PERSON"],[10,18,"LOCATION"],[20,34,"LOCATION"]]}],["Urgent job require in Jabalpur in finance and marketing",{"entities":[[22,30,"LOCATION"],[34,55,"ROLE"]]}],["Urgent needed job in finance and marketing in Jabalpur",{"entities":[[21,42,"ROLE"],[46,54,"LOCATION"]]}],["Work Experience",{"entities":[]}],["Finance & Marketing\nHome credit finance\nMay 2015 to September 2017",{"entities":[[0,19,"ROLE"],[20,39,"ORGANISATION"],[40,66,"DURATION"]]}],["Finance & Marketing\nHome credit finance\nApril 2016 to August 2017",{"entities":[[0,19,"ROLE"],[20,39,"ORGANISATION"],[40,65,"DURATION"]]}],["Education",{"entities":[]}],["MBA MASTER DEGREE\nSRIT COLLEGE RDVV",{"entities":[[0,17,"EDUCATION"],[18,35,"INSTITUTION"]]}],["\f",{"entities":[]}]]}