{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Jupiter Muddana\nHyderabad, Telangana\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Jupiter-Muddana/00edad6d802d3128\n\n• Knowledge on SDFC Administrative tasks like creating Profiles, Roles, Users, Page \nLayouts, Permission Sets, Email Services, Approvals, Workflows, Reports, \nDashboards, Tasks and Events. \n• Knowledge on CRM business processes like Campaign Management, Lead \nManagement, Opportunity Management, Account Management and Case \nManagement. \n• Knowledge on designing Custom Formula Field Dependencies, Validation Rules, \nWork Flows, and Approval Processes for automated alerts, field updates, and Email \ngeneration according to application requirements. \n• Knowledge on field level security for level of access to records \n• Knowledge on Reports & Dashboards for various requirements. \n• Knowledge on Apex Classes & Apex Triggers \n• Knowledge on Visualforce Pages\n\nWork Experience\n\nDeveloper\nSalesforce\nOctober 2019 to January 2021\n\n1|Pa ge\n\nEducation\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• 2|Pa ge\n\nDevelop tools and automation frameworks for continuous integration, performance\nmeasurement, and evaluation.\n• Contribute to the design and velocity of our global products.\n•  Optimize  our  systems  end-to-end  by  advising  infrastructure  design,  server  and  application\ndevelopment/tuning, solving complex cluster architecture, and any data\nstorage issues that impact features.\n\nBachelor's in Civil Engineering\nRajiv Gandhi University of Knowledge Technologies Andhra Pradesh - Hyderabad, Telangana\nJune 2001 to Present\n\n• Operating System: Windows, Ubuntu, Fedora\n\n• Programming Languages: Python, HTML (basics), C (basics)\n\n\f• .NET\n\n• Python\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,15,"PERSON"],[16,25,"LOCATION"],[27,36,"LOCATION"],[894,903,"ROLE"],[904,914,"ORGANISATION"],[915,943,"DURATION"],[1381,1412,"EDUCATION"],[1413,1477,"INSTITUTION"],[1480,1489,"LOCATION"],[1491,1500,"LOCATION"],[1501,1521,"DURATION"],[1543,1550,"SKILLS"],[1552,1558,"SKILLS"],[1560,1566,"SKILLS"],[1593,1599,"SKILLS"],[1601,1605,"SKILLS"],[1616,1617,"SKILLS"],[1631,1635,"SKILLS"],[1639,1645,"SKILLS"]]}]]}