{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Kamlesh Gujariya\nIndore, Madhya Pradesh\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Kamlesh-Gujariya/a54ca3ec2718970c\n\nSelf-motivated, Logical thinking, Solving complex problems, Teamwork, Multitasking & \nStrong work ethic.\n\nWork Experience\n\nFull Stack & Blockchain Developer\nESP Softtech Pvt. Ltd. - Indore, Madhya Pradesh\nJanuary 2020 to Present\n\nMandsaur Madhya Pradesh\nSolidity -\nBlockchain Very Good Work Experience\nWeb3.js- 2020-01 - Full Stack & Blockchain Developer\nBlockchain Good\nCurrent ESP Softtech Pvt Ltd, Indore, Madhya Pradesh\nNode.js Managed development milestones from initial steps through final delivery.\nGood Took initial concepts and developed project plans.\nReact.js Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues.\nGood Constructed integration libraries to interface with Blockchain and APIs.\nGuided the team by understanding the requirements of the project.\nJavascript\nVery Good NFT Marketplace development.\nBlockchain: Ethereum, Binance Smart Chain.\nPHP\nSmart Contract: ERC20, BEP20, TRC20, ERC721, ERC1155.\nVery Good\nUniswap & Pancakeswap router integration for crypto swap.\nMySQl Wallet Integration: Metamask, Tron wallet, Trust wallet, Coinbase wallet.\nVery Good\nPayment Gateway: Stripe & Paypal\n\nPHP Developer\nShrinkcom Software Pvt Ltd - Indore, Madhya Pradesh\nJune 2019 to January 2020\n\nEducation\n\nBachelor's\nPrashanti Institute of Technology And Science - Ujjain, Madhya Pradesh\nMay 2021\n\nGT Polytechnic College - Jaora, Madhya Pradesh\n\n\fMay 2018\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• AJAX\n\n• HTML5\n\n• JavaScript\n\n• MySQL\n\n• PHP\n\n• React.js\n\n• Node.js\n\n• Solidity\n\n• Web3.js\n\n• Ethereum\n\n• Smart contract\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,16,"PERSON"],[17,23,"LOCATION"],[25,39,"LOCATION"],[243,276,"ROLE"],[277,299,"ORGANISATION"],[302,308,"LOCATION"],[310,324,"LOCATION"],[325,348,"DURATION"],[359,373,"LOCATION"],[374,382,"SKILLS"],[385,395,"SKILLS"],[422,430,"SKILLS"],[499,519,"ORGANISATION"],[521,527,"LOCATION"],[529,543,"LOCATION"],[544,551,"SKILLS"],[682,690,"SKILLS"],[803,813,"SKILLS"],[911,939,"SKILLS"],[952,960,"SKILLS"],[962,982,"SKILLS"],[1003,1008,"SKILLS"],[1010,1015,"SKILLS"],[1017,1022,"SKILLS"],[1024,1030,"SKILLS"],[1032,1040,"SKILLS"],[1051,1091,"SKILLS"],[1109,1114,"SKILLS"],[1233,1246,"ROLE"],[1247,1273,"ORGANISATION"],[1276,1282,"LOCATION"],[1284,1298,"LOCATION"],[1299,1324,"DURATION"],[1337,1347,"EDUCATION"],[1348,1393,"INSTITUTION"],[1396,1402,"LOCATION"],[1404,1418,"LOCATION"],[1419,1427,"DURATION"],[1429,1451,"INSTITUTION"],[1461,1475,"LOCATION"],[1478,1486,"DURATION"],[1510,1514,"SKILLS"],[1518,1523,"SKILLS"],[1527,1537,"SKILLS"],[1541,1546,"SKILLS"],[1550,1553,"SKILLS"],[1557,1565,"SKILLS"],[1569,1576,"SKILLS"],[1580,1588,"SKILLS"],[1592,1599,"SKILLS"],[1603,1611,"SKILLS"],[1615,1629,"SKILLS"]]}]]}