{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Kancharla Lyla\nJob application\nKhammam, Telangana\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Kancharla-Lyla/ff286168fe267165\n\nTo work in organization, which provides me with a challenging atmosphere where I can utilize and\nimprove my technical and interpersonal skills and thus contribute to the organization.\n\nI will do confidently to complete my work seriously with in time, I follow the ruls as for the company, I\nhave a good communication skills, learning ability, highly motivated.\n\nPersonal Details\n\nDate of Birth: 1990-06-05\nEligible to work in: India\nHighest Career Level: 1-2 years experience\nIndustry: Accounting, Management, Medical Technician\nTotal years of experience: 2\n\nWork Experience\n\nMarketing Executive\nSaboo hyundai pvt lmtd company - Secunderabad, Telangana\nJuly 2016 to May 2019\n\nEducation\n\nMaster's\nJawaharlal Nehru Technological University - Hyderabad, Telangana\nJune 2012 to August 2015\n\nMaster's in Computers\nJawaharlal Nehru Technological University - Hyderabad, Telangana\nJune 2012 to August 2015\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• Microsoft office, tally basics, PGDCA\n\n• Microsoft Office, tally, PGDCA\n\n• Marketing\n\n• Communication skills\n\n• Microsoft Excel\n\n• Computer skills\n\n\f• Business development\n\n• Customer service\n\n• Sales\n\n• Negotiation\n\n• English\n\nLanguages\n\n• Telugu, english, tamil, hindi. - Expert\n\nProjects / Papers Presented\n\nWorking capital management\n2014\n\nAdditional Information\n\nSpecial reference to BAJAJ ALLIANZ LIFE INSURANCE CO. LTD. HYDERABAD\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[40,49,"LOCATION"],[555,560,"LOCATION"],[583,592,"DURATION"],[614,624,"ROLE"],[626,636,"ROLE"],[638,656,"ROLE"],[657,685,"DURATION"],[704,723,"ROLE"],[724,746,"ORGANISATION"],[757,769,"LOCATION"],[771,780,"LOCATION"],[781,802,"DURATION"],[815,823,"EDUCATION"],[824,865,"INSTITUTION"],[868,877,"LOCATION"],[879,888,"LOCATION"],[889,913,"DURATION"],[915,936,"EDUCATION"],[937,978,"INSTITUTION"],[981,990,"LOCATION"],[992,1001,"LOCATION"],[1002,1026,"DURATION"],[1050,1066,"SKILLS"],[1068,1080,"SKILLS"],[1082,1087,"SKILLS"],[1091,1107,"SKILLS"],[1109,1114,"SKILLS"],[1116,1121,"SKILLS"],[1125,1134,"SKILLS"],[1138,1158,"SKILLS"],[1162,1177,"SKILLS"],[1181,1196,"SKILLS"],[1201,1221,"SKILLS"],[1225,1241,"SKILLS"],[1245,1250,"SKILLS"],[1254,1265,"SKILLS"],[1361,1387,"PROJECTS"],[1388,1392,"DURATION"],[1439,1476,"ORGANISATION"],[1477,1486,"LOCATION"]]}]]}