{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Khushbu Dhiman\nFull stack developer\nAmbala, Haryana\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Khushbu-Dhiman/4fba604b1d87e774\n\nA curious learner and result-oriented professional with in-depth knowledge of designing and\ndevelopment tools currently working in \nInfogain India Pvt. Ltd. as a Software Engineer with 3 years of experience in Software Development\nusing Java, Python, J2EE with \nproven expertise using frameworks like Spring Boot, Django to drive improvements throughout an\nentire software development life- \ncycle and sprints.\n\nWilling to relocate to: Noida, Uttar Pradesh - Bengaluru, Karnataka -\n\nPersonal Details\n\nDate of Birth: 1995-01-25\nEligible to work in: India\nHighest Career Level: 2-5 years experience\nIndustry: IT Operations & Helpdesk\nTotal years of experience: 3\n\nWork Experience\n\nSoftware Developer\nINFOGAIN India Pvt. Ltd - Noida, Uttar Pradesh\nApril 2021 to Present\n\nVision 4.x Noida UP, IN\n\nWeb Application Development\nKey  Skills:  Java,  Python,  Hibernate,  MySQL,  Junit,  SonarQube,  Postman,  SVN,  Spring  Boot,  Mockito,\nJenkins, Spring scheduler\nProject Description: NCR - Vision 4.x\nAPTRA  Vision's  Incident  Management  (Vision  IM)  feature  is  an  automated  service-level  management\nsystem designed to identify\nproblems that occur to networked Terminals. Vision IM tracks the problems, dispatches service teams if\nnecessary, and solves the problems without relying on Help Desk operators\nRoles/ Responsibilities:\nGained hands-on experience in developing, implementing, and maintaining internal web applications\nWorking on Spring Boot, Spring MVC Using Hibernate with Oracle, SQL Server as Database.\nWorked in collaboration with UI Team for modification of API'S and integrating with Application.\nCoordinate with onsite people for technical design and implementation.\nPerformed Unit tests to ensure the software is up to date and working properly\nUsed TDD approach for Software development for high test coverage.\n\n\fAdded Logging Aspect for REST APIs using Spring AOP.\nBug Fixing in the code using Apache Solr 8.3.\n\nSoftware Developer\nINFOGAIN India Pvt. Ltd - Noida, Uttar Pradesh\nFebruary 2020 to March 2021\n\nKey Skills: Java, Python, Django, SQL, MongoDB, Angular6, Swagger, SVN, Spring, Radis Cache.\nProject Description:: NCR IT - Quote Builder As A Service -This Project is an Quote Builder Domain project\nand provide functionality in order to create Product/Service and Subscription Quote and support SSOT\nrelated functionalities.\nRoles/ Responsibilities:\nDesign, Develop and Implements REST APIs as per the requirements.\nCoding the programs in accordance with Program Specifications and adhering to Coding Standards\nWorked in collaboration with UI Team for modification of API'S and integrating with Application.\nJunit test cases for testing the functionality of application and bug fixing.\nCreating REST API as per the requirements and involved in bug fixing of the existing API's.\nAchievements: SPOT Performance Award of September'20\n\nEducation\n\nM.C.A. in Computer Applications\nPanjab University\nJanuary 2019\n\nBSC\nKurukshetra University - Kurukshetra, Haryana\nMay 2015\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• Java\n\n• HTML5\n\n• Python\n\n• SQL\n\n• JavaScript\n\n• Django\n\n• Spring Boot\n\n• ROS\n\n• Mongodb\n\n• Mysql\n\n• Programming languages: Java, Python, C, C++. \n\nWeb Technologies: Spring Framework, Microservices, Spring MVC, Spring AOP, Django, HTML, CSS,\nJSP, Angular. \nData Modelling: XSLT, XML, Data Structure, Machine Learning \nData Management: MongoDB, MySQL, Oracle, Redis, MS Access \nIDEs: Spring Boot, Eclipse, Visual Studio, Tensor Flow, Intellij, Jupiter Notebook Matlab. \nTools: SVN, GIT, Crucible.\n\n\f• Angular\n\n• Css\n\n• Agile\n\n• C\n\nOnline Profile\n\nhttp://www.linkedin.com/in/khushbu-dhiman-712135168\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[15,35,"ROLE"],[36,42,"LOCATION"],[44,51,"LOCATION"],[208,217,"SKILLS"],[222,239,"SKILLS"],[262,286,"ORGANISATION"],[292,309,"ROLE"],[315,322,"DURATION"],[367,371,"SKILLS"],[373,379,"SKILLS"],[381,385,"SKILLS"],[431,442,"SKILLS"],[444,450,"SKILLS"],[566,571,"LOCATION"],[573,586,"LOCATION"],[589,598,"LOCATION"],[600,609,"LOCATION"],[678,683,"LOCATION"],[706,726,"DURATION"],[762,790,"DURATION"],[809,827,"ROLE"],[828,851,"ORGANISATION"],[854,859,"LOCATION"],[861,874,"LOCATION"],[875,896,"DURATION"],[965,970,"SKILLS"],[972,978,"SKILLS"],[981,990,"SKILLS"],[993,998,"SKILLS"],[1001,1006,"SKILLS"],[1009,1018,"SKILLS"],[1021,1028,"SKILLS"],[1031,1034,"SKILLS"],[1037,1049,"SKILLS"],[1052,1059,"SKILLS"],[1061,1068,"SKILLS"],[1070,1086,"SKILLS"],[1108,1124,"PROJECTS"],[2064,2082,"ROLE"],[2083,2106,"ORGANISATION"],[2109,2114,"LOCATION"],[2116,2129,"LOCATION"],[2130,2157,"DURATION"],[2171,2175,"SKILLS"],[2177,2183,"SKILLS"],[2185,2191,"SKILLS"],[2193,2196,"SKILLS"],[2198,2205,"SKILLS"],[2207,2215,"SKILLS"],[2217,2224,"SKILLS"],[2226,2229,"SKILLS"],[2231,2237,"SKILLS"],[2239,2251,"SKILLS"],[2274,2296,"PROJECTS"],[3003,3034,"EDUCATION"],[3035,3052,"INSTITUTION"],[3053,3065,"DURATION"],[3067,3070,"EDUCATION"],[3071,3093,"INSTITUTION"],[3096,3107,"LOCATION"],[3109,3116,"LOCATION"],[3117,3125,"DURATION"],[3149,3153,"SKILLS"],[3157,3162,"SKILLS"],[3166,3172,"SKILLS"],[3176,3179,"SKILLS"],[3183,3193,"SKILLS"],[3197,3203,"SKILLS"],[3207,3218,"SKILLS"],[3222,3225,"SKILLS"],[3229,3236,"SKILLS"],[3240,3245,"SKILLS"],[3272,3276,"SKILLS"],[3278,3284,"SKILLS"],[3286,3287,"SKILLS"],[3289,3293,"SKILLS"],[3314,3330,"SKILLS"],[3332,3345,"SKILLS"],[3347,3357,"SKILLS"],[3359,3369,"SKILLS"],[3371,3377,"SKILLS"],[3379,3383,"SKILLS"],[3385,3388,"SKILLS"],[3390,3393,"SKILLS"],[3395,3403,"SKILLS"],[3421,3425,"SKILLS"],[3427,3430,"SKILLS"],[3432,3446,"SKILLS"],[3483,3490,"SKILLS"],[3492,3497,"SKILLS"],[3499,3505,"SKILLS"],[3507,3512,"SKILLS"],[3514,3523,"SKILLS"],[3531,3542,"SKILLS"],[3544,3551,"SKILLS"],[3553,3566,"SKILLS"],[3568,3579,"SKILLS"],[3581,3589,"SKILLS"],[3591,3607,"SKILLS"],[3608,3615,"SKILLS"],[3624,3627,"SKILLS"],[3629,3632,"SKILLS"],[3634,3643,"SKILLS"],[3648,3655,"SKILLS"],[3659,3662,"SKILLS"],[3666,3671,"SKILLS"],[3675,3676,"SKILLS"]]}]]}