{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Lakshya Joshi\nFront end developer|angular| HTML|CSS|software\nHyderabad, Telangana\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Lakshya-Joshi/989c5899a0048f03\n\nA diligent technology enthusiast with a total of 2.10 years of experience in the field of software \ndevelopment. Having a good knowledge and hands on experience with development of websites with \nhelp of HTML, CSS, JS, SQL and Bootstrap. Microsoft Certified with AZ-900. Determined to work on \nJavaScript based frameworks where I can enhance my skills and in return benefit the organization as \nwell.\n\nWilling to relocate to: Pune, Maharashtra - Bengaluru, Karnataka - Gurgaon, Haryana\n\nPersonal Details\n\nDate of Birth: 1996-10-26\nHighest Career Level: 2-5 years experience\nIndustry: Software Development\nTotal years of experience: 3\n\nWork Experience\n\nDeveloper\nIBM - Hyderabad, Telangana\n2019 to Present\n\nSoftware Developer\nIBM - Hyderabad, Telangana\n2019 to Present\n\nAs  a  Software  developer  my  responsibility  is  to  make  interactive  applications  and  also  dynamic  web\napplications. Used HTML, CSS and angular to dynamic and user friendly applications\n\nCEMEX is a global leader in the building material industry that provides high-quality products and reliable\nservices with a rich history of improving the well being of those it serves through innovative\nbuilding solutions, efficiency, advancements and sustainability efforts.\nCEMEX Go project is a digital solution that automates order-to-cash workflows, enabling the purchase of\nproducts, tracking of deliveries, and managing of order sin real time. The platform is transforming\nthe role of the company's Salesforce, allowing it to dedicate more time to better serving customers.\nRole and Responsibility:\nAs a Software developer, primarily worked on building and designing dynamic web pages using\nHTML5, CSS3, JS.\nImplementing a mobile-first approach to existing websites\nUsed SQL procedures and DML queries for storing and updating the user data.\nAlso provide support and resolve all complex programs and coordinate with clients.\n\n\fEducation\n\nBachelor's in Electronics and Communication\nRajasthan Technical University - Jaipur, Rajasthan\nAugust 2014 to June 2018\n\nHigher Secondary(12th Pass) in Physics Mathematics and chemistry\nJaipur, Rajasthan\nApril 2013 to May 2014\n\nSecondary(10th Pass) in Others\nJaipur, Rajasthan\nApril 2011 to May 2012\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• ON: CSS, HTML, JS, SQL, SQL DBA, Sublime, SQL Management Studio, Angular\n\n• WITH: Python, Java, Jupyter\n\n• WORKED\n\n• FAMILAR\n\n• C\n\n• HTML5\n\n• JavaScript\n\n• SQL\n\n• Angularjs\n\n• Angular\n\n• Agile\n\n• Java\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[14,42,"ROLE"],[43,60,"SKILLS"],[61,70,"LOCATION"],[72,81,"LOCATION"],[208,218,"DURATION"],[363,367,"SKILLS"],[369,372,"SKILLS"],[374,376,"SKILLS"],[378,381,"SKILLS"],[386,396,"SKILLS"],[397,429,"CERTIFICATE"],[453,480,"SKILLS"],[585,589,"LOCATION"],[591,602,"LOCATION"],[605,614,"LOCATION"],[616,625,"LOCATION"],[628,635,"LOCATION"],[637,644,"LOCATION"],[712,732,"DURATION"],[764,792,"DURATION"],[811,820,"ROLE"],[821,824,"ORGANISATION"],[827,836,"LOCATION"],[838,847,"LOCATION"],[848,863,"DURATION"],[865,883,"ROLE"],[884,887,"ORGANISATION"],[890,899,"LOCATION"],[901,910,"LOCATION"],[911,926,"DURATION"],[1060,1064,"SKILLS"],[1066,1069,"SKILLS"],[1074,1081,"SKILLS"],[1125,1130,"ORGANISATION"],[1401,1409,"PROJECTS"],[1736,1754,"ROLE"],[1823,1828,"SKILLS"],[1830,1834,"SKILLS"],[1836,1839,"SKILLS"],[2070,2113,"EDUCATION"],[2114,2144,"INSTITUTION"],[2147,2153,"LOCATION"],[2155,2164,"LOCATION"],[2165,2189,"DURATION"],[2191,2207,"EDUCATION"],[2208,2217,"EDUCATION"],[2256,2262,"LOCATION"],[2264,2273,"LOCATION"],[2274,2296,"DURATION"],[2298,2307,"EDUCATION"],[2308,2317,"EDUCATION"],[2329,2335,"LOCATION"],[2337,2346,"LOCATION"],[2347,2369,"DURATION"],[2397,2400,"SKILLS"],[2402,2406,"SKILLS"],[2408,2410,"SKILLS"],[2412,2415,"SKILLS"],[2417,2424,"SKILLS"],[2426,2433,"SKILLS"],[2435,2456,"SKILLS"],[2458,2465,"SKILLS"],[2475,2481,"SKILLS"],[2483,2487,"SKILLS"],[2489,2496,"SKILLS"],[2500,2506,"SKILLS"],[2510,2517,"SKILLS"],[2521,2522,"SKILLS"],[2526,2531,"SKILLS"],[2535,2545,"SKILLS"],[2549,2552,"SKILLS"],[2556,2565,"SKILLS"],[2569,2576,"SKILLS"],[2580,2585,"SKILLS"],[2589,2593,"SKILLS"]]}]]}