{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Lavanya Nakka\nKukatpalli, Andhra Pradesh\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Lavanya-Nakka/70413f2ec69854cb\n\nA results oriented individual Expertise is broad in scope. Possess a high technical aptitude and a\nhigh level of analytical ability. Trained in the use and creation of tools and applications customized\nfor proprietary uses. I understand and believe in the integration of techniques, I learn more and do\nmore of the work, add more value to the team. Be able to handle complex situations and time crunch\nschedules, would create more value for the company and for the customer. \n \nSummary \nAround 6 years of experience as software engineer, \n• Experience in PHP Scripting \n• Knowledge of other scripting languages like JAVA scripting, AJAX \n• Worked on joomla components developing, cms and wordpress. \n• Knowledge of software development life cycle \n• Can work independently, lead or work within a team environment. \n• Excellent organizational and communication skills, both oral and written. \nCareer break: \n• From 2013 Jan to till date. Total 9 years of break due to maternity and some personal issues.\n\nWork Experience\n\nPHP Developer\nMindtech Solutions - Hyderabad, Telangana\nJuly 2010 to April 2011\n\n• I worked independently or work within a team environment.\n• Be able to handle complex situations and time crunch schedules,\n•\n\nDeveloper\nMBM IT solutions - Hyderabad, Telangana\nDecember 2009 to June 2010\n\nDeveloper\nIbee software Solutions - Hyderabad, Telangana\n2007 to February 2009\n\nWorked as a Developer with Dreamz Soft Tech, Hyderabad from 2006 Nov to 2007 Oct.\n\nDeveloper\nFree Foundation Software Solutions - Hyderabad, Telangana\nAugust 2005 to November 2006\n\n\fBachelor's Degree in Computer Science Engineering in Computer Science\nEngineering\nAcharaya Nagarjuna University\n2005\n\n• Languages/ Scripting: PHP, JavaScript, html.\n\n• Worked on joomla components, developing new component and also in wordpress blogs.\n\n• Write monthly, weekly, Daily status reports.\n\n• Skilled in both the writing and execution of system, functional and Unit Testing.\n\nEducation\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• OS: Windows\n\n• Database: MYSQL.\n\n• Administration\n\n• Quality control,\n\n• learming codeigniter\n\n• JavaScript\n\n• PHP\n\n• MySQL\n\n• Wordpress\n\n• HTML5\n\n• AJAX\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[26,40,"LOCATION"],[612,619,"DURATION"],[673,676,"SKILLS"],[734,738,"SKILLS"],[750,754,"SKILLS"],[768,774,"SKILLS"],[798,801,"SKILLS"],[806,816,"SKILLS"],[833,853,"SKILLS"],[1027,1054,"DURATION"],[1061,1077,"DURATION"],[1139,1152,"ROLE"],[1153,1171,"ORGANISATION"],[1174,1183,"LOCATION"],[1185,1194,"LOCATION"],[1195,1218,"DURATION"],[1349,1358,"ROLE"],[1359,1375,"ORGANISATION"],[1378,1387,"LOCATION"],[1389,1398,"LOCATION"],[1399,1425,"DURATION"],[1427,1436,"ROLE"],[1437,1460,"ORGANISATION"],[1463,1472,"LOCATION"],[1474,1483,"LOCATION"],[1484,1505,"DURATION"],[1519,1528,"ROLE"],[1534,1550,"ORGANISATION"],[1552,1561,"LOCATION"],[1567,1588,"DURATION"],[1590,1599,"ROLE"],[1600,1634,"ORGANISATION"],[1637,1646,"LOCATION"],[1648,1657,"LOCATION"],[1658,1686,"DURATION"],[1689,1738,"EDUCATION"],[1771,1800,"INSTITUTION"],[1801,1805,"DURATION"],[1831,1834,"SKILLS"],[1836,1846,"SKILLS"],[1848,1853,"SKILLS"],[1867,1884,"SKILLS"],[1923,1939,"SKILLS"],[2044,2072,"SKILLS"],[2111,2118,"SKILLS"],[2132,2138,"SKILLS"],[2142,2156,"SKILLS"],[2160,2175,"SKILLS"],[2180,2200,"SKILLS"],[2204,2214,"SKILLS"],[2218,2221,"SKILLS"],[2225,2230,"SKILLS"],[2234,2243,"SKILLS"],[2247,2252,"SKILLS"],[2256,2260,"SKILLS"]]}]]}