{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["MOHAN G\nSalem, Tamil Nadu\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/MOHAN-G/8bc5f2594908d4d1\n\nExtremely motivated to constantly develop my skills and grow professionally. I am confident in my \nability to come up with interesting ideas for unforgettable marketing campaigns.\n\nWilling to relocate to: Bengaluru, Karnataka - Chennai, Tamil Nadu - Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu\n\nWork Experience\n\nANALYST, DIGITAL MARKETING (DEMAND GENERATION)\nTrue Influence - Bengaluru, Karnataka\nJanuary 2021 to Present\n\nrequiring  database \n\n• Develop, maintain and execute demand generation plans aligned with business goals.\n•  Create  campaign  segmentation, \nMarketingOperations product\n• Ensuring design and layouts of emails are optimized,\n• Proofreading key messaging in and out of email templates\n• Develop content for marketing assets such as marketing emails, landing pages.\n• Include persuasive 'call-to-actions' in advertisements and promotions.\n• Track, report, and analyze ABM program performance,\n\njoins  and  selections,  within \n\nthe\n\nDIGITAL MARKETING SPECIALIST\nAimglobal - Bengaluru, Karnataka\nMay 2018 to December 2020\n\n• Plans and executes all web, SEO/SEM, Email, social media, and display advertising campaigns.\n• Enhance brand awareness in the digital space.\n• Drive website traffic and acquire leads.\n• Plans, executes, and measures experiments and conversion tests.\n• Identifies critical conversion points and optimizes user funnels.\n• Owning and maintaining site analytics, metrics, and campaign reporting.\n•  Managing  digital  agency  relationships,  day-to-day  production,  as  well  as  campaign  budgets\nandschedules.\n• Creating and executing SMS, and email-based marketing campaigns.\n\nEducation\n\nBachelor's degree in Electronics and Communication Engineering\nKongu Engineering College - Erode, Tamil Nadu\nJune 2013 to May 2016\n\n\fSkills / IT Skills\n\n• Creative spirit\n\n• Search Engine Optimization\n\n• Time management\n\n• Search Engine Marketing\n\n• Fast learner\n\n• Social Media Marketing\n\n• Motivated\n\n• Dedicated\n\n• Campaign Management\n\n• Email Marketing\n\n• Content Writing\n\n• Digital marketing\n\n• Google AdWords\n\n• Google Analytics\n\n• Demand Generation/Lead Generation\n\n• HTML5\n\n• SEO\n\n• Marketing\n\n• SEM\n\n• JavaScript\n\nLanguages\n\n• Tamil - Expert\n• Englis - Fluent\n\nOnline Profile\n\nhttp://digitaltipsy.com/\n\nhttps://www.linkedin.com/in/mohan-govindan/\n\nAwards / Achievements\n\nBest Employee\nSeptember 2020\n\nAward for the achievement of the highest revenue target for \nQ3 2020 (JUL-SEP).\n\n\fCertifications and Licenses\n\nFundamentals of digital marketing\nPresent\n\nEmail Marketing Course: HUBSPOT\nApril 2020 to April 2022\n\nGoogle My Business Basics: Google Digital Unlocked\nPresent\n\nDigital Skills: Digital Marketing - Accenture (FUTURE LEARN)\nPresent\n\nDigital Skills: Web Analytics - Accenture (FUTURE LEARN)\nPresent\n\nAdditional Information\n\nMy skillset includes the following: SEO, Google Ads, Social Media Marketing, Email Marketing,\nfamiliarity with HTML and CSS, website management, campaign management and experience in\nexecuting digital marketing campaigns for brands. I am creative and personable with an attention to\ndetail. \n \nExcelling as an integral member of the digital marketing team at True Influence for the past two years,\nI Dug into data and Developed, maintained and executed email marketing campaigns aligned with\nbusiness goals. \n \nCreate campaign segmentation, requiring database joins and selections within the Marketing\nOperations product. \n \nPlayed a crucial role in achieving an increase in revenue and was awarded for achieving the highest\nrevenue target for Q3 2020 (JUL-SEP). \nOne of my clients, a well-known CRITICAL EVENT MANAGEMENT SOLUTIONS company I can't name\nbecause of an NDA, realized a huge revenue improvement and extended their contract. \n \nAt Aimglobal, I handled project budgets of 3-4 Lakhs every month and Increased the sales by 80% of\nhome decor and online jewellery clients. \n \nWorked on several foreign websites and Made the websites rank the first page on Google. \n \nI am a person who always looks for challenges and learning opportunities and never stops to update\nmyself with the ongoing trends. \n \nThank you for your time in considering me for the position. I would enjoy talking with you about my\nskills in SEO, SEM, email marketing, and conversion rate optimization and I feel that I'd be a qualified\nfit for this role.\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[15,25,"LOCATION"],[302,311,"LOCATION"],[313,322,"LOCATION"],[325,332,"LOCATION"],[334,344,"LOCATION"],[347,357,"LOCATION"],[359,369,"LOCATION"],[388,395,"ROLE"],[397,414,"ROLE"],[435,449,"ORGANISATION"],[452,461,"LOCATION"],[463,472,"LOCATION"],[473,496,"DURATION"],[1030,1058,"ROLE"],[1059,1068,"ORGANISATION"],[1071,1080,"LOCATION"],[1082,1091,"LOCATION"],[1092,1117,"DURATION"],[1144,1147,"SKILLS"],[1149,1156,"SKILLS"],[1191,1202,"SKILLS"],[1224,1239,"SKILLS"],[1469,1478,"SKILLS"],[1480,1487,"SKILLS"],[1709,1771,"EDUCATION"],[1772,1797,"INSTITUTION"],[1800,1805,"LOCATION"],[1807,1817,"LOCATION"],[1818,1839,"DURATION"],[1883,1909,"SKILLS"],[1932,1955,"SKILLS"],[1975,1997,"SKILLS"],[2027,2046,"SKILLS"],[2050,2065,"SKILLS"],[2069,2084,"SKILLS"],[2088,2105,"SKILLS"],[2109,2123,"SKILLS"],[2127,2143,"SKILLS"],[2147,2180,"SKILLS"],[2184,2189,"SKILLS"],[2193,2196,"SKILLS"],[2200,2209,"SKILLS"],[2213,2216,"SKILLS"],[2220,2230,"SKILLS"],[2389,2402,"CERTIFICATE"],[2403,2417,"DURATION"],[2480,2497,"DURATION"],[2530,2563,"CERTIFICATE"],[2564,2571,"DURATION"],[2573,2604,"CERTIFICATE"],[2605,2629,"DURATION"],[2631,2656,"CERTIFICATE"],[2658,2681,"CERTIFICATE"],[2682,2689,"DURATION"],[2707,2736,"CERTIFICATE"],[2752,2759,"DURATION"],[2777,2802,"CERTIFICATE"],[2887,2890,"SKILLS"],[2892,2902,"SKILLS"],[2904,2926,"SKILLS"],[2928,2943,"SKILLS"],[2962,2966,"SKILLS"],[2971,2974,"SKILLS"],[2976,2994,"SKILLS"],[2996,3015,"SKILLS"],[3044,3061,"SKILLS"],[3210,3224,"ORGANISATION"],[3233,3247,"DURATION"],[3595,3612,"DURATION"],[3647,3682,"ORGANISATION"],[3794,3803,"ORGANISATION"],[4269,4272,"SKILLS"],[4274,4277,"SKILLS"],[4279,4294,"SKILLS"],[4300,4328,"SKILLS"]]}]]}