{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Muralidhar K Ashrit\nGulbarga, Karnataka\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Muralidhar-K-Ashrit/7b75d3bf9e022e02\n\nWilling to relocate to: Gulbarga, Karnataka\n\nBachelor's in Computer science\nGulbarga University - Gulbarga, Karnataka\nJanuary 2018 to Present\n\nWork Experience\n\nMarketing Executive\nGulbarga, Karnataka\n\nSales\nGulbarga, Karnataka\nStill I Am fresher to join job\n\nEducation\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• Business development\n\n• Microsoft Excel\n\n• Marketing\n\n• Microsoft office\n\n• Negotiation\n\nLanguages\n\n• English kannada - Native\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,19,"PERSON"],[20,28,"LOCATION"],[30,39,"LOCATION"],[147,155,"LOCATION"],[157,166,"LOCATION"],[168,198,"EDUCATION"],[199,218,"INSTITUTION"],[221,229,"LOCATION"],[231,240,"LOCATION"],[241,264,"DURATION"],[283,302,"ROLE"],[303,311,"LOCATION"],[313,322,"LOCATION"],[324,329,"ROLE"],[330,338,"LOCATION"],[340,349,"LOCATION"],[415,435,"SKILLS"],[439,454,"SKILLS"],[458,467,"SKILLS"],[471,487,"SKILLS"]]}]]}