{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Naqueeb Madni\nPatna, Bihar\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Naqueeb-Madni/136c43effc739cf9\n\nTo take a challenging role in Business Operations and learn the new Industries advancement over the \nperiod of time.\n\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\n\nWork Experience\n\nMarketing / Operation Assistance\nField of Oil & Gas - Patna, Bihar\n2019 to Present\n\nHaving Over 8+ years of Experience in Marketing / Operation Assistance in the Field of Oil & Gas\nIndustry and Real Estate and Construction works.\n\nCreative Steel India (Patna) \"Free Lancing'' (2019 till date)\n\nJob Responsibility:-\n• Identifying the Customers who may need the Mechanical fabrication and UPVC (Door and Windows)\nwork by visiting their sites.\n•  Visits  EPC,  AMC  Mechanical  and  Civil  /  Road  Contractors,  Architect,  Interior  Designer,  Hardware\nDistributors.\n• Reach customer through ecommerce and cold calling.\n• Accompany the Interested customer to visit \"Creative Steel India'' Facility.\n• Identify the customer requirement and advise the best suitable option to them.\n• Providing Techno-Commercial offer to the customers and the associates.\n• Closing the deal with Advance payment and issue the Performa Invoice.\n• Insure the resource availability and minimum stock level.\n• Follow-Up with vendors and the Supplier for timely delivery of materials.\n• Insure inline production progress.\n• Continuous site supervision to meet the delivery schedule.\n• Progress invoicing and receiving of payment.\n• Offer final Inspection to the client and insure client's acknowledgement against final delivery.\n• Generate remaining payment invoice against the order.\n• Getting work Completion Certificate and the Feed Back.\n• Maintain inquiry log book.\n• Preparing monthly Sales funnel.\n• Reporting to the top level management.\n\nVisiting clients and sites\nHertel \"ALTRAD Group\"\n2014 to 2019\n\nExperience in Oman - During -2014- 2019\nJob Responsibilities:-\n\n\f• Reviewing existing contracts and looking for growth opportunities.\n• Close monitoring of intended projects in Oman by using web access.\n• Developing new and old clients to grow them into a diversified customer base in a specialist niche\nmarket.\n• Pre-Qualifying with Oman major companies ie: Orpic, PDO, OXY.\n• Visiting clients and sites for possible scope.\n• Maintaining log of Enquires & Offer's.\n• Implementing sales and marketing strategies and plans.\n• Entertain Verbal & Email Enquiries.\n• Identifying the scope & getting clarification on specification, drawing, details.\n• Sharing detailed BOQ, Spec, Project Start date & location with the estimation team.\n• Manage day to day work of Operations department as per client Priority.\n•  Preparation  of  quotations,  internal  memos,  project  related  correspondences,  proper  filing  system  &\nstorage of records.\n• Coordinating with clients, suppliers, associates for companies day to day work\n• Coordinate with clients regarding progress of work, scope of work, plan and schedule activities.\n• Assisting Operations Manager and Country Manager to run daily office work.\n• Coordinating Project/Site Managers, Supervisors and Engineers for preparation of various project\nrelated documents such as schedules, method statements and ITP for client's approval.\n• Coordinating with Account department to ensure the invoices are prepared on time.\n• Highly adhere to confidentiality matters.\n\n2\n\nMarketing & Sales\nAPS Buildtech Pvt Ltd - Ghaziabad, Uttar Pradesh\nMarch 2011 to February 2014\n\nCrosschecking the suppliers invoices with companies LPO.\n• Resolving disputes and claims with suppliers.\n• Reporting to Vice-president responsible for marketing of real estate project in Ghaziabad.\n• Forecasting periodic sales targets & driving sales initiatives to achieve business goals.\n• Identifying business development scopes through channelizing different media section.\n• Deals in corporate presentation and offering corporate scheme to developbusiness\n• to meet companies goal.\n• Building Client relationship, briefing them about our projects along with arrangements of sitevisits.\n• Handling of queries of Walk in clients and through telephone and emails.\n• Pitching of products according to customer requirements\n• Escorting interested clients to actual construction sites.\n• Increasing and maintaining Broker Base\n• Adding new brokers to existing channel by visits and teleconversations.\n• Motivating brokers for additional business through various incentive schemes.\n• Updating information about new projects and developments in current projects.\n• Customer Relations and Services (after sales).\n• Servicing existing customers on financial assistance by bank loans.\n• Assisting customers in documentation formalities.\n• Project Planning and Promotion.\n• Analyzing market conditions and competition.\n• Providing inputs for detailing of projects for pricing and promotion\n\n\f• Exhibit real estate projects at trade shows and trade fairs.\n\nInternship Completed: -\nCompany Name • Land Craft Developers Pvt. Ltd.\nProject Title • After Sales services.\n\nEducation\n\nMaster's in MBA (Marketing & Finance)\nPTU - Punjab\nFebruary 2009 to February 2011\n\nBachelor's in Commerce\nAligarh Muslim University - Aligarh, Uttar Pradesh\nJanuary 2005 to April 2008\n\nHigher Secondary(12th Pass) in I.COM\nAligarh Muslim University - Aligarh, Uttar Pradesh\nJanuary 2003 to January 2005\n\nSecondary(10th Pass) in All Subjects\nBihar Board - Patna, Bihar\nJanuary 1990 to February 2002\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• Proficient in Handling Back End,\n\n• MS Windows XP, MS Windows Vista\n\n• MS Office (word, power-point, excel Language:-\n\n• Microsoft, Excel, Word, Power Point (8 years)\n\n• ISO 9001-2015 QMS Lead Auditor Training.\n\n• First Aider Training.\n\n• Confined Space HSE Training.\n\nLanguages\n\n• Hindi, English - Fluent\n\nAdditional Information\n\nQMS 9001-2018 Lead Auditor\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[14,19,"LOCATION"],[21,26,"LOCATION"],[270,302,"ROLE"],[303,321,"ORGANISATION"],[324,329,"LOCATION"],[331,336,"LOCATION"],[337,352,"DURATION"],[366,374,"DURATION"],[392,424,"ROLE"],[501,521,"ORGANISATION"],[523,528,"LOCATION"],[531,543,"ROLE"],[547,561,"DURATION"],[1792,1818,"ROLE"],[1826,1840,"ORGANISATION"],[1841,1853,"DURATION"],[1869,1873,"LOCATION"],[1883,1894,"DURATION"],[3367,3384,"ROLE"],[3385,3406,"ORGANISATION"],[3409,3418,"LOCATION"],[3420,3433,"LOCATION"],[3434,3461,"DURATION"],[4951,4982,"ORGANISATION"],[4999,5020,"PROJECTS"],[5033,5048,"EDUCATION"],[5071,5074,"INSTITUTION"],[5077,5083,"LOCATION"],[5084,5114,"DURATION"],[5116,5138,"EDUCATION"],[5139,5164,"INSTITUTION"],[5167,5174,"LOCATION"],[5176,5189,"LOCATION"],[5190,5216,"DURATION"],[5218,5234,"EDUCATION"],[5235,5244,"EDUCATION"],[5255,5280,"INSTITUTION"],[5283,5290,"LOCATION"],[5292,5305,"LOCATION"],[5306,5334,"DURATION"],[5336,5345,"EDUCATION"],[5346,5355,"EDUCATION"],[5373,5384,"INSTITUTION"],[5387,5392,"LOCATION"],[5394,5399,"LOCATION"],[5400,5429,"DURATION"],[5476,5484,"SKILLS"],[5489,5499,"SKILLS"],[5500,5502,"SKILLS"],[5507,5520,"SKILLS"],[5524,5533,"SKILLS"],[5535,5539,"SKILLS"],[5541,5552,"SKILLS"],[5554,5559,"SKILLS"],[5574,5583,"SKILLS"],[5585,5590,"SKILLS"],[5592,5596,"SKILLS"],[5598,5609,"SKILLS"],[5611,5618,"DURATION"],[5667,5678,"SKILLS"],[5707,5720,"SKILLS"]]}]]}