{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Niket Gopikrishnan\r\nCalicut, Kerala\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Niket-Gopikrishnan/9920850f71d69613\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nMarketing Executive\r\nGrey WorldWide - Bengaluru, Karnataka\r\n2019 to 2021\r\n\r\nManaged 4 of both agency's largest accounts, serving as the primary liaison between\r\nagency staff, client marketing teams and outsourced vendors.\r\n\r\nMARKETING EXECUTIVE\r\nPeople Design and Communication Pvt Ltd\r\niD Fresh Food\r\nWork with clients in the development of digital and traditional brand strategies. Managed\r\ndozens of multimedia campaigns. Collaborated with clients from concept to production and launch of\r\nnationwide print, TV, Web and social media campaigns that routinely\r\nexceeded client expectations.\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nBachelor's in Business\r\nBangalore University - Bengaluru, Karnataka\r\n2015 to 2018\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• KEY STRENGTHS\r\n\r\n• Content Development\r\n\r\n• Brand Development\r\n\r\n• Market Research\r\n\r\n• Adaptability\r\n\r\n• Creativity\r\n\r\n• Marketing\r\n\r\n• Communication skills\r\n\r\n• could help in conceptualizing the strategy for the brand. Handled packaging work when\r\n\r\n\fLanguages\r\n\r\n• English - Expert\r\n• Hindi - Fluent\r\n• Malayalam - Native\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,18,"PERSON"],[20,27,"LOCATION"],[29,35,"LOCATION"],[173,192,"ROLE"],[194,208,"ORGANISATION"],[211,220,"LOCATION"],[222,231,"LOCATION"],[233,245,"DURATION"],[398,417,"ROLE"],[419,458,"ORGANISATION"],[781,803,"EDUCATION"],[805,825,"INSTITUTION"],[828,837,"LOCATION"],[839,848,"LOCATION"],[850,862,"DURATION"],[909,928,"SKILLS"],[934,951,"SKILLS"],[957,972,"SKILLS"],[978,990,"SKILLS"],[996,1006,"SKILLS"],[1012,1026,"SKILLS"]]}]]}