{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Nilesh Sahu\nKanpur, Uttar Pradesh\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Nilesh-Sahu/eaf3bbadafddc038\n\nWorking in \"Exceliun Solutions Pvt. Ltd.\" in Gurgaon, Haryana As a Senior Software \nDeveloper (OCT-2020 to TILL NOW). \n \nWorked at \"Compare Infobase Ltd.\" in Janakpuri, Delhi As a Web Developer \n(SEP-2019 to AUG-2020). \n \nWorked at \"Xeliumtech Solutions Pvt. Ltd.\" in Sector 18, Gurugram As a Web \nDeveloper (DEC-2015 to AUG-2019). \n \nWorked at \"Sumit Associates\" in Lucknow As a Web Developer (NOV-2014 to \nNOV-2015). \n \nPROFESSIONAL SUMMARY \n \nOver 7 years of experience in Web Development. \nHaving in-depth knowledge of Software Development. \nWorking knowledge of various Web Technologies like OOPS, JAVASCRIPT, J-QUERY, \nCORE PHP, LARAVEL, CakePHP, HTML, CSS, MYSQL, MONGODB, AGILE \nDEVELOPMENT, WEBSERVICES, REST API, WORDPRESS. \nA strong believer in teamwork, building cordial relations with people inside and outside \nthe organization, innovative solutions for difficult programming problems, self-learner \nand fast learning.\n\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\n\nPersonal Details\n\nDate of Birth: 1991-12-25\nEligible to work in: India\nHighest Career Level: 5+ years experience\nIndustry: Software Development\nTotal years of experience: 7\n\nWork Experience\n\nDeveloper\n\"Exceliun Solutions Pvt. Ltd.\" - Gurgaon, Haryana\nOctober 2020 to Present\n\nAs a Web Developer\n\"Compare Infobase Ltd.\" in Janakpuri - Delhi, Delhi\n\n\fSeptember 2019 to August 2020\n\nDeveloper\n\"Xeliumtech Solutions Pvt. Ltd.\" in Sector 18\nDecember 2015 to August 2019\n\nAs a Web Developer\n\"Sumit Associates\" - Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh\nNovember 2014 to November 2015\n\nPROFESSIONAL SUMMARY\nOver 7 years of experience in Web Development.\nHaving in-depth knowledge of Software Development.\nWorking knowledge of various Web Technologies like OOPS, JAVASCRIPT, J-QUERY,\nCORE PHP, LARAVEL, CakePHP, HTML, CSS, MYSQL, MONGODB, AGILE\nDEVELOPMENT, WEBSERVICES, REST API, WORDPRESS.\nA strong believer in teamwork, building cordial relations with people inside and outside the organization,\ninnovative solutions for difficult programming problems, self-learner\nand fast learning.\n\nEducation\n\nSenior Secondary - Kanpur, Uttar Pradesh\n2010\n\nB.Tech in Computer Science & Engg\nAxis Institute of Technology and Management - Kanpur, Uttar Pradesh\n\nBNSD Inter College - Kanpur, Uttar Pradesh\n\nSkills / IT Skills\n\n• Web Technology: JAVASCRIPT, J-QUERY, PHP, LARAVEL, CakePHP, CODEIGNITER, HTML, CSS, OOPS,\nWEBSERVICES, REST API, WORDPRESS. Database: Mysql, MongoDb. Server: Linux, Windows. Tools\nUsed: Visual Studio Code, Netbeans, Sublime text. Version Control: GIT, SNV. Project Management:\nJIRA. Project Name: Accounting System Project Brief: This is a web and manages the customer-\nsupplier, sales-purchase ledger, Invoices, Purchase order, Credit-note, debit-note, debtors-creditors,\nasset-product, bank/cash, balance sheet, financial reporting, financial planning, billing application\nmanagement, reconciliation, ledger, etc. Teamwork (5 members)\n\n• Analyze the requirement document provided by the client\n\n• Coding & Testing Technologies: PHP(Laravel Framework), MySQL, HTML, CSS, Ajax, JavaScript, jQuery\nProject Name: Care Kit Ordering System Project Brief: This is a web application and it's like a tool for\nproduct orders management. This system has three types of users, these are Admin, Supplier and\nStore. The system shall provide the support for\n\n• Store Management\n\n• Supplier Management\n\n• Product Management\n\n• Commission management\n\n• Order Management\n\n• Sales Order Management\n\n\f• Purchase Order Management\n\n• Invoice Management\n\n• Order dispatch and delivery management\n\n• Generated sales and purchase analysis reports. Teamwork (5 members)\n\n• Analyze the requirement document provided by the client\n\n• Writing use-case document\n\n• Writing test-case document\n\n• Coding, Database architecture & Testing Technologies: PHP(Laravel Framework), MySQL, HTML, CSS,\nAjax, JavaScript, jQuery Project Name: HTSS (Ticket Support System) Project Brief: HTSS is the web\napplication and shall manage the support enquiries that are requested from clients. When clients\nhave encountered any issue (Bug/Notice/Error) with the system or tool, they are trying to access,\nthey can report this to the IT Help desk via HTSS. The system then creates a record of the report/\nticket and Notifies an IT professional for assistance. Help-desk ticketing systems shall formalize the\nsupport process. The HTSS system automatically notifies the IT team whenever a ticket is created.\nThe automated notifications alert the client whenever any update or changes occurred on the Ticket.\nTeamwork (5 members)\n\n• Analyze the requirement document provided by the client\n\n• Writing use-case document\n\n• Writing test-case document\n\n• Coding, Database architecture & Testing Technologies: CORE PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Ajax,\n\nJavaScript, JQuery Project Name: Qizwiz Project Brief: A quiz based web application designed for\nthe user to play different types of quizzes. Playing a quiz will earn points which leads to you on the\ndashboard. Also, create apis for the mobile application. Individual work\n\n• Analyze the feature to implement for the application\n\n• Coding, Database architecture and Testing\n\n• Rest API Technologies: PHP(CakePhp), MySQL, HTML, CSS, Ajax, JavaScript, jQuery Project Name:\n\nMapsofindia Project Brief: A site has maps related details and many other utilities for the user to get\nTeamwork (4 members)\n\n• Coding and Database architecture\n\n• Rest Api Technologies: CORE PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Ajax, JavaScript, jQuery Project Name:\n\nMapsofindia\n\n• Myindia Project Brief: This is a web application. This application is related to blogging. This web\n\napplication provides a feature to the user to create their blog and post. User reads their blog and\nprovides reviews. Teamwork (4 members)\n\n• Coding and Database architecture Technologies: CORE PHP, Wordpress, MySQL, HTML, CSS,\n\nAjax, JavaScript, jQuery Project Name: Tata Hitachi Project Brief: This is a web application. In the\napplication, there is an admin panel which use for the representation of data on the maps. Data are\nplotted on the maps and it gives the user a representation view the user to understand the progress\nof the company. Teamwork (2 members)\n\n• Admin\n\n• Front\n\n• Admin\n\n• Database\n\n• Admin\n\n• Database Technologies: PHP(CakePhp), MySQL, HTML, CSS, Ajax, JavaScript, jQuery Project Name:\n\nVodafone Fx Project Brief: This is a template design application. In this application, the user designs\na template using the elements and published it to display on the android and ios applications.\nTeamwork (8 members)\n\n• Rest API Technologies: CORE PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Ajax, JavaScript, jQuery Project Name:\nGOM Project Brief: This application is related to health management. In this application, users\nregister themself as a patient and after that, a doctor is assigned to the patient who will monitor the\nprogress. Teamwork (4 members)\n\n\f• Rest API Technologies: CORE PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Ajax, JavaScript, jQuery\n\n• Front\n\n• Database\n\n• HTML5\n\n• PHP\n\n• JavaScript\n\n• SQL\n\n• Agile\n\n\f",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[12,18,"LOCATION"],[20,33,"LOCATION"],[121,149,"ORGANISATION"],[154,161,"LOCATION"],[163,170,"LOCATION"],[176,202,"ROLE"],[204,224,"DURATION"],[240,263,"ORGANISATION"],[267,276,"LOCATION"],[278,283,"LOCATION"],[289,302,"ROLE"],[305,325,"DURATION"],[341,373,"ORGANISATION"],[388,396,"LOCATION"],[402,416,"ROLE"],[418,438,"DURATION"],[454,472,"ORGANISATION"],[476,483,"LOCATION"],[489,502,"ROLE"],[504,525,"DURATION"],[560,567,"DURATION"],[585,601,"SKILLS"],[632,653,"SKILLS"],[706,710,"SKILLS"],[712,722,"SKILLS"],[724,731,"SKILLS"],[734,742,"SKILLS"],[744,751,"SKILLS"],[753,760,"SKILLS"],[762,766,"SKILLS"],[768,771,"SKILLS"],[773,778,"SKILLS"],[780,787,"SKILLS"],[796,807,"SKILLS"],[809,820,"SKILLS"],[822,830,"SKILLS"],[832,842,"SKILLS"],[1167,1175,"DURATION"],[1275,1305,"ORGANISATION"],[1308,1315,"LOCATION"],[1317,1324,"LOCATION"],[1325,1348,"DURATION"],[1369,1392,"ORGANISATION"],[1408,1413,"LOCATION"],[1415,1420,"LOCATION"],[1423,1452,"DURATION"],[1464,1496,"ORGANISATION"],[1510,1538,"DURATION"],[1545,1558,"ROLE"],[1559,1577,"ORGANISATION"],[1580,1587,"LOCATION"],[1589,1602,"LOCATION"],[1603,1633,"DURATION"],[1661,1668,"DURATION"],[1805,1809,"SKILLS"],[1811,1821,"SKILLS"],[1823,1830,"SKILLS"],[1832,1840,"SKILLS"],[1842,1849,"SKILLS"],[1851,1858,"SKILLS"],[1860,1864,"SKILLS"],[1866,1869,"SKILLS"],[1871,1876,"SKILLS"],[1878,1885,"SKILLS"],[1887,1904,"SKILLS"],[1906,1917,"SKILLS"],[1919,1927,"SKILLS"],[1929,1939,"SKILLS"],[2148,2164,"EDUCATION"],[2167,2173,"LOCATION"],[2175,2188,"LOCATION"],[2189,2193,"DURATION"],[2195,2228,"EDUCATION"],[2229,2272,"INSTITUTION"],[2275,2281,"LOCATION"],[2283,2296,"LOCATION"],[2298,2316,"INSTITUTION"],[2319,2325,"LOCATION"],[2327,2340,"LOCATION"],[2380,2390,"SKILLS"],[2392,2399,"SKILLS"],[2401,2404,"SKILLS"],[2406,2413,"SKILLS"],[2415,2422,"SKILLS"],[2424,2435,"SKILLS"],[2437,2441,"SKILLS"],[2443,2446,"SKILLS"],[2448,2452,"SKILLS"],[2454,2465,"SKILLS"],[2467,2475,"SKILLS"],[2477,2487,"SKILLS"],[2498,2503,"SKILLS"],[2505,2513,"SKILLS"],[2522,2527,"SKILLS"],[2529,2537,"SKILLS"],[2550,2568,"SKILLS"],[2570,2578,"SKILLS"],[2611,2614,"SKILLS"],[2616,2620,"SKILLS"],[2641,2646,"SKILLS"],[2661,2678,"PROJECTS"],[3412,3428,"SKILLS"],[3432,3451,"SKILLS"],[3455,3473,"SKILLS"],[3477,3498,"SKILLS"],[3502,3518,"SKILLS"],[3522,3544,"SKILLS"],[3549,3574,"SKILLS"],[3578,3596,"SKILLS"],[3619,3638,"SKILLS"],[3662,3688,"SKILLS"],[3831,3837,"SKILLS"],[3839,3860,"SKILLS"],[3863,3883,"SKILLS"],[3885,3888,"SKILLS"],[3889,3906,"SKILLS"],[3909,3914,"SKILLS"],[3916,3920,"SKILLS"],[3922,3925,"SKILLS"],[3927,3931,"SKILLS"],[3933,3943,"SKILLS"],[3945,3951,"SKILLS"],[3966,3994,"PROJECTS"],[6274,6279,"SKILLS"],[6313,6321,"SKILLS"],[6336,6339,"SKILLS"],[6340,6347,"SKILLS"],[6350,6355,"SKILLS"],[6357,6361,"SKILLS"],[6363,6366,"SKILLS"],[6368,6372,"SKILLS"],[6374,6384,"SKILLS"],[6386,6392,"SKILLS"],[6408,6419,"PROJECTS"],[6654,6662,"SKILLS"],[6664,6669,"SKILLS"],[6671,6675,"SKILLS"],[6677,6680,"SKILLS"],[6682,6686,"SKILLS"],[6688,6698,"SKILLS"],[6700,6706,"SKILLS"],[6721,6724,"PROJECTS"],[6956,6964,"SKILLS"],[6979,6987,"SKILLS"],[6989,6994,"SKILLS"],[6996,7000,"SKILLS"],[7002,7005,"SKILLS"],[7007,7011,"SKILLS"],[7013,7023,"SKILLS"],[7025,7031,"SKILLS"],[7035,7040,"SKILLS"],[7044,7052,"SKILLS"],[7056,7061,"SKILLS"],[7065,7068,"SKILLS"],[7072,7082,"SKILLS"],[7086,7089,"SKILLS"],[7093,7098,"SKILLS"]]}]]}