{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Nitin Kumar\r\nKaithal, Haryana\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Nitin-Kumar/efeb4b6a2c4a901d\r\n\r\nH. No. 249/26, \r\nBalaji Nagar, Kutubpur Raod, Gali No.: - 2, District Kaithal, Haryana Mobile: +91-80598-53507,\r\n98969-54077 \r\nEmail: nitinkumar53507@gmail.com \r\n \r\nWorking in an environment which gives me a chance to utilize my skills and talents to the best, which\r\nhelps me in obtaining a challenging position where opportunity for the growth and overall personality\r\ndevelopment is ample by keeping the organization's goal in mind.\r\n\r\nWilling to relocate: Anywhere\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nSale marketing\r\nGoyal trading company - Kaithal, Haryana\r\nJanuary 2020 to July 2021\r\n\r\nSale's man\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nM.Sc.Economics\r\nKurukshetra University - Kurukshetra, Haryana\r\n2019\r\n\r\nB.Sc.Economics (Hons.) in Economics\r\nKurukshetra University - Kurukshetra, Haryana\r\n2017\r\n\r\nCommerce\r\nBoard of School Education - Bhiwani, Haryana\r\n2014\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• OPERATING SYSTEM: Windows-XP, Vista and Windows-7 SOFTWARE PACKAGE: MS-Office 2003\r\n& 2007, internet Hardware Skills: The good knowledge of \"Computer Assembling, Installation &\r\nMaintenance\". Seminars & Conferences\r\n\r\n• Attending International Conference on \"BRICS and India Recent Developments, Challenges and\r\n\r\nOpportunities organized by Department of Economics, KUK\r\n\r\n• Basic computer knowledge\r\n\r\n• Marketing\r\n\r\n\f• Sales\r\n\r\n• Management\r\n\r\n• Business development\r\n\r\n• Hindi\r\n\r\n• English\r\n\r\n• Leadership\r\n\r\n• Negotiation\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[13,20,"LOCATION"],[22,29,"LOCATION"],[187,194,"LOCATION"],[203,218,"CONTACT"],[221,232,"CONTACT"],[242,267,"EMAIL"],[599,613,"ROLE"],[615,636,"ORGANISATION"],[639,646,"PERSON"],[648,655,"PERSON"],[657,682,"DURATION"],[713,727,"EDUCATION"],[729,751,"INSTITUTION"],[754,765,"LOCATION"],[767,774,"LOCATION"],[784,798,"EDUCATION"],[800,805,"EDUCATION"],[810,819,"EDUCATION"],[821,843,"INSTITUTION"],[846,857,"INSTITUTION"],[859,866,"LOCATION"],[876,901,"INSTITUTION"],[914,921,"LOCATION"],[923,930,"LOCATION"],[964,980,"SKILLS"],[982,993,"SKILLS"],[994,999,"SKILLS"],[1004,1013,"SKILLS"],[1032,1041,"SKILLS"],[1056,1064,"SKILLS"],[1105,1124,"SKILLS"],[1339,1363,"SKILLS"],[1369,1378,"SKILLS"],[1385,1390,"SKILLS"],[1396,1406,"SKILLS"],[1412,1432,"SKILLS"]]}]]}