{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["Nizamuddeen Auliya\r\nHSR layout, Bangalore, Karnataka\r\n-Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Nizamuddeen-Auliya/39aa01e6f5f99b3e\r\n\r\n◦ To obtain a challenging career opportunity, utilizing my technical and business skills. \r\n◦ To commit, demonstrate and work hard soastobea part of company's defining moment that\r\ntransforms the society and the world and to get the much needed exposure to new and innovative\r\nideas. o To creat new of creativity for the company growth updation like digitaly.\r\n\r\nWork Experience\r\n\r\nMarketing Manager\r\nAttica Gold Company - Hospet, Karnataka\r\nDecember 2014 to January 2016\r\n\r\n1. I worked as a collection executive in muthoot capital service limited for one year from 21/12/2014\r\nto 31/01/2016\r\n2. I have worked for malabar gold and diamonds as a Marketing Manager from 09/01/2016 to 03/03/2020.\r\n3. I have worked in abhyasa international residential school as a academic administrative officer from\r\n11/03/2020 to 25/03/2020.\r\n4. Now I am working in attica gold company, hospet as a branch manager from 03/09/2020 to till date.\r\n\r\nB C A in bachelor of computer application\r\nSri Mata Degree College - Hospet, Karnataka\r\n\r\nEducation\r\n\r\nPre-University Board\r\n2007\r\n\r\nS.S.L.C. in Education\r\nKarnataka Secondary\r\n2005\r\n\r\nSkills / IT Skills\r\n\r\n• Software Proficiency: \r\n\r\n• basic\r\n\r\n \r\n1. Knowledge of Windows Operating System, MS word and MS office. \r\n \r\n1. Excellent communication, analytical, and organizational skills. \r\n2. Leadership qualities, Willingness to learn, Ability to deal with people diplomatically\r\n\r\n\fCertifications and Licenses\r\n\r\nMBA\r\nJune 2011 to December 2012\r\n\r\nMarketing\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,18,"PERSON"],[32,41,"LOCATION"],[43,52,"LOCATION"],[520,537,"ROLE"],[539,558,"ORGANISATION"],[561,567,"LOCATION"],[569,578,"LOCATION"],[580,609,"DURATION"],[704,729,"DURATION"],[752,777,"ORGANISATION"],[783,792,"ROLE"],[806,831,"DURATION"],[853,893,"ORGANISATION"],[899,930,"ROLE"],[937,962,"DURATION"],[1068,1073,"EDUCATION"],[1077,1109,"EDUCATION"],[1111,1134,"INSTITUTION"],[1137,1143,"LOCATION"],[1145,1154,"LOCATION"],[1171,1191,"EDUCATION"],[1201,1209,"EDUCATION"],[1224,1243,"INSTITUTION"],[1333,1357,"SKILLS"],[1359,1366,"SKILLS"],[1371,1381,"SKILLS"],[1581,1584,"CERTIFICATE"],[1586,1612,"DURATION"],[1616,1625,"CERTIFICATE"]]}]]}