{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["RAHIL RIYAZ\r\n\r\nAdd:\r\n\r\nContact No:\r\n :\r\nEmail:\r\n\r\n              \r\n\r\n H.No- 5, Street No. 2, Ghulam Mehboob Road, \r\n Hathi Khana, Bhopal M.P (INDIA).\r\n 9644751518             (INDIA),\r\n\r\n rahilriyaz82@yahoo.co.in\r\n\r\nOBJECTIVE\r\nTo be engaged with an organization where my Civil AutoCAD skills can be applied as part of a dynamic team \r\nthat will work towards the growth of the company and contribute my level at best to its success.\r\n\r\nVIKAS ASSOCIATES ENGINEERS AND ARCHITECT\r\n\r\nPROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE\r\nName of \r\nOrganization:\r\nDepartment\r\nDuration:\r\nDesignation:\r\nJob Profile \r\n\r\nCIVIL AutoCAD\r\n2008 JAN. To 2010 FEB.\r\nDraughtsman\r\n\r\nDf \r\n \r\n      I was \r\n\r\n \r\n responsible for CIVIL department including:\r\n \r\n\r\n Draft new approved sketches at construction Site, Built drawings for clients and \r\n\r\nforward to finalize the approval .\r\n\r\n Prepare Structural designs and execute them hence forth.\r\n Prepare MEP Electrical designs as per specification and requirement.\r\n Architectural designs and samples for luxurious Shops/Villas.\r\n Preparation of wet area, Landscaping, false malfunctioning interiors, Kitchen details, \r\n\r\nElevation, Wardrobe details etc.\r\n\r\n Creating animated views and following up with clients requirement.\r\n Detailed Theory of whole design before executing it to final step it is sent to client to \r\n\r\ncross check if any alteration required as per their project.\r\n\r\nName of \r\nOrganization:\r\nDepartment/Posting \r\nDuration:\r\nDesignation:\r\nJob Profile \r\n\r\nASHRAY ENGINEER  & ARCHITECT\r\n\r\nCIVIL AutoCAD\r\n\r\nApril 2013 To Dec. 2015\r\nDraughtsman/Supervision\r\n\r\nDf  \r\n \r\n responsible for CIVIL department including:\r\n \r\nI      I was \r\n \r\n\r\n Calculate and find the difference of quantities between the drawings for the actual \r\n\r\nwork which is supposed to be executed on Site as per requirement.\r\n\r\n Keep a proper track of records and manage the additional changes of new drawing \r\n\r\nfor clients.\r\n\r\n Keeping an eye and having a detailed inspection of  Site as per approved there of \r\n\r\ndrawings and structures.\r\n\r\n Supervising projects of Buildings and Villas.\r\n Distribution of work to labors as per requirements.\r\n Managing Man Power, site requirement periodically.\r\n\r\n\fEDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION\r\nSr\r\n1\r\n2 Diploma in \r\n\r\nCourse/Class\r\n\r\n10th\r\n\r\nCollege/Grade\r\nGovt. Higher Sr. School Bhopal / 2nd\r\nEmperial institute of management\r\n science & research( Delhi)\r\n\r\nengineer(civil)\r\n\r\nYear of Completion\r\n2008\r\n2010 to 2012\r\n\r\nIT EXPERTISE\r\nSr Skills & Abilities \r\n1 Ms Office Word/Excel\r\n2 Net surfing and downloading\r\n3 AutoCAD : Architectural designing, Engineering \r\n\r\nDrawings, Highway Drawings, Draughtsman Work\r\nPrinting all Size A4/A3, Soft copies\r\n\r\n4\r\n\r\n5\r\nEmail, Scanning, Printing, Fax\r\n6 Xp operating, Windows/Vista/2007\r\n\r\nLANGUAGES/ COMMUNICATION SKILLS\r\n\r\nProficiency Level\r\nExcellent\r\nExcellent\r\nFully Versed\r\n\r\nLast Used / Practiced\r\nCurrently Using\r\nCurrently Using\r\nSince 5 Years till present\r\n\r\nExcellent\r\n\r\nExcellent\r\nExcellent\r\n\r\nRead\r\nExcellent\r\n\r\naverage\r\nExcellent\r\n\r\nCurrently Using\r\n\r\nCurrently Using\r\nCurrently Using\r\n\r\nWrite\r\nExcellent\r\n\r\naverage\r\nExcellent\r\n\r\nLanguage\r\nEnglish\r\nArabic\r\nUrdu\r\nHindi\r\n\r\nSpeak\r\n\r\n                  Average\r\n\r\nExcellent\r\nExcellent\r\n\r\nPERSONALITY TRAITS\r\n\r\n Solid Communicator.\r\n Strong problem solver.\r\n Adaptive to any situation.\r\n Ready to work in Shifts.\r\n Confident and persistency of work.\r\n\r\nACHIEVEMENTS\r\n\r\nPERSONAL DETAILS\r\nName\r\nFathers Name\r\nDate of Birth\r\nGender\r\nMarital Status \r\nNationality/Religion\r\nViza Status \r\n\r\nRAHIL RIYAZ\r\nMr. RIYAZ RASHEED\r\n01/01/1989\r\nMale\r\nSingle \r\nIndian/Muslim\r\n\r\n Certified for Windows XP Fundamentals/ MS Office from S.C.I.T.  COMPUTER  EDUCATIONAL \r\n\r\nTRAINING  CENTRE  BHOPAL  (M.P) INDIA.\r\n\r\n Certified for completing AutoCAD from BRAIN CUMPUTER  SOLUTIONS  BHOPAL (M.P). INDIA.\r\n\r\nNote: Above mention is all true to the belief of my knowledge and trust.\r\n\r\nRAHIL RIYAZ\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[129,135,"LOCATION"],[136,139,"LOCATION"],[141,146,"LOCATION"],[151,161,"CONTACT"],[187,211,"EMAIL"],[270,283,"SKILLS"],[434,474,"ORGANISATION"],[596,618,"DURATION"],[620,637,"ROLE"],[1481,1509,"ORGANISATION"],[1530,1553,"DURATION"],[1555,1584,"ROLE"],[2229,2233,"EDUCATION"],[2234,2241,"EDUCATION"],[2265,2269,"EDUCATION"],[2294,2311,"INSTITUTION"],[2312,2318,"LOCATION"],[2321,2379,"INSTITUTION"],[2381,2386,"LOCATION"],[2391,2406,"EDUCATION"],[2492,2501,"SKILLS"],[2502,2512,"SKILLS"],[2516,2527,"SKILLS"],[2547,2554,"SKILLS"],[2557,2580,"SKILLS"],[2582,2606,"SKILLS"],[2608,2624,"SKILLS"],[2626,2652,"SKILLS"],[2669,2680,"SKILLS"],[2692,2697,"SKILLS"],[2699,2707,"SKILLS"],[2709,2717,"SKILLS"],[2719,2722,"SKILLS"],[2726,2738,"SKILLS"],[2740,2758,"SKILLS"],[3521,3532,"PERSON"],[3534,3551,"PERSON"],[3613,3647,"CERTIFICATE"],[3653,3705,"INSTITUTION"],[3707,3713,"LOCATION"],[3716,3719,"LOCATION"],[3721,3727,"LOCATION"],[3758,3765,"CERTIFICATE"],[3771,3796,"INSTITUTION"],[3798,3804,"LOCATION"],[3806,3809,"LOCATION"],[3812,3818,"LOCATION"],[3898,3909,"PERSON"]]}]]}