{"classes":["PERSON","LOCATION","SKILLS","CONTACT","EMAIL","ROLE","ORGANISATION","DURATION","CERTIFICATE","PROJECTS","EDUCATION","INSTITUTION"],"annotations":[["SANJAYSINH  JADEJA\r\n\r\nVILLAGE\r\nTALUKA\r\nDIST\r\n\r\nMob.\r\nE-mail\r\n            \r\n\r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\n\r\n:\r\n:\r\n\r\nBEHIND POST OFFICE,\r\nMOTAKAPADA,\r\nDISA.\r\nBANASKATHA\r\nGUJARAT\r\n+91 9909545802\r\n \r\nsanjay4832@gmail.com\r\n\r\n \r\n  / sanjay4832@yahoo.co.in\r\n \r\n\r\n APPLICATION\r\n\r\nSub: Application for the vacant post stores in your esteemed \r\n\r\n .  \r\n Organization\r\n \r\n\r\n \r\n\r\nRespected Sir,\r\n\r\nI have come to know from some reliable sources that there is a vacancy in your reputed organization for\r\n\r\nabove position. I would like to apply my self for it.\r\n\r\nI have total 13 years experience store dept. of various construction companies. I will submit my credentials while\r\nreceiving your reply for attending the interview.\r\n\r\nI hope you will consider my application sympathically and looking forward for favorable, positive response at\r\nearliest convinced same as per requirement for the position.\r\n\r\nThanking you in anticipation.\r\n\r\nYours sincerely,\r\n\r\n(Jadeja Sanjaysinh S.)\r\n\r\n(Encl.: Curriculum Vitae)\r\n\r\n\fSANJAYSINH  JADEJA\r\n\r\nCURRICULUM VITAE\r\n\r\nVILLAGE\r\nTALUKA\r\nDIST\r\n\r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\n\r\nBEHIND POST OFFICE,\r\nMOTAKAPADA,\r\nDISA.\r\nBANASKATHA\r\nGUJARAT\r\n+91-9909545802                                                                                                       \r\nsanjay4832@gmail.com\r\n\r\nMob.\r\nE-mail\r\nPassport          :            N0649260 Validity 26.06.2025\r\n\r\n:\r\n:\r\n\r\n        \r\nCareer Objective:\r\n\r\nTo obtain a Sr. Store Officer Position with Carter\r\n\r\ns where I may be able to utilize my\r\nskills   in   managing   employees   and   store   operations   while   working   in   a   highly   stimulating   work\r\nenvironment.\r\n\r\ns where I may be able to utilize my\r\n\r\nPersonal Information :-\r\n\r\ns Name\r\n\r\nName\r\ns where I may be able to utilize my\r\nFather\r\nDate of Birth\r\nSex\r\nMarriage \r\nLanguage Proficiency :\r\n\r\nSanjaysinh Jadeja\r\nSukhdevsinh Jadeja\r\n5th May 1982\r\nMale\r\nMarried\r\n\r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\n:\r\nEnglish, Hindi and Gujarati\r\n\r\nAcademic Qualification:-\r\n\r\nSr.\r\nNo.\r\na)\r\nb)\r\nc)\r\nd)\r\n\r\nAcademic\r\nQualification\r\nSSC\r\nHSC\r\nBBA\r\nMBA\r\n\r\nComputer Skills:-\r\n\r\nUniversity/ Board\r\n\r\nPercentage\r\n\r\nSIR AJITSINHJI GOVT. HIGHSCHOOL\r\nSIR AJITSINHJI GOVT. HIGHSCHOOL\r\nSIKKIM MANIPAL UNIVERSITY\r\nSIKKIM MANIPAL UNIVERSITY\r\n\r\nYear of\r\nPassing\r\n1996\r\n1998\r\n2012\r\n2014\r\n\r\n42.43\r\n50.83\r\n51.00\r\n58.15\r\n\r\n(1) Operating Systems\r\n(2)  Store\r\n\r\n: Windows XP, MS Office.\r\n: SAP (System Applications Products, ERP(ENTERPRISE\r\n\r\nRESOURCE PLANNING) PMS SYSTEM, TALLY9,\r\n\r\nWork Experience:-\r\n\r\n14 years Experiences in Stores\r\n\r\n     \r\nTotal experiences are in Store Dept. of Various Construction Companies which is taking contract of\r\nconstruction of Industrial Building, Factory, power projects, and Infrastructures projects.\r\n\r\nPresently Working: - KUNAL STRUTURE INDIA PVT LTD\r\nProject  \r\nPosition\r\nDuration\r\n\r\n    : Tawa Canal Project  (Harda \r\n    : Store Officer \r\n    : 13th Feb’ 2017 To Till Date.\r\n\r\n MP) MP)\r\n\r\n\fPreviously Working Company :-\r\n \r\n\r\nFrom\r\n\r\nTo\r\n\r\nName  of Company\r\n\r\nDuration\r\n\r\nLocation\r\n\r\n20/06/2015\r\n12/02/2012\r\n11/06/2007\r\n25/02/2005\r\n\r\n31/01/2017\r\n15/05/2015\r\n15/01/2012\r\n30/05/2007\r\n\r\nApco Infratech Pvt. Ltd.\r\nSuyog Infra (I) Pvt. Ltd.\r\nDesai Construction Pvt. Ltd.\r\nJMC Projects (I) Ltd.\r\n\r\n1 Yrs \r\n4 Yrs \r\n4 Yrs \r\n2 Yrs \r\n\r\n MP)\r\n MP)\r\n MP)\r\n MP)\r\n\r\n 8 Month\r\n 03 Month \r\n 07 Month     \r\n 03 Month\r\n\r\nUttar Pradesh\r\nGujarat & MH\r\nGujarat & MH\r\nHyderabad (A.P)\r\n\r\nPreviously Working Projects:-\r\n\r\nFrom\r\n\r\nTo\r\n\r\nName  of Company\r\n\r\nProject\r\n\r\nLocation\r\n\r\n20/06/2015\r\n\r\n31/01/2017\r\n\r\nApco Infratech Pvt. Ltd.\r\n\r\nGorakhpur (UP)\r\n\r\n12/02/2012\r\n\r\n15/05/2015\r\n\r\nSuyog Infra (I) Pvt. Ltd.\r\n\r\n15/02/2008\r\n\r\n15/01/2012\r\n\r\nDesai Construction Pvt. Ltd.\r\n\r\n11/06/2007\r\n\r\n14/02/2008\r\n\r\nDesai Construction Pvt. Ltd.\r\n\r\nGandak Canal\r\nProject\r\nFord India Project\r\n\r\nBombay Rayon\r\nFashion Ltd\r\nPower Project\r\n\r\nSanand(Guj)\r\n\r\nBoiser (MH)\r\n\r\nKovaya (GJ)\r\n\r\n25/02/2005\r\n\r\n30/05/2007\r\n\r\nJMC Projects (I) Ltd.\r\n\r\nWipro Technology\r\n\r\nHyderabad\r\n\r\nResponsible for Maintain Books, Statements, Records as per ISO 9001.\r\nResponsible for managing all day to day stores related activities.\r\nCoordinating with site stores at different locations on a regular basis.\r\nMaterial Inward, outward management & Dispatch.\r\nReconciliation of materials.\r\nCo-ordination with purchase dept for all necessary documents.\r\nOverall inventory control.\r\nMaintain stock, supplies and inventories.\r\n\r\n Kamal Deep               :- +919473722439 (Apco -  Sr, Engineer)\r\n Pradeep Kumar        :- +919415816950 (Apco – HR & Admin)\r\n\r\nRs. 4.80 LPA + Food Facility + Bachelor Accommodation + Provident Fund  \r\n\r\nSr.\r\nNo.\r\n1.\r\n    2.\r\n3.\r\n4.\r\n\r\nSr.\r\nNo.\r\n    1.\r\n\r\n2.\r\n\r\n3.\r\n\r\n4.\r\n\r\n5.\r\n\r\n1.\r\n2.\r\n3.\r\n4.\r\n5.\r\n6.\r\n7.\r\n8.\r\n\r\nJob Profile :-\r\n\r\nReference:-\r\n\r\nCurrent Salary:-\r\n\r\nDeclaration:-\r\n\r\nbelief.\r\n\r\nDate:-\r\n\r\nPlace:-\r\n\r\nI hereby declare that the above provided information is correct to the best of my knowledge & \r\n\r\n(Jadeja Sanjaysinh S.)\r\n\r\n\f",{"entities":[[0,18,"PERSON"],[149,156,"LOCATION"],[158,172,"CONTACT"],[177,197,"EMAIL"],[208,230,"EMAIL"],[984,1002,"PERSON"],[1115,1122,"LOCATION"],[1124,1138,"CONTACT"],[1243,1263,"EMAIL"],[1395,1412,"ROLE"],[1796,1813,"PERSON"],[1815,1833,"PERSON"],[1993,1996,"EDUCATION"],[1998,2001,"EDUCATION"],[2003,2006,"EDUCATION"],[2008,2011,"EDUCATION"],[2071,2135,"EDUCATION"],[2137,2143,"LOCATION"],[2144,2162,"EDUCATION"],[2164,2170,"LOCATION"],[2171,2189,"EDUCATION"],[2306,2316,"SKILLS"],[2318,2328,"SKILLS"],[2332,2365,"SKILLS"],[2367,2403,"SKILLS"],[2404,2414,"SKILLS"],[2416,2422,"SKILLS"],[2705,2733,"ORGANISATION"],[2774,2792,"PROJECTS"],[2831,2859,"DURATION"],[2864,2866,"LOCATION"],[2869,2871,"LOCATION"],[2971,2981,"DURATION"],[2983,2993,"DURATION"],[2995,3005,"DURATION"],[3007,3017,"DURATION"],[3021,3031,"DURATION"],[3033,3043,"DURATION"],[3045,3055,"DURATION"],[3057,3067,"DURATION"],[3071,3122,"ORGANISATION"],[3124,3175,"ORGANISATION"],[3179,3184,"DURATION"],[3187,3192,"DURATION"],[3195,3200,"DURATION"],[3203,3208,"DURATION"],[3215,3217,"LOCATION"],[3222,3224,"LOCATION"],[3229,3231,"LOCATION"],[3236,3238,"LOCATION"],[3244,3251,"DURATION"],[3254,3262,"DURATION"],[3266,3274,"DURATION"],[3282,3290,"DURATION"],[3294,3307,"LOCATION"],[3309,3316,"LOCATION"],[3319,3321,"LOCATION"],[3323,3330,"LOCATION"],[3333,3335,"LOCATION"],[3337,3346,"LOCATION"],[3446,3470,"DURATION"],[3474,3516,"ORGANISATION"],[3520,3544,"DURATION"],[3548,3573,"ORGANISATION"],[3577,3601,"DURATION"],[3605,3633,"ORGANISATION"],[3637,3661,"DURATION"],[3665,3693,"ORGANISATION"],[3697,3718,"PROJECTS"],[3720,3738,"PROJECTS"],[3742,3767,"ORGANISATION"],[3793,3796,"LOCATION"],[3809,3811,"LOCATION"],[3824,3826,"LOCATION"],[3831,3855,"DURATION"],[3859,3880,"ORGANISATION"],[3884,3900,"ORGANISATION"],[3904,3913,"LOCATION"],[4346,4356,"PERSON"],[4374,4387,"CONTACT"],[4389,4393,"ORGANISATION"],[4397,4409,"ROLE"],[4414,4427,"PERSON"],[4438,4451,"CONTACT"],[4453,4457,"ORGANISATION"],[4460,4470,"ROLE"],[4862,4882,"PERSON"]]}]]}